<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><feed xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom' xmlns:openSearch='http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/' xmlns:gsx='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006/extended'><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>speakers</title><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/pub?key=t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw'/><link rel='http://schemas.google.com/g/2005#feed' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic'/><author><name>christine.lee</name><email>christine.lee@gmail.com</email></author><openSearch:totalResults>197</openSearch:totalResults><openSearch:startIndex>1</openSearch:startIndex><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/cpzh4</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 2</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: ﻿, speakerabstract: ﻿, speakerldap: ﻿</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/cpzh4'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/cre1l</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 3</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Aaron Koblin, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Aaron takes social and infrastructural data and uses it to depict cultural trends and emergent patterns. He received the National Science foundation’s first place award for scientific visualization and is part of the permanent collection of the Museum of Modern Art. Currently, Aaron is part of Google’s Creative Lab in San Francisco., speakerldap: AaronKoblin</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/cre1l'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/chk2m</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 4</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Adam Graff, speakercompany: Genentech, speakerabstract: Adam has worked in various roles at Genentech in software development, support and management while contributing to saving the lives of patients with unmet medical needs.  Adam leads a team that is implementing Google Apps for 18,000 employees.  They are also delivering innovative integrations between the Google Apps platform and other critical business systems that delight users, foster collaboration and increase productivity., speakerldap: AdamGraff</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/chk2m'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ciyn3</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 5</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Adam Nash, speakercompany: LinkedIn, speakerabstract: Adam joined LinkedIn in 2007 and has helped build a number of product &amp; technology teams. After taking over LinkedIn platform efforts in 2009, he led the effort to launch their first open platform, &lt;a href="http://developer.linkedin.com"&gt;developer.linkedin.com&lt;/a&gt;, and their full support for OAuth.  He currently spends his time focused on how the next generation of business applications will leverage social platforms., speakerldap: AdamNash</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ciyn3'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ckd7g</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 6</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Adam Powell, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Adam is a software engineer at Google with a background in small-scale games and a fascination with UI. As a member of the Android framework team, Adam is working to turn mobile devices into more approachable windows to the world's information., speakerldap: AdamPowell</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ckd7g'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/clrrx</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 7</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Adam Schuck, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Adam is the technical lead for the Google Wave client. Since commencing work at Google Sydney in February 2006, Adam worked on Google Maps, having co-created Mapplets in 2007. Having achieved a black-belt as a JavaScript ninja, Adam dusted off his Java textbook, threw away his ninja uniform, and embraced the new art of GWT. He received the University Medal for his B.S. with Honours in Computer Science from the University of New South Wales., speakerldap: AdamSchuck</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/clrrx'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/cyevm</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 8</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Alan Green, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Alan is a software engineer building enterprise and privacy features for Google Wave. Prior to joining Google, Alan consulted in a range of industries, including government, banking, insurance, airlines and telecommunications. His code still dispatches fire engines in at least one major city., speakerldap: AlanGreen</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/cyevm'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/cztg3</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 9</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Albert Cheng, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Albert is a software engineer on the iGoogle team. He currently leads the Gadget Development Tools projects. Interests include mountain climbing, enjoying free food, and fixing bugs., speakerldap: AlbertCheng</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/cztg3'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/d2mkx</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 10</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Albert Wenger, speakercompany: Union Square Ventures, speakerabstract: Albert is a managing partner at Union Square Ventures. He currently serves on the boards of Twilio, Foursquare, 10gen, AMEE, Covestor, and Clickable.  Albert has a Bachelors degree from Harvard and a PhD from MIT. He is married with three kids and lives outside New York City. Albert blogs at &lt;a href="http://continuations.com"&gt;http://continuations.com&lt;/a&gt;, speakerldap: AlbertWenger</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/d2mkx'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/cssly</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 11</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Alex Russell, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Alex is a member of the Google Chrome Frame team and a believer in the web as a democratizing platform. Prior to his work on Google Chrome Frame, Alex was Project Lead for the Dojo Toolkit JavaScript framework., speakerldap: AlexRussell</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/cssly'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/cu76f</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 12</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Alfred Fuller, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Alfred recently joined Google after getting his Ph.D. in Computer Science from the University of California, Davis. Since joining Google's App Engine team, he has worked primarily on improving the Datastore., speakerldap: AlfredFuller</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/cu76f'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/cx0b9</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 13</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Amit Agarwal, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Amit is a product manager at Google. He has spent the last 10+ years designing, developing and deploying infrastructure., speakerldap: AmitAgarwal</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/cx0b9'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/d9ney</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 14</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Amit Kulkarni, speakercompany: Manymoon, speakerabstract: Amit is the co-founder and CEO of Manymoon, a social productivity tool that helps people get work done by leveraging their connections and existing cloud platforms.  He has a passion for building applications that make people more productive. Amit has a BS in Electrical Engineering and minor in Computer Science from the University of Illinois, Urbana-Champaign., speakerldap: AmitKulkarni</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/d9ney'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/db1zf</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 15</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Amit Manjhi, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Amit is a software engineer on the Google Web Toolkit team, where he works towards GWT delivering "productivity for developers, performance for users." In particular, he has contributed to improving GWT's development mode, testability of GWT applications, and resource selection in GWT. He holds a Ph.D. degree in Computer Science from Carnegie Mellon University, has founded a VC-backed Web startup, and enjoys mathematical puzzles., speakerldap: AmitManjhi</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/db1zf'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dcgjs</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 16</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Amit Weinstein, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Amit is a developer on the Google Chart Tools team based in Israel. The team is now working on unifying the available chart tools in Google and enhancing them. When not at work, Amit is also working on his PhD in Computer Science at Tel Aviv University., speakerldap: AmitWeinstein</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dcgjs'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ddv49</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 17</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Anders Sandholm, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Anders is a Product Manager at Google. He launched the V8 JavaScript engine and Developer Tools in Google Chrome. Before coming to Google, Anders was a management consultant with McKinsey &amp; Company. Anders holds a PhD in computer science from the University of Aarhus and an MBA from INSEAD. , speakerldap: AndersSandholm</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ddv49'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/iow8x</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 18</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Angus Logan, speakercompany: Microsoft, speakerabstract: Angus helps websites connect with the 500 million people who use Windows Live including products such as Messenger., speakerldap: AngusLogan</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/iow8x'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/d415a</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 19</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Anne Veling, speakercompany: BeyondTrees, speakerabstract: After a M.Sc. in Computer Science/Artificial Intelligence, Anne worked for several years in the search engine industry, designing highly scalable knowledge extraction, clustering and visualization modules for search applications. Currently self-employed and helping out global companies deal with large amounts of loosely structured information as an internet application architect. Married, father of 3, theatresports addict, Lucene trainer., speakerldap: AnneVeling</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/d415a'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/d5fpr</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 20</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Arne Roomann-Kurrik, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Arne is a Developer Programs Engineer at Google, working with the Chrome team.  Just like the rest of you, he puts his pants on one leg at a time; except that once his pants are on, he makes excellent samples, developer tools, and documentation., speakerldap: ArneRoomann-Kurrik</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/d5fpr'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/d6ua4</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 21</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Bart Locanthi, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Bart joined Google in 2005 and most recently has worked on MyMaps and the Maps Data API. Prior to Google, he did freelance work on embedded languages and XML app servers. In ancient times, he was at AT&amp;T Bell Labs, where he worked on the Blit and Gnot (Plan9) terminals, CAD tools, and CS in general., speakerldap: BartLocanthi</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/d6ua4'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/d88ul</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 22</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Ben Appleton, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Ben is the tech lead manager for Google's Maps APIs.  He is interested in randomized algorithms and computational geometry.  Ben has a PhD in image analysis and degrees in electrical engineering and mathematics from the University of Queensland., speakerldap: BenAppleton</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/d88ul'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dkvya</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 23</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Ben Cheng, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Ben is a software engineer in the Android team working on Dalvik. His primary project is to develop a JIT compiler that improves the efficiency of the VM. He also spends time developing tools for performance tuning and code verification. Before Google, Ben worked at various companies on virtual machines, including Transmeta, Azul, and PeakStream. Ben got a PhD degree in Computer Science from University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign., speakerldap: BenCheng</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dkvya'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dmair</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 24</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Ben Collins-Sussman, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Ben is a tech lead and manager for Google Code's project hosting service. He was one of the founding developers of Subversion, and later helped port it to Google's Bigtable infrastructure. He also has a degree in mathematics, plays banjo, writes musicals, and takes lots of photos., speakerldap: BenCollins-Sussman</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dmair'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dnp34</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 25</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Ben Fried, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Ben is Chief Information Officer at Google and oversees Google's global technology systems. His extensive hands-on experience in technology includes stints as a dBASE II programmer, front-line support manager, Macintosh developer, Windows 1.0 programmer, and Unix systems programmer. Prior to joining Google, he spent more than 13 years in Morgan Stanley's technology department., speakerldap: BenFried</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dnp34'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/if29y</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 26</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Ben Huh, speakercompany: Cheezburger Network, speakerabstract: Ben is a former journalist turned dot com entrepreneur who has a knack for nailing the zeitgeist. He has been credited with bringing Internet memes to the mainstream and popularizing Internet culture. The success of his business is attributed to his knowledge of memes, viral content, and crowd sourcing. Ben graduated with a BSJ from Northwestern University’s Medill School of Journalism., speakerldap: BenHuh</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/if29y'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dp3nl</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 27</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Bill Buzbee, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Bill is a software engineer on Google's Android team, where he works on the Dalvik JIT Compiler.  Prior to Google, Bill worked on dynamic compilation at Hewlett-Packard and Transmeta.  He lives in Half Moon Bay with his wife, three kids and a dog., speakerldap: BillBuzbee</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dp3nl'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/df9om</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 28</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Bob Aman, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Bob works on the Developer Relations team at Google in Mountain View.  He loves contributing to open source, open web standards, and generally making the web a friendlier, more useful place for everybody.  Bob was once saved from a volcanic mishap by a bad case of malaria.  True story., speakerldap: BobAman</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/df9om'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dgo93</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 29</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Brad Feld, speakercompany: Foundry Group, speakerabstract: Brad is a managing director at the Foundry Group located in Boulder, Colorado.  He has been an early stage investor and entrepreneur for over 20 years.  Brad is also an avid art collector and long-distance runner. He has completed fifteen marathons as part of his mission to run a marathon in each of the 50 states., speakerldap: BradFeld</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dgo93'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dw4je</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 30</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Brad Fitzpatrick, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Brad is a software engineer on Google's Android team, where he works on performance.  Brad's also worked Google's social efforts and, prior to Google, founded Danga.com where he developed OpenID, LiveJournal and created open source server software such as memcached, Gearman, MogileFS, djabberd, etc.  Originally from Portland and Seattle, Brad now lives in San Francisco., speakerldap: BradFitzpatrick</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dw4je'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dxj3v</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 31</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Bradley Vickers, speakercompany: OAR Northwest, speakerabstract: Bradley obtained a Guinness World Record over the course of 71 days as part of the first crew to Row across the North Atlantic from New York, USA to Falmouth, England. He co-founded OAR Northwest and is on the board of Around-n-Over. Bradley’s shares his adventures in presentations that focus on achieving goals and developing leadership skills., speakerldap: BradleyVickers</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dxj3v'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dyxo8</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 32</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Brady Forrest, speakercompany: O'Reilly Media/Ignite, speakerabstract: Brady co-created &lt;a href="http://igniteshow.com"&gt;Ignite&lt;/a&gt; and is the Chair for O'Reilly's Where 2.0. Additionally, he co-Chairs the &lt;a href="http://web2expo.com"&gt;Web 2.0 Expo&lt;/a&gt; in San Francisco and NYC. Brady writes for &lt;a href="http://radar.oreilly.com/"&gt;O'Reilly Radar&lt;/a&gt; tracking changes in technology. Brady lives in Seattle, where he builds &lt;a href="http://heaid.com"&gt;music-making robots&lt;/a&gt; for Burning Man and runs &lt;a href="http://igniteseattle.com"&gt;Ignite Seattle&lt;/a&gt;. You can track his web travels at &lt;a href="http://trufflehoney.com/"&gt;TruffleHoney&lt;/a&gt;., speakerldap: BradyForrest</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dyxo8'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/e0c8p</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 33</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Brett Bavar, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Brett is a software engineer working on Google's AJAX APIs. Brett has worked on a few other projects during his time at Google, including the integration of Google Reader with Google Translate, which was his first 20% project., speakerldap: BrettBavar</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/e0c8p'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dqi9q</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 34</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Brett Slatkin, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Brett is the co-creator of the PubSubHubbub protocol and a Software Engineer on the Google App Engine team. He joined Google in 2005. He earned his B.S. in Computer Engineering from Columbia University in the City of New York. He lives in San Francisco., speakerldap: BrettSlatkin</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dqi9q'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/drwu7</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 35</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Brian Kennish, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Brian was the first support engineer at Google back when the AdWords API was launched. Since then, he’s helped launch four more Google developer products - Gadget Ads, the Analytics API, Wave, and Chrome Extensions. Brian is currently a developer advocate for Google Chrome., speakerldap: BrianKennish</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/drwu7'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dtbek</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 36</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Brian Rakowski, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Brian joined Google as the company's first Associate Product Manager in 2002. He worked on Gmail through launch until 2005 when he moved to Google's Zurich office. Brian has since returned to Google headquarters and has been working on Google Chrome since the project began. , speakerldap: BrianRakowski</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dtbek'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dupz1</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 37</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Brian Swetland, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Brian has been the Android Systems/Kernel technical lead since Android's startup days in 2005.  Prior to Android, Brian was responsible for the Hiptop OS and the 1.0 virtual machine at Danger, Inc.  Over ten years of mobile/embedded OS development has yet to completely destroy his sanity., speakerldap: BrianSwetland</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/dupz1'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/e7d2q</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 38</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Brian W. Fitzpatrick, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Brian started Google's Chicago engineering office in 2005. An open source contributor for over 10 years, Brian is the engineering manager for Google's Data Liberation Front, a member of the Apache Software Foundation, a former engineer at Apple and CollabNet, a Subversion developer, and a co-author of "Version Control with Subversion"., speakerldap: BrianWFitzpatrick</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/e7d2q'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/e8rn7</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 39</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Bruce Johnson, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Bruce founded the Google Web Toolkit project and Google's engineering office in Atlanta, Georgia., speakerldap: BruceJohnson</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/e8rn7'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ea67k</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 40</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Bryan McQuade, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: During his time at Google, Bryan has contributed to projects that make the web faster, including Shared Dictionary Compression over HTTP, optimizing web servers to better utilize HTTP, and most recently, the Page Speed web performance tool. Prior to working on web performance, Bryan was the first full time engineer on the Google TV Ads team, where he helped to build some of Google’s TV ad auction and video management systems., speakerldap: BryanMcQuade</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ea67k'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ebks1</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 41</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Chris Chabot, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Chris is a Developer Advocate at Google, who's interested in Open Source, OpenSocial, and trying to do the impossible. Most recently he's been the driving force behind PHP Shindig, the reference OpenSocial server implementation, Partuza a popular open-source example social network site that shows how to use OpenID, OAuth and OpenSocial, and the OpenSocial PHP client libraries., speakerldap: ChrisChabot</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ebks1'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ihves</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 42</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Chris Cole, speakercompany: MySpace, speakerabstract: Chris focuses on guiding and implementing open solutions for MySpace as a software architect and a core contributor and committer to the OpenSocial specification. Recently he co-authored the book “Building OpenSocial Apps.” He’s been an Internet developer from the gopher and Mosaic days, through the dot-com era, and into today’s social web and beyond., speakerldap: ChrisCole</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ihves'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/e1qt2</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 43</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Chris DiBona, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Chris is the open source and public sector programs manager at Google. His team oversees license compliance and supports the open source developer community through programs such as the Google Summer of Code and through the release of open source software projects and patches. In the public sector space, he looks after Google Moderator and the polling locations API., speakerldap: ChrisDiBona</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/e1qt2'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/e35dj</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 44</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Chris Dixon, speakercompany: Hunch, speakerabstract: Chris is co-founder/CEO of Hunch and co-founder of Founder Collective, a $40M early-stage VC fund. Previously he was co-founder/CEO of SiteAdvisor which was acquired by McAfee. As a software developer, Chris worked on high speed trading algorithms and later on multimedia software. He is a personal investor in startups including Skype, Gerson Lerhman Group, TrialPay, Invite Media, OMGPOP, DocVerse and Knewton.  He has a BA &amp; MA from Columbia and Harvard., speakerldap: ChrisDixon</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/e35dj'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/e4jxw</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 45</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Chris Lambert, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Chris is a software engineer working on location based services, including Google Latitude and the HTML5 network location provider in Chrome and Firefox. Previously, Chris spent some time in Google Research working on data mining for natural language translation. Chris graduated from Northeastern University in Boston with his BS in Computer Science., speakerldap: ChrisLambert</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/e4jxw'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/e5yid</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 46</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Chris Messina, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Chris got his start in 2004 by leading community marketing through the launch of Firefox. He is a board member of the OpenID and Open Web Foundations and plays an instrumental role in advancing OAuth and safer online computing. In 2008, Chris received the Google Open Source Award recognizing his community work on initiatives like microformats. He also co-founded the coworking and BarCamp communities and introduced hashtags on Twitter., speakerldap: ChrisMessina</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/e5yid'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/inhog</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 47</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Chris Nesladek, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Chris is a lead interaction designer on the Android project, with a focus on social. His work can be seen across the platform with the Quick Contact widget as well as the Contacts and Facebook applications. Prior to Android, Chris worked on projects with Danger, Intuit, and Sony Design Center. In addition to staying in shape through tennis and triathlon-related sports, Chris is an avid pizza aficionado., speakerldap: ChrisNesladek</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/inhog'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/eilm2</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 48</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Chris Pruett, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Chris works from Google's Japan office to support local Android application development. Prior to joining the Android team he worked as an engineer on Lively, Google's 3D online world. Chris worked for several years at a subsidiary of Activision, Inc developing video games. In his free time Chris enjoys dissecting horror games. Read about his research at &lt;a href="http://www.dreamdawn.com/sh"&gt;http://www.dreamdawn.com/sh&lt;/a&gt;., speakerldap: ChrisPruett</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/eilm2'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ek06j</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 49</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Chris Schalk, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Chris is a Developer Advocate at Google who engages both the App Engine and Enterprise OpenSocial communities. He has also worked on Google Friend Connect, Google AJAX APIs, Maps, Gears and Google Web Toolkit. Prior to Google, Chris was a Principal Product Manager at Oracle in the development tools group as well as co-author of "JavaServer Faces: The Complete Reference". In his spare time, he plays trumpet in local Bay Area symphonies., speakerldap: ChrisSchalk</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ek06j'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/eleqw</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 50</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Chris Vander Mey, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Chris is a Sr. Product Manager at Google where he works on Google Apps. He's shipped the Google Apps Marketplace, Google Apps Sync for Microsoft Outlook, elements of Chrome, and Google Pack.  Before Google, Chris was an engineering manager at Amazon and an early member of multiple startups. He earned a Masters of Engineering Management from Dartmouth and BS in Aerospace Engineering from the University of Virgina., speakerldap: ChrisVanderMey</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/eleqw'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/emtbd</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 51</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Chrix Finne, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Chrix (with an 'x'!) is a Product Manager at Google focused on Mobile Ads, where he is responsible for search ads and ads quality as well as mobile features in Google Analytics. Previously, he was Product Manager for Google Reader, where he helped develop some of Google's first social sharing features. Chrix is a graduate of Harvard University, and has also worked at Microsoft and Intellectual Ventures., speakerldap: ChrixFinne</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/emtbd'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/eczce</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 52</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Chuck Dietrich, speakercompany: Sliderocket, speakerabstract: Chuck is the CEO of SlideRocket.  Thousands of companies use SlideRocket’s web based presentation application to create stunning and interactive presentations that can be centrally managed and measured. Previously, Chuck spent 9 years at Salesforce.com and was the General Manager &amp; Vice President for Salesforce.com Mobile.  Chuck holds a BA from University of Colorado in Economics and an MBA from University of Utah. , speakerldap: ChuckDietrich</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/eczce'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/eedwv</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 53</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Ciaran Rochford, speakercompany: Samsung, speakerabstract: Ciaran is Director of Software Engineering at Samsung Mobile R&amp;D lab in San Jose, California, where he leads the Android R&amp;D effort. Since joining Samsung he has helped form a team experts focusing on JME and Android. Prior to joining Samsung, Ciaran worked at Sun Microsystems on the JME stack from its inception and related mobile platform technologies., speakerldap: CiaranRochford</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/eedwv'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ij9z9</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 54</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Dan Bornstein, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Dan joined Google in 2005 to join the Android project, continuing his work on virtual machines and related technology. He designed and co-developed the Dalvik virtual machine and core libraries, and he continues to lead the Dalvik team today. Dan earned an ScB in Cognitive Science from Brown University, and just for the record, he does not believe that he has any Icelandic ancestors., speakerldap: DanBornstein</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ij9z9'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/efsh8</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 55</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Dan Holevoet, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Dan Holevoet is a Developer Programs Engineer at Google, focused on Gadgets and Apps. In his free time he likes gardening, playing video games, and recycling speaker bios., speakerldap: DanHolevoet

</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/efsh8'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/eh71p</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 56</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Dan Peterson, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Dan is a Product Manager on Google Wave and President of the OpenSocial Foundation. Previously, Dan led the Google Web Toolkit (GWT) team as it became an open source project and worked on Google's infrastructure team on web search and data center management. Dan earned a B.S. in Computer Science from the University of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, as well as minors in Technology &amp; Management and philosophy. , speakerldap: DanPeterson</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/eh71p'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/etu5e</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 57</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Daniel Danilatos, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Dan is the tech lead for the Google Wave editor and has been using GWT for two years. Dan lives in Sydney, Australia. He earned a B.S. in Computer Science from the University of New South Wales. , speakerldap: DanielDanilatos</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/etu5e'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ewna8</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 58</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Daniel Lee, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Daniel joined the Developer Relations team at Google over 3 years ago.  He dedicated most of his time supporting and building up the community around the Google Gadgets API for iGoogle.  After spending over two years on the product, he shifted focus onto supporting the Google Maps APIs., speakerldap: DanielLee</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ewna8'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ey1up</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 59</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Daniel Raffel, speakercompany: Yahoo!, speakerabstract: Daniel is a Product Manager at Yahoo! on the Open Strategy team. He launched Yahoo! Pipes and Yahoo! Messenger with Voice. Previously, he worked at Songbird, ABC News Online, and CondeNet. Earlier in his career his passion for food led him to pursue a culinary degree which culminated in a stint as a chef in the kitchen of Thomas Keller’s NYC restaurant per se.  Daniel received a Masters from the Interactive Telecommunications Program at NYU. , speakerldap: DanielRaffel</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ey1up'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/eo7vq</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 60</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Dave Day, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Dave works in the Sydney office as the Tech Lead of the Maps Javascript API v2, as well as Maps Labs. Before joining Google, Dave studied electrical engineering and computer science at Sydney University and worked in the power industry on simulation and database software., speakerldap: DaveDay</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/eo7vq'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/epmg7</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 61</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Dave McClure, speakercompany: 500 Hats, speakerabstract: Dave likes to hang out with entrepreneurs, and occasionally help or invest in their startups if they let him. Dave has been geeking out in Silicon Valley for over twenty years, and has worked with companies such as PayPal, Mint, Founders Fund, Facebook, LinkedIn, SlideShare, Twilio, Simply Hired, O'Reilly Media, Intel, &amp; Microsoft. Dave also likes to play ultimate frisbee when his knees don't hurt., speakerldap: DaveSparks</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/epmg7'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/er10k</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 62</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Dave Sparks, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Dave  is the technical lead for the Android media framework. He was the principal author of the MMA's Downloadable Sounds specification (DLS) now part of the MPEG-4 and 3GPP standards., speakerldap: DaveMcClure</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/er10k'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/esfl1</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 63</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Dave Springer, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: David joined Google in 2008 and currently works on developer-facing tools for the Google Chrome and Native Client application development environment.  Prior to Google, David was at Apple where he developed debugging and performance measuring tools for OpenGL. He also worked at NeXT Computer where he developed Interactive RenderMan and the 3D aspects of NeXTSTEP. David was a founder of Alias Research, Inc. and received an Academy Award for his work on Alias Power Animator., speakerldap: DaveSpringer</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/esfl1'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/a59y2</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 64</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Dave Wang, speakercompany: Booyah, speakerabstract: Dave is a veteran of the exploding geo-location space with a proven track record in both the application and technology-enabling layers.  Dave has been integral to driving the product roadmap, design, and rapid user growth of the MyTown franchise.  Prior to joining Booyah, Dave was the Sr. Director of Marketing at SiRF/Centrality, focusing on location platforms and services. Dave graduated from Stanford University with a dual Masters in EE/MS&amp;E Dave and received a BS in EE/CS from UC Berkeley., speakerldap: DaveWang</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/a59y2'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/a6oij</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 65</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: David  Byttow, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: David has been a software engineer for 8 years and is currently working on Google Wave out of Mountain View, CA where he has focused his efforts primarily on Google Wave APIs. Prior to joining Google in 2008, David developed video games for popular gaming consoles and has since hung up his C++ hat to embrace all sorts of newfangled languages and technologies., speakerldap: DavidByttow</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/a6oij'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/a832w</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 66</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: David Erb, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: David is a technical lead at Google in Seattle. Since joining Google in 2005, David has also worked on projects related to mobile phones and telephone systems. Prior to Google, David worked at Microsoft, Borland, SRI International, and numerous start-ups., speakerldap: DavidErb</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/a832w'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/a9hnd</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 67</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: David Glazer, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: David is an Engineering Director at Google where he leads the Developer Platforms team and is responsible for Google's developer-facing APIs, tools, and hosting offerings. He is active in Google's ongoing contributions to the social web, including being on the board of the OpenSocial Foundation.  Prior to Google, David was a founder of Eloquent (later acquired by Open Text) and Verity., speakerldap: DavidGlazer</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/a9hnd'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/9znoe</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 68</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: David LaPalomento, speakercompany: Novell, Inc., speakerabstract: David is the lead frontend developer for the Novell Pulse project.  He is interested in the challenges of building large-scale and concurrent systems, test-driven development and delivering innovative user experiences through emerging web standards.  He has worked on Pulse since its inception. , speakerldap: DavidLaPalomento</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/9znoe'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/a128v</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 69</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: David Primmer, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: David is a software engineer working on the security technologies used in Google Developer Platforms, including OAuth, OpenID and Secure Data Connector. David is a former systems and database administrator with a wide background managing the business computing environment., speakerldap: DavidPrimmer</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/a128v'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/a2gt8</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 70</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Debajit Ghosh, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Debajit is the tech lead manager for the Android Sync Team and has worked on Android through all of its major releases.  He previously worked on Google’s mobile efforts, focusing on server-side infrastructure for browser-based properties.  Prior to Google, Debajit worked on speech recognition technology at Nuance Communications and has Bachelor’s and Master’s degrees from MIT., speakerldap: DebajitGhosh</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/a2gt8'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/a3vdp</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 71</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: DeWitt Clinton, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: DeWitt is a technical lead on Google's developer team, focused on building product APIs, growing the developer ecosystem, and defending the open web. Previously, DeWitt held engineering and product management roles at Amazon, Travelocity, Microsoft, several successful early Internet ventures, and several not-quite-as-successful Internet adventures. DeWitt holds a BA in Computer Science and Political Science from Williams College. He enjoys each and every day., speakerldap: DeWittClinton</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/a3vdp'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ivx4q</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 72</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Dhanji Prasanna, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Dhanji contributes to open source projects in his free time such as Google Guice, Google Wave, Sitebricks and the MVEL language. Dhanji is the author of "Dependency Injection: Design Patterns", a book published by Manning in 2009. He represents Google on several Java expert groups including Servlet and JAX-RS. Say hi to him at: &lt;a href="http://twitter.com/dhanji"&gt;http://twitter.com/dhanji&lt;/a&gt;., speakerldap: DhanjiPrasanna</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ivx4q'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/agihe</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 73</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Dick Costolo, speakercompany: Twitter, speakerabstract: Dick is the COO of Twitter, Inc. Prior to Twitter, he worked in the Ads product group at Google. Dick was co-founder and CEO of FeedBurner, which was acquired by Google in June 2007. , speakerldap: DickCostolo</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/agihe'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ahx1v</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 74</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Dino Brusco, speakercompany: Motorola, speakerabstract: Dino is the Senior Director of Android Product Management at Motorola. In the past, he has held key management positions with Palmsource, Turbolinux, Hewlett-Packard and Concurrent Computer Corp. Dino has led product development, software developer communities, marketing, software support and services organizations., speakerldap: DinoBrusco</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ahx1v'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ajbm8</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 75</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Don Dodge, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Don is a Developer Advocate focusing on helping developers work with Google Apps. Don recently joined Google after 5 years as a developer evangelist at Microsoft. Don is a veteran of five start-ups including Forte Software, AltaVista, Napster, Bowstreet, and Groove Networks and has been in the software business for more than 25 years. Don spent 5 years at Microsoft working with VCs and start-ups in the greater Boston area., speakerldap: DonDodge</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ajbm8'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/akq6p</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 76</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Don Schwarz, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Don is a software engineer in Google's Chicago engineering office. He has worked on a number of projects including Google Mashup Editor and most recently as one of the co-creators of Google App Engine for Java. Prior to joining Google, Don wrote distributed systems for a large financial institution., speakerldap: DonSchwarz</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/akq6p'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/aaw7q</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 77</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Douwe Osinga, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Douwe is the technical lead for the Google Wave APIs. After studying Computer Science and Philosophy at the Free University in Amsterdam, Douwe started various companies with widely differing amounts of success. After becoming bored with talking to customers, he joined Google in 2004, working on Search Quality, Google Trends, and on SMS Channels in India. , speakerldap: DouweOsinga</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/aaw7q'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/acas7</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 78</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Eric Ayers, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Eric is a Software Engineer on the Speed Tracer team and is also the maintainer of the Google API Library for GWT. He holds a Master's Degree in Computer Science from the Georgia Institute of Technology. Eric enjoys hobby electronics and is a 5 year veteran mentor of the FIRST program, inspiring elementary through high school students to develop interest in pursuing careers in technology through building robots. , speakerldap: EricAyers</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/acas7'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/adpck</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 79</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Eric Bidelman, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Eric is an engineer and developer advocate at Google. He works on the Google Data APIs, primarily on the Google Documents List, Google Health, and the Authentication APIs. Prior to Google, Eric worked as a software engineer at the University of Michigan where he designed rich web applications and APIs for the university's 19 libraries. Eric holds a B.S.E in Computer Engineering and a B.S.E in Electrical Engineering from the University of Michigan, Ann Arbor., speakerldap: EricBidelman</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/adpck'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/af3x1</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 80</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Erik Hellman, speakercompany: Sony Ericsson, speakerabstract: Erik has worked on projects ranging from large-scale telecom systems to mobile application development; now he is one of the principal Software Architects for Android at Sony Ericsson. Despite being severely colorblind, he manages to oversee most of the architectural aspects of Android application development within Sony Ericsson while still having time to write code himself., speakerldap: ErikHellman</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/af3x1'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/arr0q</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 81</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Erik Kay, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Erik is an engineer on the Google Chrome team.  He's currently a lead on the extensions project and also designed Chrome's autoupdate system., speakerldap: ErikKay</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/arr0q'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/at5l7</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 82</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Evan Roseman, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Evan joined Google in 2005 and is a software engineer in Google's Search Quality Team.  His primary focus is on Webspam in Google's search index.  Prior to joining Google, Evan studied Computer Science at Rice University., speakerldap: EvanRoseman</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/at5l7'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/auk5k</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 83</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Evin Levey, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Evin is a Product Manager on the Google Apps team, managing the Docs Platform and Google Apps Script.  Before joining Google three years ago, he spent more than eight years at a video game middleware startup, working variously as coder, manager and salesman, focused exclusively on the developer community.  Evin has a Masters in Computer Science from Trinity College, Dublin., speakerldap: EvinLevey</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/auk5k'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/avyq1</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 84</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Gareth McSorley, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Gareth is a Software Engineer with Google Switzerland who spends most of his time tinkering with the YouTube APIs. His main focus is the handling of video uploads., speakerldap: GarethMcSorley</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/avyq1'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/am4r2</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 85</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: German Bauer, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: German joined Google in 2006, working on the Android mobile operating system UI on both interaction and visual design. Before Google, he worked at Adobe, Apple, Claris, Netscape and Motorola on mobile and desktop products. German has a background in Industrial Design working in medical and consumer areas., speakerldap: GermanBauer</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/am4r2'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/anjbj</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 86</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Gideon Mann, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Gideon has worked as a research scientist at Google in New York City since 2007. His recent published work has been in weakly supervised learning and large-scale distributed training., speakerldap: GideonMann</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/anjbj'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/aoxvw</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 87</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Greg D'alesandre, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Greg is a Product Manager on Google Wave based in Sydney, Australia. Before heading down under he was a PM for Google Sites and Google Groups. Pre-Google Greg worked at a variety of start-ups in a variety of roles, most recently as a Product Manager for JotSpot leading up to the Google Acquisition. Eons ago, when the sun was still young, Greg received his ScB and ScM in Electrical Engineering from Brown University. , speakerldap: GregD'alesandre</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/aoxvw'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/aqcgd</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 88</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Greg Grothaus, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Greg is a Staff Software Engineer who joined Google's Search Quality team in 2005, where he is responsible for maintaining the quality of the search results in Google's search index.  Prior to Google, he studied Computer Science with an interest in Bioinformatics at Virginia Tech., speakerldap: GregGrothaus</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/aqcgd'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/b2zk2</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 89</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Guido van Rossum, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Guido is the creator of the Python programming language. He joined Google in 2005. In 2007 he joined the Google App Engine team, where he has been working on Python language support, API design, UI programming, the Admin Console, and developer tools., speakerldap: GuidovanRossum</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/b2zk2'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/b5sow</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 90</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Helen Chen, speakercompany: Cisco, speakerabstract: Helen is a software development manager at Emerging Technologies Group with Cisco Systems, Inc., where she leads OpenSocial enterprise adoption at Cisco Pulse and web application development. Her expertise includes web 2.0, User Experience, and social applications., speakerldap: HelenChen</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/b5sow'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/b779d</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 91</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Ian Fette, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Ian joined the Google Chrome team as a product manager in 2007, focused on security, browser infrastructure, and the team's implementation and development of new web standards. Prior to joining Google, Ian worked for the U.S. Government. Ian has degrees in Computer Science from the University of Michigan and Carnegie Mellon University., speakerldap: IanFette</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/b779d'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/axdae</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 92</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Ian Lewis, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Ian has spent many years in the computer game industry. He was part of the launch team for the Xbox 360 and is credited on numerous titles such as Halo 3 and Grand Theft Auto 4. He joined Google in 2009 and is currently working on the Native Client team to make Chrome the ultimate platform for developers., speakerldap: IanLewis</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/axdae'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ayruv</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 93</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Ian Taylor, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Ian works on the Go compiler.  He is the primary author of the gold linker and (years ago) Taylor UUCP, and has worked on a number of other free software projects., speakerldap: IanTaylor</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ayruv'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/b06f8</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 94</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Irwin Boutboul, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Irwin is a software engineer with Google NYC. He works on building enterprise applications on App Engine. Before joining Google, Irwin worked on grid computing, VoIP and social networks at IBM. He then enjoyed going bankrupt with Lehman Brothers building real time trading systems in Java., speakerldap: IrwinBoutboul</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/b06f8'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/b1kzp</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 95</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: J.D.  Zamfirescu Pereira, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: J.D. is a software engineer focused on open sourcing the Google Wave code. J.D. left Google to become CTO at AppJet, the makers of EtherPad. AppJet was acquired by Google in December 2009, and J.D. is excited to be back -- this time, in sunny Sydney, Australia. He holds S.B. and M.Eng. degrees from MIT, speakerldap: J.D.ZamfirescuPereira</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/b1kzp'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/be856</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 96</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Jaime Yap, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Jaime is a software engineer on the Google Speed Tracer team. He is a contributor to the Google Web Toolkit project, and loves expanding the boundaries for what can be accomplished in the browser. Jaime earned his Masters degree in Computer Science from the Georgia Institute of Technology in 2007, and has been with Google since 2008. He currently resides in Atlanta and enjoys long walks on the beach., speakerldap: JaimeYap</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/be856'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bfmpn</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 97</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: James Kelm, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Jim is a Product Manager at Google responsible for AdSense for Mobile Applications. He previously worked on a variety of payments, commerce, shopping, and mobile projects at Google. Jim holds degrees from Columbia and MIT. Before Google he worked at Sun Microsystems on Solaris and Apple on consumer portables. Outside work, Jim has run or consulted on Internet strategy in several high profile political campaigns., speakerldap: JamesKelm</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bfmpn'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bh1a0</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 98</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: James Young, speakercompany: Local Credit Union, speakerabstract: James is a happy father, husband, and geek. He voraciously read books and will read anything. James also builds (and fights) model warships. He belongs to northern Utah and feels that life isn't complete without mountains. James goes backpacking in the summer and snowboarding in the winter., speakerldap: JamesYoung</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bh1a0'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ba0fz</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 99</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Jay Simons, speakercompany: Atlassian Software, speakerabstract: Jay leads sales &amp; marketing for Atlassian, who sell ~$60M annually in software development tools directly to developers over the Web. Atlassian's tools include JIRA, an issue tracker for IT project management, Confluence, an advanced enterprise wiki, and Studio, a hosted software development suite integrated with Google Apps., speakerldap: JaySimons</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ba0fz'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/b8lvi</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 100</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Jeff Chang, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Jeff joined the Google Chrome team as a product manager in September 2009. He currently focuses on the web platform, plug-ins, and Chrome's user-facing features. Prior to joining Google, Jeff received a B.S. in Computer Science and Engineering from MIT., speakerldap: JeffChang</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/b8lvi'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bifuh</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 101</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Jeff Clavier, speakercompany: SoftTech VC, speakerabstract: Jeff is the Founder and Managing Partner of SoftTech VC, one of the most active seed stage investors in Web 2.0 startups. Since 2004, Jeff has invested in more than 60 consumer Internet companies in areas like social media, communities, search, gaming or consumer infrastructure, almost exclusively in Silicon Valley., speakerldap: JeffClavier</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bifuh'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bpgoi</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 102</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Jeff Scudder, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Jeff has been an engineer with Google since 2006 and has worked on products including the AdWords API, Google Data APIs, App Engine, Google AJAX APIs, and Google Web Elements. After graduating from Baylor with a CS degree, Jeff worked on web services at Boeing. When not crafting code, Jeff's been known to strum the guitar and be otherwise musical., speakerldap: JeffScudder</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bpgoi'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bbf0c</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 103</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Jeffrey Posnick, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Jeff is a member of Google's Developer Relations team. He currently helps developers navigate the ins and outs of the YouTube APIs. Based in New York City, Jeff is happy to be making his first trip out to Google I/O in San Francisco., speakerldap: JeffreyPosnick</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bbf0c'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/btodt</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 104</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Jez Fletcher, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Jez joined Google in 2008 after deciding academia wasn't the thrill-ride he'd expected. Since joining Google, Jez has worked on just about everything in the Google Geo APIs spectrum, including the v2 and v3 JS API, the Maps API for Flash and the Static Map API., speakerldap: JezFletcher</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/btodt'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bqv8z</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 105</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Jim Palmer, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Jim is the head of the Android UX team. Prior to joining Google, he worked on consumer experiences for Motorola, Good Technology, Liberate, and Apple. , speakerldap: JimPalmer</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bqv8z'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bl8zb</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 106</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Jimin Li, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Jimin is a Software Engineer on the Google Wave team working on Wave Media and API Projects. Prior to Google Wave, Jimin led Revenue and Reporting team of Google Relationship Manager. Prior to Google, Jimin was a Software Engineer in the Customer Relationship Management industry., speakerldap: JiminLi</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bl8zb'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bo245</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 107</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Jochen  Bekmann, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Jochen is Tech Lead for federation on Google Wave. Prior to that, he worked on concurrency control and the wave server and on Google Maps at some point. He worked on TCP/IP at Microsoft and was part of a few start-ups before that. The dazzling allure of academia didn't entirely pass him by (PhD(UNSW), BScHons,BCom(UCT)). , speakerldap: JochenBekmann</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bo245'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/c0p7u</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 108</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Joe Kraus, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Joe is a partner at Google Ventures focused on mobile, gaming and local services. Previously, he was a two-time entrepreneur. In 1993, he co-founded Excite.com, an early Internet search engine. In 2004, he co-founded JotSpot, a wiki company that was acquired by Google in 2006. While at Google, Joe held multiple product management roles. He is also on the board of the EFF., speakerldap: JoeKraus</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/c0p7u'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bmnjo</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 109</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Joel Webber, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Joel is a software engineer at Google and the co-creator of the Google Web Toolkit. Before working at Google, Joel spent his time banging bits and building cross-platform UI frameworks for mobile devices at AppForge. Still earlier, he was a game engine developer, but oddly enough finds working at Google to be more fun than writing games., speakerldap: JoelWebber</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bmnjo'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bv2y6</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 110</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: John Panzer, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: John hacks social software, standards, and products.  He has participated in the Atom, AtomPub, OpenID, OAuth, OpenSocial, and Salmon standards efforts.  He has helped to launch groups and blogging products at AOL and most recently managed Blogger.  He is now working on open standards for the Social Web., speakerldap: JohnPanzer</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bv2y6'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/c4wx5</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 111</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: John Zeratsky, speakercompany: YouTube, speakerabstract: John is a senior designer at YouTube. Prior to that he was a user experience lead at Google, focused on the company's suite of advertising products for agencies. From 2005 through 2007, he helped create FeedBurner, which was acquired by Google in June 2007., speakerldap: JohnZeratsky</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/c4wx5'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/c3ico</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 112</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Joon Kang, speakercompany: LG Electronics Mobile Research, speakerabstract: Joon has a broad and unique combination of experience in new business development, mobile and web technology and product strategy development. Prior to joining LG, Joon has been playing a pivotal role at Yahoo Search Marketing where he led global technology development and partner management.  Joon studies at POSTECH, Korea, Columbia University and U.C. Berkeley, received Bachelor of Science and MBA emphasis on international business and technology management., speakerldap: JoongKang</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/c3ico'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bwhin</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 113</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Joseph Schorr, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Joey is a software engineer on the Google Data team and is responsible for all API configuration development, including API automated configuration tools. Joey has worked at Google for almost two years and is a graduate of the University of Pennsylvania, with degrees in Computer Science and Business., speakerldap: JosephSchorr</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bwhin'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bxw30</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 114</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Joseph Smarr, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Joseph is a software engineer at Google, focused on socially enabling the web using open standards. Previously, he was Plaxo's Chief Technology Officer. He is also a member of the Board of Directors of the OpenID Foundation. A frequent speaker and community participant in the social networking and web development communities, Joseph has built web applications for many years., speakerldap: JosephSmarr</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bxw30'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ceqw0</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 115</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Josh Livni, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Josh is a Developer Programs Engineer, currently focusing on KML and the Earth API.  Before joining Google, he worked as a consultant, integrating analytic, cartographic, and statistical tools on the web. Josh is an active member of the open source geospatial community, and plans to spend more time paragliding right after I/O., speakerldap: JoshLivni</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ceqw0'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/cdcbn</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 116</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Justin Mattson, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Justin is a Developer Advocate at Google. For the past year he has devoted his time to Android. Before that he spent time on some of Google's ads products. He has a strong interest in operating system architectures, macro economics, and advanced armchair physics., speakerldap: JustinMattson</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/cdcbn'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/c6bhi</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 117</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Justin McWilliams, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Justin is a developer in Corporate Engineering based in Google NYC. He has been building enterprise web applications on App Engine for the past year, previously filling a desktop support role since he joined Google in 2006.  Justin graduated from the University of Michigan with a BA in 2005., speakerldap: JustinMcWilliams</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/c6bhi'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/cg5gh</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 118</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Kara Swisher, speakercompany: Wall Street Journal, speakerabstract: Kara started covering digital issues for The Wall Street Journal's San Francisco bureau in 1997 and also wrote the BoomTown column about the sector. With Walt Mossberg, she co-produces and co-hosts D: All Things Digital, a major high-tech and media conference., speakerldap: KaraSwisher</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/cg5gh'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/cbxr6</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 119</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Kathrin Probst, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Kathrin is a software engineer on the Google Web Toolkit team. Most recently, she has worked on making Ajax applications crawlable, and is now contributing to the next generation of the Google Plugin for Eclipse. Kathrin earned her Ph.D. in Computer Science in 2005, and has been with Google since 2008. She lives in Atlanta with her family, which she loves because she gets to spend lots of time outside., speakerldap: KathrinProbst</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/cbxr6'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bzanh</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 120</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Kelly Norton, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Kelly writes software for Google and enjoys working in the gooey area between humans and technology. He has a range of quirky experience from network hardware to graphic design and is a contributor to the Google Web Toolkit project. Kelly is the proud owner of two degrees both with ornate lettering, the first in electrical engineering from Georgia Tech and the second from the MIT Media Lab., speakerldap: KellyNorton</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/bzanh'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hmyxm</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 121</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Kevin Gibbs, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Kevin joined Google in 2004 and is the technical lead and manager of the Google App Engine project. Prior to his work on Google App Engine, Kevin worked for a number of years in Google's systems infrastructure group, where he worked on the cluster management systems that underlie Google's products and services. Kevin created Google Suggest, the product which provides interactive search suggestions as you type on the Google homepage., speakerldap: KevinGibbs</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hmyxm'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/caj6t</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 122</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Kris Muller, speakercompany: Salesforce.com, speakerabstract: Kris is a product marketer with Salesforce.com. He joined the company in 2006 and enjoyed several years of selling the Force.com platform and CRM apps as a sales engineer. He's now pushing to make the workplace more collaborative and is fired up by the collective intelligence that Salesforce Chatter delivers. , speakerldap: KrisMuller</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/caj6t'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/c94mc</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 123</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Kuan Yong, speakercompany: YouTube, speakerabstract: Kuan is the Product Manager for the YouTube developer platform. Prior to working on the YouTube APIs, he worked on enterprise video hosting, mobile syndication and monetization, launching Google Video for business and AdSense for mobile content. Kuan loves his iPhone and writes iPhone apps in his spare time., speakerldap: KuanYong</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/c94mc'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hps2g</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 124</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Lars Rasmussen, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Lars is a member of Google's technical staff, based in the Sydney office, and with his brother Jens is co-founder of the Google Wave effort. In early 2003, the brothers co-founded a mapping start-up, Where 2 Technologies, which was acquired by Google in October of 2004. Lars joined Google and worked as one of the lead engineers in the team that turned this acquisition into Google Maps, now used by millions of people around the world. Lars holds a Ph.D. in theoretical computer science from the University of California at Berkeley. Lars has possibly the world's least developed sense of direction, and consistently types faster than he can spell. , speakerldap: LarsRasmussen</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hps2g'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hodi3</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 125</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Linus Upson, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Linus joined Google in 2005 and is currently a vice president of engineering overseeing Google's browser products including Chrome and Chrome OS. , speakerldap: LinusUpson</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hodi3'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hhcny</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 126</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Loic Le Meur, speakercompany: Seesmic, speakerabstract: Loic is Founder and CEO of Seesmic, one of the most popular Twitter and Facebook social apps. He also founded and hosts the #1 European internet conference, LeWeb, with his wife Geraldine. Loic was named one of the "25 Most Influential People on the Web" and 'Young Global Leader' by Business Week and the World Economic Forum, respectively. He lives in San Francisco and has three boys., speakerldap: LoicLeMeur</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hhcny'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hr6mx</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 127</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Mano Marks, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Mano joined Google's Geo API team in 2006. He helps large companies, small startups, and international aid organizations all over the world develop and deploy their content in KML and Google Maps. Before Google, Mano had an eclectic career that involved getting a Masters in History, a Masters in Information Management and Systems, and working as a data manager in small and mid-sized organizations for over a decade., speakerldap: ManoMarks</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hr6mx'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/c7q1z</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 128</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Marc Ridey, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Marc is a Software Engineer working on Google Maps JavaScript API v3. His focus for the past year has been on mobile and performance. Marc graduated as a Computer Engineer in France before moving to Australia. Before joining Google, Marc worked as a Senior Consultant on Microsoft .NET and SQL Technologies., speakerldap: MarcRidey</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/c7q1z'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hlkd9</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 129</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Marcel Prasetya, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Marcel is a software engineer on Google Wave, focusing on the Google Wave Robot API. He joined Google in early 2006, and worked for the internal system team for three years before joining Google Wave. Marcel graduated from the University of Texas at Austin, with a bachelor's degree in Computer Science., speakerldap: MarcelPrasetya</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hlkd9'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hk5ss</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 130</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Marcelo Camelo, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Marcelo is a software engineer with Google Australia, where he works in the Maps API team, with a focus on latency and mobile. Previously, Marcelo worked developing massively multiplayer games and data visualization software. Marcelo holds a B.Eng. in Metallurgical Engineering and a Masters in Industrial Engineering., speakerldap: MarceloCamelo</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hk5ss'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hir8f</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 131</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Mark Halvorson, speakercompany: Atlassian Software, speakerabstract: Mark is the Chief Imagineer and OpenSocial Evangelist at Atlassian Software - the makers of JIRA and Confluence.  He has a long history working with portals and social enterprise software having worked in various capacities from software developer to technical marketer for Firepond, Plumtree, BEA and Oracle., speakerldap: MarkHalvorson</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hir8f'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hzm1f</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 132</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Mark Stahl, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Mark is a technical lead on the Google Data APIs clients team. After starting his career at Bell Labs, Mark was lured into a small networking startup just in time for the dot-com crash.  In 2005, he took his experiences to Google, where he started working on the API infrastructure. He spends his time trying to figure out how to make it easy to build great APIs., speakerldap: MarkStahl</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hzm1f'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hsl7a</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 133</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Mark Weitzel, speakercompany: International Business Machines (IBM), speakerabstract: Mark is a Senior Technical Staff Member in IBM Software Group’s Emerging Standards and Open Source team focusing on social networking and is also Secretary of the OpenSocial Foundation. Prior to this, Mark, as part of Tivoli’s Autonomic Computing team, was responsible for several open source systems management initiatives at Eclipse and Apache. , speakerldap: MarkWeitzel</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hsl7a'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/i2f69</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 134</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Matt Cutts, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Matt is the head of the webspam team at Google where he specializes in search engine optimization (SEO) issues. He is known in the webmaster and SEO community for applying Google's Quality Guidelines. Matt sometimes discusses search issues and offers advice on website visibility in Google on his personal blog at http://www.mattcutts.com/blog/ . You can also catch him on Twitter at http://twitter.com/mattcutts, speakerldap: MattCutts</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/i2f69'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/i10ls</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 135</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Matt Harding, speakerabstract: Matt travels around the world and films himself dancing badly in exotic places. That's basically his job. God bless the internet., speakerldap: MattHarding</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/i10ls'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hy7gy</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 136</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Matt Holleran, speakercompany: Emergence Capital Partners, speakerabstract: Matt is a Venture Partner at Emergence Capital Partners.  He is an expert in cloud application business models and cloud ecosystems.  Prior to joining the firm, Matt’s team started and built the AppExchange and Force.com partner ecosystem at salesforce.com.  He advises cloud platform companies and helps ISVs leverage them.  He is interested in freemium business application companies., speakerldap: MattHolleran</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hy7gy'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/i9g0a</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 137</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Matt Lowrie, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Matt is a Test Engineer who has worked at Google since 2006. He ensures product quality on several Geo products, including Building Maker and SketchUp., speakerldap: MattLowrie</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/i9g0a'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ic954</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 138</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Matt Mastracci, speakercompany: DotSpots, speakerabstract: Matt is a founder and CTO of DotSpots. He is currently leading the efforts to build better ways to allow users to attach images, videos and blog posts to the news in real-time using a platform based on Google Web Toolkit. Prior to DotSpots, he worked on building rich, scalable, browser-based applications for the energy sector and micropayments., speakerldap: MattMastracci</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ic954'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/iaukr</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 139</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Matt Pruden, speakercompany: Appirio, speakerabstract: Matt is a Technical Architect at Appirio who has helped transition over 200,000 users at 40 companies to Google Apps. His expertise is in enterprise use of the Google Apps platform. Prior to Appirio, Matt spent seven years in Intel IT, providing perspective into large scale technology transitions.  Matt's technical repertoire includes Python, Twisted, Ruby, Java, etc., speakerldap: MattPruden</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/iaukr'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hwswl</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 140</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Matt Shobe, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Matt is a staff user experience designer at Google whose work centers on services for publishers. Prior to Google, Matt was a co-founder of FeedBurner and led user experience design efforts there and on two prior startups with the same team. Matt is an avid distance runner, private pilot, and skier, though no such triathlon exists (yet)., speakerldap: MattShobe</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hwswl'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hvec4</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 141</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Matt Tucker, speakercompany: Jive Software, speakerabstract: Matt is the CTO and Co-Founder of Jive Software. He leads technology efforts such as Jive's adoption of cloud technologies and open standards. He's also an active member of the OpenSocial and XMPP communities., speakerldap: MattTucker</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/hvec4'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/htzrr</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 142</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Matthew Blain, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Matthew is a software engineer on the Google App Engine team working on tools. Prior to joining App Engine, he worked on Google Toolbar. Prior to Google, Matthew had stints as a software consultant and as a developer on Microsoft Internet Explorer and InfoPath., speakerldap: MatthewBlain</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/htzrr'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/i58b3</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 143</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Matthew Holden, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Matthew is a Product Manager for the Google Maps Data API, Google Earth vector layers, and global problem reporting on Google Maps.  He joined Google in 2008, and recently helped launch spatial + attribute search in the Maps Data API.  The Maps Data API provides scalable hosting and searching of geographic content in Google's cloud., speakerldap: MatthewHolden</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/i58b3'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/i3tqm</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 144</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Matthew Papakipos, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Matthew is an Engineering Director at Google, where he runs the Chrome OS and Chrome Graphics efforts. Prior to working at Google, he was the CTO of PeakStream and Architecture Director at NVIDIA. His interests include computer hardware and software, interactive computer graphics, and games. He has over forty awarded patents in processor design and software architecture. He received his BS in Mathematics and Computer Science from Brown University., speakerldap: MatthewPapakipos</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/i3tqm'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/im343</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 145</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Matthew Simmons, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Matthew is a developer working in Google Corporate Engineering. His work centers on developing and evaluating knowledge management systems. In his spare time he can be found hanging out with his wife and daughters or doing research at the University of Michigan in pursuit of his Ph.D. in Information., speakerldap: MatthewSimmons</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/im343'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ikojm</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 146</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Matthew Tonkin, speakercompany: Memeo Inc, speakerabstract: Matt is the Mac Applications Architect at Memeo and technical lead for Memeo Connect, a client for syncing files between the desktop and Google Docs by utilizing the new API's for storing any file type. Memeo is extending Connect and Google Docs beyond the desktop to mobile platforms including Android and iPad. Matt originates from Australia and is currently living and working in Orange County, CA., speakerldap: MatthewTonkin</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ikojm'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/i81fx</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 147</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Max Lin, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Max is a software engineer with Google Research in New York City office.  Prior to Google, he published research work in video content analysis, sentiment analysis, machine learning, and cross-lingual information retrieval.  He has a PhD in Computer Science from Carnegie Mellon University., speakerldap: MaxLin</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/i81fx'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/i6mvg</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 148</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Max Ross, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Max is a test-driven Software Engineer on the App Engine team where he works on the datastore and the Java runtime.  He is also the founder of the Hibernate Shards project.  Prior to joining Google he was a software engineer in the supply chain management and travel technology industries.  He holds a BA in American Studies and Computer Science from Williams College., speakerldap: MaxRoss</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/i6mvg'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/idnpl</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 149</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Michael Fink, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Michael joined Google Research in 2005, where he started the “mass personalization” effort. Since then, Michael Fink initiated several media-based projects, including YouTube's Interactive Video Annotations, which enables embedding of hyperlinks onto objects in YouTube videos. When he's not at work, you'll probably find him scuba diving in the Red Sea., speakerldap: MichaelFink</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/idnpl'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ixbp7</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 150</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Michael Goderbauer , speakercompany: Hasso Plattner Institute, speakerabstract: Michael is a student of Germany's #1 ranked software engineering school, the Hasso Plattner Institute in Potsdam. Right now he is in his sixth semester and he will finish his bachelor’s degree this summer. About a year ago, he and six fellow students started the processWave.org project to create a collaborative diagram editor for Google Wave. , speakerldap: MichaelGoderbauer </content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ixbp7'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/iyq9k</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 151</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Michael Morrissey, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Michael runs the Android services team at Google, which includes Market, sync, and device management. Prior to Android, he built the Sidekick/Hiptop service platform at Danger and worked on mobile products at Microsoft., speakerldap: MichaelMorrissey</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/iyq9k'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/j04u1</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 152</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Michael Schwartz, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Mike is a software engineer in Google's Seattle office. Before Google he worked at a number of start-up companies, and was an Associate Professor of Computer Science at the University of Colorado - Boulder., speakerldap: MichaelSchwartz</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/j04u1'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/iqav2</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 153</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Michael Van Riper, speakercompany: Krillion, Inc., speakerabstract: Van is Chief Web Technologist at Krillion and a Java Champion. He leads the largest Java and Google Technology User Groups in Silicon Valley. Van is also a serial community organizer., speakerldap: MichaelVanRiper</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/iqav2'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/irpfj</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 154</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Mihai Ionescu, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Since starting at Google in 2003, Mihai has worked on Google Desktop, O3D and Chrome.  Lately, he is focusing on HTML5 and particularly on Chrome as a developer platform for rich web applications. Prior to Google, Mihai worked at Microsoft on Internet Explorer, Java VM, and .NET. He holds an MBA from the Berkeley Haas School of Business and an MS in Computer Science from UC Santa Barbara., speakerldap: MihaiIonescu</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/irpfj'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/it3zw</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 155</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Mike Aizatsky, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Mike is a software engineer working on Google App Engine. He worked on Google Code Search prior to joining the App Engine team. Before joining, Google he was a Project Manager at JetBrains working on developer tools.
, speakerldap: MikeAizatsky</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/it3zw'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/iuikd</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 156</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Mike O'Brien, speakercompany: Appirio, speakerabstract: Mike manages Appirio's growing enterprise Google business. He has responsibility for sales and delivery of Appirio's Google customers with a focus on large global enterprise implementations. He brings over 15 years of experience leading large enterprise software deployments that involve complex business requirements for global businesses., speakerldap: MikeOBrien</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/iuikd'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/j75o2</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 157</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Ming Yong, speakercompany: Voiceroute Pte Ltd (Socialwok)
, speakerabstract: Ming is Founder and CEO of Socialwok (http://socialwok.com), one of the most popular business social productivity service on the web for group collaboration and enterprise microblogging. Ming previously founded Druid, a popular open source project on Unified Communications for small medium businesses.He is also one of the committee member of the Singapore Google Technology User group (SG-GTUG)., speakerldap: MingYong</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/j75o2'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/j8k8j</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 158</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Moishe Lettvin, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Moishe is a software engineer working in Google's Kirkland and Seattle offices. In his time at Google, he's worked on many aspects of Google Talk and is currently working on Google App Engine., speakerldap: MoisheLettvin</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/j8k8j'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/j9ysw</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 159</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Nathan Naze, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Nathan is a software engineer at Google. He works on user interface for Google Books, one of many projects using  Closure Library.  Open sourcing Closure Library was his 20% project with Daniel Nadasi. He joined Google in 2005 after graduating from the University of Wisconsin with majors in computer science, political science, and economics. He lives in San Francisco., speakerldap: NathanNaze</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/j9ysw'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jbddd</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 160</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Nick Johnson, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Nick is a Developer Programs Engineer on the App Engine team. He spends his days helping people write code for App Engine. His nights are spent writing code about App Engine and then blogging about it., speakerldap: NickJohnson</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jbddd'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/j1jee</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 161</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Nick Mihailovski, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Nick has been working on Google Analytics for over 5 years and is currently working as a developer programs engineer to help developers create better tools, integrations and automation with Google Analytics and 3rd party systems., speakerldap: NickMihailovski</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/j1jee'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/j2xyv</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 162</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Pamela Fox, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Pamela has worked in the Developer Relations group at Google for the last 3 years. She spent 3 years supporting the Maps API community, and now is focusing her time on helping the blossoming Wave APIs community. In her free time, she likes to play around with any one of Google's 60+ APIs. , speakerldap: PamelaFox</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/j2xyv'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/j4cj8</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 163</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Paul Graham, speakercompany: Y Combinator, speakerabstract: Paul is a partner at Y Combinator and the author of On Lisp (1993), ANSI Common Lisp (1995), and Hackers &amp; Painters (2004). In 1995, he and Robert Morris started Viaweb, the first ASP, which in 1998 became Yahoo! Store. In 2002 he discovered a simple spam filtering algorithm that inspired the current generation of filters. He has an AB from Cornell and a PhD in Computer Science from Harvard., speakerldap: PaulGraham</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/j4cj8'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/j5r3p</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 164</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Pavel Feldman, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Pavel is a software engineer working on Google Chrome Developer Tools and WebKit's Inspector. He worked on Google Calendar prior to joining the Chrome team. Before joining Google, he was Chief Scientist at Borland working on modeling tools., speakerldap: PavelFeldman</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/j5r3p'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jie7e</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 165</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Peter Birch, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Peter joined Google in 2006 as Product Manager for Google Earth, Google's 3D earth visualization tool that combines the power of Google Search with satellite imagery, maps, terrain and 3D buildings. He is responsible for the direction, growth, and success of the Google Earth product family including Google Earth Free, Pro, and Enterprise, the Google Earth API and browser plug-in, and Google Earth for the iPhone., speakerldap: PeterBirch</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jie7e'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jjsrv</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 166</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Phil Liao, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Phil is a Software Engineer on the Google Wave team.  Prior to joining Google, he built software in areas of education, supply chain execution, brain imaging and finance.  Phil holds computer science degrees from MIT and Berkeley., speakerldap: PhilLiao</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jjsrv'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jl7c8</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 167</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Ray Cromwell, speakercompany: Timefire, speakerabstract: Ray is CTO and co-founder of Timefire where he dreams of flying over vast historical data landscapes. These days, he works on visualization software using Google Web Toolkit. Prior to Timefire, he led Oracle's efforts to build mobile XForms implementations and draft IETF standards for push email., speakerldap: RayCromwell</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jl7c8'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jmlwp</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 168</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Ray Ryan, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Ray is part of the Google Web Toolkit team, and has been goading people into writing software the way he thinks they should since the 1980s. He has worked at Lighthouse Design, Sun, AOL, and has spent the last four years at Google. Recently he had a strong hand in shaping the architecture of the new GWT-based user interface for AdWords., speakerldap: RayRyan</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jmlwp'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jcrxq</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 169</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Reto Meier, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Reto is a Developer Advocate for Android at Google and is the author of 'Professional Android 2 Application Development'. As the EMEA Android Advocate he works closely with Android developers, helping them make the most of the platform to bring rich, compelling apps to the Android Market. Before Google he worked in various industries, including offshore oil and gas while in Australia and the London finance market. , speakerldap: RetoMeier</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jcrxq'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/je6i7</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 170</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Richard Fulcher, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Richard Fulcher is a senior user interface designer on the Android team, focused on communication applications. Prior to joining Google, he designed consumer experiences for TiVo, Sirius, Dell and AOL. He freely admits to playing lots of board games., speakerldap: RichardFulcher</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/je6i7'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jfl2k</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 171</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Richard Rabbat, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Richard is a product manager at Google. He recently released Page Speed, a Firefox add-on that analyzes web pages and gives suggestions on how to improve them in addition to doing some of the optimizations itself. Richard manages the Google program to make the web faster and works on projects that power Google’s infrastructure including latency measurements for Google apps., speakerldap: RichardRabbat</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jfl2k'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jgzn1</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 172</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Rob Pike, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Rob works on distributed systems, programming languages, and software development tools. Before Google, Rob was at Bell Labs Research. He was an architect of the Plan 9 and Inferno operating systems and is the co-author with Brian Kernighan of The Unix Programming Environment and The Practice of Programming., speakerldap: RobPike</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jgzn1'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jtmqq</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 173</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Romain Guy, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Romain is a software engineer at Google. After spending years having fun with large UIs on the desktop and talking about them at conferences, in blogs, magazines and books, Romain decided to go for the small screen and joined the Android project, an Open Source operating system for mobile phones. He’s now trying to make mobile phone UIs as fun and exciting as desktop ones., speakerldap: RomainGuy</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jtmqq'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jv1b7</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 174</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Rus Heywood, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Rus is the lead engineer for the Google PowerMeter project, which is part of Google.org. Rus came to Google through Jotspot, a collaboration tool company that Google acquired in 2006., speakerldap: RusHeywood</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jv1b7'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jwfvk</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 175</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Russ Cox, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Russ is a software engineer working on the Go team.  Before working on Go, Russ led the creation of Code Search, Google's only regular expression-based search engine., speakerldap: RussCox</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jwfvk'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jxug1</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 176</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Ryan Boyd, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Ryan is a developer advocate at Google focused on enabling developers to extend Google Apps and build businesses on top of Google technology.  He previously worked on OpenSocial, Google Friend Connect and Google's AtomPub APIs.  Prior to joining Google, Ryan worked in higher education as a web architect for RIT's web hosting environment and as web app developer., speakerldap: RyanBoyd</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jxug1'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jo0h2</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 177</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Ryan Sarver, speakercompany: Twitter, speakerabstract: Ryan is currently the Director of Platform at Twitter where he works with developers building myriad of experiences on top of 140 characters. Previously he was the Director of Consumer Products at Skyhook Wireless where he led product initiatives that leveraged the WPS platform in consumer applications and experiences. Ryan was also one of the founding members of the W3C Geolocation API Working Group., speakerldap: RyanSarver</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jo0h2'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jpf1j</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 178</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Sami Shalabi, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Sami is a Technical Lead Manager at Google. He is leading the engineering teams responsible for Google Friend Connect and Google Buzz APIs. Prior to Google, Sami was a co-founder of Zingku (acquired by Google), and YallaStartup. Sami holds a Bachelor’s and Master’s degrees from MIT., speakerldap: SamiShalabi</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jpf1j'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jqtlw</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 179</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Scott McMullan, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Scott is a Senior Enterprise Program Manager focused on helping 3rd parties grow their business with Google Apps.  A startup guy at heart, Scott joined Google from JotSpot, where he ran developer programs, and previously founded Inovie Software, maker of early Internet collaboration service TeamCenter.  Scott holds bachelor's and master's degrees in computer science from UCSD and was a PhD student at the university's Computer Systems Lab., speakerldap: ScottMcMullan</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/jqtlw'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/js86d</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 180</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Sean Lynch, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Sean is a Product Manager for Google App Engine. Since joining Google in 2008, Sean worked on Google core infrastructure before moving to the App Engine team in 2009. Sean holds a B.S. in Computer Science from the University of Waterloo., speakerldap: SeanLynch</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/js86d'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/f52je</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 181</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Seth Covitz, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Seth is a software engineer on Google Wave. He enjoys innovating and pushing the boundaries of the web each and every day. Prior to Google, he held positions as CTO, VP of Development, and Software Architect for companies ranging from startups to the Fortune 50. Seth holds a B.S. degree in Math and Computer Science from Carnegie Mellon University. , speakerldap: SethCovitz</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/f52je'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/f6h3v</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 182</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Shih-chia Cheng, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Shih-Chia is a software engineer of JAPAC iGoogle team. Prior to iGoogle, he worked on Google Maps. Shih-Chia has a Masters degree from Stanford University. His interests include social dance, games, and Chinese chess., speakerldap: Shih-chiaCheng</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/f6h3v'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/f9a8p</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 183</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Siddartha Naidu, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Siddartha has been crunching large data sets at Google since 2005 for a variety of products and as a physics grad student before that. He has worked with or on almost every data processing framework at Google and is still looking for ways to make his job easier., speakerldap: SiddarthaNaidu</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/f9a8p'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ezg9q</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 184</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Srikanth Rajagopalan, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Srikanth is a Product Manager for Infrastructure/Advanced Projects at Google. He has tackled responsibilities ranging from rolling out Google PowerMeter to making Google’s Cloud Computing Infrastructure more efficient and scaling Google Book Search towards scanning the world's offline content., speakerldap: SrikanthRajagopalan</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/ezg9q'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/f0uu7</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 185</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Stefan  Haustein, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Stefan is a software engineer at Google in London and is responsible for the WebOS port of Google Maps. Prior to joining Google, he worked as an engineering director at Interact!v GmbH in Cologne. Stefan has a PhD in Computer Science from the University of Dortmund. , speakerldap: Stefan Haustein</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/f0uu7'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/f29ek</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 186</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Stephanie Hannon, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Stephanie, the lead product manager for Google Wave, is based in Google's Sydney office. Prior to Sydney she worked in Google's Zurich office, leading the product team for Google Maps for Europe, Middle East and Africa, and before this she was product manager for Gmail in at Google in Mountain View, CA. Stephanie holds a B.S. Computer Systems Engineering and M.S.E.E. from Stanford University and an M.B.A. from Harvard Business School.  , speakerldap: StephanieHannon</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/f29ek'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/f3nz1</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 187</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Steve Bazyl, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Steve is a Developer Advocate at Google focused on developers integrating with Google Apps.  Prior to joining Google, Steve was an architect at IGT and RSA Security where he worked on building scalable and secure web based systems. , speakerldap: Steve Bazyl</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/f3nz1'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/fgb2q</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 188</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Susannah Raub, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Susannah is the tech lead for the Maps API v3 team in Sydney, focused on latency and mobile. Prior to moving to Australia, she worked on Local Search in New York and Google Desktop in Mountain View. She earned her bachelors in Mathematics-Computer Science at Brown University., speakerldap: SusannahRaub</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/fgb2q'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/fhpn7</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 189</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Thatcher Ulrich, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Thatcher is a founding member of the Google Earth API and Browser Plugin team.  Prior to joining Google he worked on games and graphics at Oddworld Inhabitants and a variety of startups., speakerldap: ThatcherUlrich</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/fhpn7'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/fj47k</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 190</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Thor Mitchell, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Thor is a Product Manager for the Google Maps Developer Platform, based in Sydney, Australia. Although originally from the U.K., he does not have a strong preference between Marmite and Vegemite, despising both equally., speakerldap: ThorMitchell</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/fj47k'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/fkis1</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 191</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Timothy Jordan, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Timothy is a Developer Advocate at Google working on the social web. He also teaches New Media at the Academy of Art University and announces Roller Derby. As an engineer he enjoys solving problems for the benefit of fellow humans. As an artist he enjoys the search for truth and beauty., speakerldap: TimothyJordan</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/fkis1'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/faot2</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 192</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Toby Reyelts, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Toby is a progenitor of App Engine for Java and a member of the Google Web Toolkit team. Toby's current areas of interest are performance (45.32us is too slow) and improving dynalangs on the JVM and App Engine for Java., speakerldap: TobyReyelts</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/faot2'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/fc3dj</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 193</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Todd Jackson, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Todd is a product manager on Gmail and the product lead for Google Buzz. He has worked at Google since 2004. Todd holds an MS and BS in Computer Science from Stanford University., speakerldap: ToddJackson</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/fc3dj'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/fdhxw</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 194</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Tom Manshreck, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Tom is a senior technical writer and has worked on the Maps API since 2007, where he writes and maintains the Maps API documentation set. Prior to Google, Tom was a managing editor for computer science at Prentice Hall/Pearson. He enjoys driving around the States with his cocker spaniel, Faulkner., speakerldap: TomManshreck</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/fdhxw'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/fewid</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 195</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Vic Gundotra, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Vic joined Google in 2007 as VP of Engineering, responsible for mobile applications and developer evangelism. Vic spent 15 years at Microsoft, working on products and operating systems including Windows 3.0, NT, Windows XP, and Vista. He was recognized by MIT as a "Young Innovator under 35" for his work in sparking Microsoft's change from Win32 to the .NET programming model. Vic holds two patents in the area of distributed computing and identity-based access to cloud resources., speakerldap: VicGundotra</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/fewid'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/frjm2</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 196</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Vijay Bangaru, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Vijay is a product manager on the Google Docs team. Previously at Google, he ran core infrastructure teams for storage, object transport, indexing and crawling. Prior to Google, he worked at Microsoft where he drove product strategy and led development teams for SQL Server, WinFS and the .NET Framework. Vijay holds bachelor's degrees in computer engineering and electrical engineering from Washington University of St. Louis, where he graduated summa cum laude., speakerldap: VijayBangaru</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/frjm2'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/fsy6j</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 197</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Virgil Dobjanschi, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Virgil is an Android application developer at Google. He focuses on Social applications development. Prior to Android, Virgil was the President of Multiple Facets and Chief Architect at AudioTalk Networks and Essentel., speakerldap: VirgilDobjanschi</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/fsy6j'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/fucqw</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 198</title><content type='text'>speakertitle: Zach Maier, speakercompany: Google, speakerabstract: Zach is the product manager for the Google Data Protocol, and his team is responsible for building the infrastructure behind most of Google's APIs. Rumor has it that Zach invented the hashtag #myjobisawesome after he started working on developer products at Google.  Before APIs, Zach attended Kansas State University where he graduated summa cum laude with a degree in computer engineering and a specialty in machine intelligence., speakerldap: ZachMaier</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od4/public/basic/fucqw'/></entry></feed>