<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><feed xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom' xmlns:openSearch='http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/' xmlns:gsx='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006/extended'><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>sandbox</title><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/pub?key=t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw'/><link rel='http://schemas.google.com/g/2005#feed' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic'/><author><name>christine.lee</name><email>christine.lee@gmail.com</email></author><openSearch:totalResults>183</openSearch:totalResults><openSearch:startIndex>1</openSearch:startIndex><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/cpzh4</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 2</title><content type='text'>companyname: 12wiki, companylocation: Breda, Noord-Brabant, The Netherlands, companydesc: 12wiki is a webdevelopment company specialised in open-source software., companyurl: www.12wiki.eu, productdesc: Currently we are working on MediawikiWave, which will allow you to edit Mediawiki articles (i.e. Wikipedia) in a Wave Enviroment, solving a lot of the issues with the current editor and making contributing content a pain-free experience., companylogo: 12wiki.png, companypod: Wave, companytags: Wave, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/cpzh4'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/cre1l</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 3</title><content type='text'>companyname: 280 North, Inc., companylocation: San Francisco, California, companydesc: Creators of 280 Slides, a web based presentation editor; the Cappuccino Web Framework, for building desktop-class applications that run in any browser; and Atlas, a powerful visual editor for building applications with Cappuccino., companyurl: www.280north.com, productdesc: 280 Slides relies on the Google AJAX APIs to provide a rich media experience to users. Without leaving the site, users can integrate relevant pictures and videos from the web in just a few clicks., companylogo: 280north.png, companypod: Google APIs, companytags: Google APIs, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/cre1l'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/b8lvi</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 4</title><content type='text'>companyname: 6rounds, companylocation: Tel Aviv, Israel, companydesc: 6rounds is a social entertainment video chat platform. The platform combines interactive video chats, co-browsing activities and real-time games to create a fun, playful and thrilling place for people of all ages., companyurl: www.6rounds.com, productdesc: 6rounds created a Google Wave extension which enables Wave users to enjoy instant one-on-one video chats and collaborate together in real-time using webcams, various rich activities and different interactive games., companylogo: 6rounds.png, companypod: Wave, companytags: Wave, adddate: 4/22/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/b8lvi'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/chk2m</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 5</title><content type='text'>companyname: Adobe Systems Incorporated, companylocation: San Jose, California, companydesc: Adobe revolutionizes how the world engages with ideas and information - anytime, anywhere and through any medium., companyurl: www.adobe.com, companylogo: adobe.png, companypod: Chrome, companytags: Chrome, adddate: 5/7/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/chk2m'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ciyn3</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 6</title><content type='text'>companyname: Aloqa, companylocation: Palo Alto, California, companydesc:  Aloqa is a mobile service that proactively notifies you of interesting places, events, music, movies and other activities near you. Instead of having to search, you can just look at your phone and see your favorite hotspots, activities, events of interest, and recommended bargains close by., companyurl: www.aloqa.com, productdesc: We use several Google products: the Android SDK for building the Android client, the Google Static Maps API for maps on WinMo and J2ME phones, the Google Visualization API for our internal analytics, Google Local Search for our Pull-based Search Channel, Google AdSense for Mobile, and Google Web Toolkit for some of our websites., companylogo: aloqa.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, Geo, Google APIs, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ciyn3'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ckd7g</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 7</title><content type='text'>companyname: Amazon, companylocation: Seattle, Washington, companydesc: Amazon.com, Inc., seeks to be Earth's most customer-centric company, where customers can find and discover anything they might want to buy online, and endeavors to offer its customers the lowest possible prices., companyurl: www.amazon.com, companylogo: amazon.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ckd7g'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/clrrx</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 8</title><content type='text'>companyname: Appirio, companylocation: San Mateo, California, companydesc: Appirio is a cloud solution provider, delivering both products and professional services that help enterprises accelerate their adoption of cloud computing., companyurl: www.appirio.com, productdesc: Appirio uses Google App Engine, GWT, GData, OpenID/oAuth and OpenSocial Gadgets to build custom productivity extensions to Google Apps which help a wide range of customers increase productivity and enrich their experience with existing SaaS investments. For example, our popular "connector" products have helped almost 5,000 customers worldwide synchronize their contacts and calendar events between Salesforce CRM and Google Apps. , companylogo: appirio.png, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, App Engine, GWT, Google APIs, Social Web, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/clrrx'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/cztg3</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 9</title><content type='text'>companyname: Atlassian, companylocation: San Francisco, California, companydesc: Atlassian is an Australian software company specialising in collaboration and development tools to help technical teams build better software. Atlassian's flagship products include JIRA, the popular issue tracker, Confluence, the enterprise wiki, and JIRA Studio, a hosted development suite., companyurl: www.atlassian.com, productdesc: Atlassian makes use of many different Google products and technologies in its products. JIRA and Confluence are both OpenSocial containers and publishers, and Atlassian uses OpenSocial gadgets across its product portfolio to integrate and share information between products. JIRA Studio, Atlassian's hosted development suite, integrates with Google Apps, and several Atlassian products use Google Web Toolkit., companylogo: atlassian.png, companypod: Social Web, companytags: Social Web, GWT, Enterprise, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/cztg3'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/cssly</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 10</title><content type='text'>companyname: Aviary, companylocation: New York, New York, companydesc: Aviary has created a suite of powerful, free web apps for designers and multimedia creators. Whether you are trying to edit a screen capture of your website, remix a music track or create a logo for your new business, Aviary has the right tool for you., companyurl: www.aviary.com, productdesc: Aviary has developed for many of Google's APIs including: the Android SDK for our Android app, integration with OpenID and OAuth to let people login to Aviary using their Google account, Picasa's API to import people's photos, Google's Web Toolkit to build our website and a plugin for Google Chrome. We also use Google Apps for email, documents and collaboration and Google Analytics for traffic monitoring., companylogo: aviary.png, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, Android, Google APIs, Social Web, GWT, Chrome, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/cssly'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/cu76f</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 11</title><content type='text'>companyname: BeeBole, companylocation: Wallonia, Belgium, companydesc: BeeBole builds web apps for small and medium businesses. The current core features are: contact manager, timesheet and reporting, but the main objective is to let anyone add modules, either from the community or their own. BeeBole is also the author of the popular open source JavaScript templates engine PURE., companyurl: www.beebole.com, productdesc: Google APIs fit very well with our integration design. BeeBole is using: Google Chart Tools, Google Maps, Google Calendar, Google Docs, Google Login Authentication., companylogo: beebole.png, companypod: Google APIs, companytags: Google APIs, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/cu76f'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ba0fz</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 12</title><content type='text'>companyname: Big Ladder, companylocation: Denver, Colorado, companydesc: Big Ladder is a software and consulting company offering services at the intersection of programming, engineering, and energy simulation.  We specialize in developing open source tools for modeling energy usage in the built environment., companyurl: www.bigladdersoftware.com, productdesc: Big Ladder uses the Google SketchUp API to couple building energy simulation with SketchUp's intuitive 3-D drawing tools., companylogo: bigladder.png, companypod: Geo, companytags: Geo, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ba0fz'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/cvlqs</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 13</title><content type='text'>companyname: bit.ly, companylocation: New York, New York, companydesc: bit.ly shortens, shares, and tracks the social propagation of links on the Internet., companyurl: www.bit.ly, productdesc: We make use of Google code, perftools, Closure, Google Apps, the Google Safebrowsing, and other Google APIs in various roles for development and management of our product., companylogo: bitly.png, companypod: Chrome, companytags: Chrome, Enterprise, Google APIs, adddate: 4/22/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/cvlqs'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/cx0b9</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 14</title><content type='text'>companyname: Black Tonic, companylocation: Portland, Oregon, companydesc: Present. Demo. Share. Whatever you do, be on the same page at the same time with Black Tonic - the only web based tool providing real-time presentation delivery and control without using plugins or flash. Changes can be made on the fly, delivery is non-linear, and content can be added while the conversation is taking place., companyurl: www.blacktonic.com, productdesc: Black Tonic uses Google Web Toolkit (GWT) to serve the client side interface of our web-page html synchronization solution, FLOW.  , companylogo: blacktonic.png, companypod: GWT, companytags: GWT, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/cx0b9'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/d9ney</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 15</title><content type='text'>companyname: Box.net, companylocation: Palo Alto, California, companydesc: Box.net is a Cloud Content Management provider that makes it simple for businesses to access, manage, and share all of their content online. , companyurl: www.box.net, productdesc: Box.net’s Cloud Content Management system adds workflow and content-based administrative oversight to Google Apps. This integration provides access to Gmail, Google Calendar, Google Sites, and Google Docs within Box.net, and likewise makes Box.net's service accessible through Google’s universal navigation links and Google Gadgets., companylogo: boxnet.png, companypod: Google APIs, companytags: Google APIs, Enterprise, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/d9ney'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/db1zf</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 16</title><content type='text'>companyname: BTBuckets, companylocation: São Paulo, SP, Brazil, companydesc: BTBuckets is a free profiling and behavioral targeting tool that aims to provide a complete solution for websites to deliver more relevant content, products and advertising to its users in an easy and low cost way., companyurl: www.btbuckets.com, productdesc: We use App Engine as our segmentation and targeting engine., companylogo: btbuckets.png, companypod: App Engine, companytags: App Engine, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/db1zf'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/dcgjs</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 17</title><content type='text'>companyname: Bump, companylocation: Mountain View, California, companydesc: Bump Technologies is building a mobile technology platform and apps to allow phones to connect and interact by simply bumping them together. Share photos, contacts, and even apps with just a bump of your phones., companyurl: www.bu.mp
, productdesc: Android features used: Location services, Accelerometer, and Custom Intent to share via Bump., companylogo: bump.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/dcgjs'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ddv49</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 18</title><content type='text'>companyname: BusyCal, companylocation: Seattle, Washington, companydesc: BusyCal is a desktop calendar for Mac OS X that provides seamless calendar sharing and enhanced productivity tools for workgroups and individuals. BusyCal syncs with Google Calendar offering online access to your calendar on any platform and the ability to share calendars with other Google Calendar users., companyurl: www.busycal.com, productdesc: BusyCal uses the Google Calendar Data API for performing two-way synchronization with Google Calendar., companylogo: busycal.png, companypod: Google APIs, companytags: Google APIs, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ddv49'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/d415a</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 19</title><content type='text'>companyname: Caseish, companylocation: Copenhagen, Denmark, companydesc: Caseish helps organize your Waves to be more organized and helps you control the flow of every case that you’re managing. Caseish also collects metrics on your processes and visualizes your pain points., companyurl: www.caseish.com, productdesc: We are using Google Wave Robots and API to integrate with Wave, AppEngine to control the robot and Google Visualization API to display graphs., companylogo: caseish.png, companypod: Wave, companytags: Wave, Google APIs, App Engine, adddate: 4/25/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/d415a'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/d5fpr</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 20</title><content type='text'>companyname: CELLULAR GmbH, companylocation: Hamburg, Germany, companydesc: CELLULAR is a leading international, full-service agencies for mobile solutions and services. We support customers with conceptualization and programming of mobile portals and applications for cell phones, smart phones and other web compatible devices. We develop solutions for market-leading mobile operators, brands, agencies and mass media., companyurl: www.cellular.de, productdesc: Android features used: Animations, lists, customized ListViews, customized toggle-buttons, customized tabs, customized video player, customized menus, exception reporting, LayoutInflater, SaxParser, ContentProvider, SQLite, and JSON., companylogo: cellular.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/d5fpr'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/d6ua4</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 21</title><content type='text'>companyname: Chromed Bird, companylocation: Fortaleza, CE, Brazil, companydesc: I came from a web and mobile applications background and started to dive into Chrome extensions since early dev channel releases. Right now I'm working on maintaining and expanding Chromed Bird extension and trying to contribute further with Chromium community., companyurl: www.chromedbird.com, productdesc: Chromed Bird uses HTML5 and Chromium extensions API to build a powerful yet simple Twitter client., companylogo: chromedbird.png, companypod: Chrome, companytags: Chrome, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/d6ua4'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/d88ul</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 22</title><content type='text'>companyname: Cisco, companylocation: San Jose, California, companydesc: Cisco Systems, Inc. designs, manufactures, and sells Internet Protocol (IP)-based networking solutions, including Routers, Switches, IP Communications Equipment, Unified I/O Compute Systems and network management software and other products to the communications and IT industry worldwide. The company also offers optical networking products, cable access, and service provider VoIP services., companyurl: www.cisco.com, productdesc: Cisco built its north bound API in OpenSocial complaint way. It uses Google Map API and service for people location, Google Guice for backend dependency injection., and Android SDK for building the Android client (in process)., companylogo: cisco.png, companypod: Social Web, companytags: Social Web, Geo, Android, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/d88ul'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/dkvya</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 23</title><content type='text'>companyname: Civio, companylocation: Palo Alto, California, companydesc: Civio provides the platform to orchestrate interactions that target and engage people in meaningful ways. Customers use Civio to engage people in actions online and offline and receive the benefit of increased participation, affinity and contribution levels.  , companyurl: www.civio.com, productdesc: We've built our platform on top of Google App Engine for our hosting and web-based infrastructure. We’re also using Google Maps and the Geocoding Service to provide geographical overlays to our users., companylogo: civio.png, companypod: App Engine, companytags: App Engine, Geo, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/dkvya'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/dmair</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 24</title><content type='text'>companyname: Clicker, companylocation: Los Angeles, California, companydesc: Clicker is the complete programming guide for the new era of Internet television. Clicker catalogues all TV shows, movies and Web originals available on the Web in one place, delivering a seamless, organized experience so you can easily discover what’s available, where you can watch it, and get suggestions for other content you might find worth watching. , companyurl: www.clicker.com, productdesc: We use Chrome for HTML5 support and Javascript/UI debugging; the YouTube API to programmatically control YouTube embeds; Page speed to analyze our UI speed; and the Notifications API to serve up notifications when new shows are online., companylogo: clicker.png, companypod: Chrome, companytags: Chrome, Google APIs, adddate: 4/25/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/dmair'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/dnp34</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 25</title><content type='text'>companyname: Cloud Sherpas, companylocation: Atlanta, Georgia, companydesc: Cloud Sherpas develops software and provides professional services to help enterprises leverage Google Apps and adopt cloud computing.  As one of the early Google Apps partners, Cloud Sherpas has migrated tens of thousands of users to Google Apps and developed SherpaTools, an valuable toolset that enhances the functionality and ease-of-use of Google Apps for both IT administrators and end users., companyurl: www.cloudsherpas.com, productdesc: SherpaTools for Google Apps is built entirely on Google App Engine and makes heavy use of Google Apps APIs and Google Web Toolkit.  SherpaTools also relies on reusable open standards such as OpenID and OAuth and leverages Google Apps as its OpenID identity provider., companylogo: cloudsherpas.png, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, App Engine, Google APIs, GWT, Social Web, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/dnp34'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/dp3nl</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 26</title><content type='text'>companyname: Columbus Internet GmbH, companylocation: Berlin, Germany, companydesc: Columbus Internet provides two acclaimed gadgets for Google Wave: Travel WithMe and Hostel WithMe. Travel WithMe allows groups of people to plan trips together in real time, presenting content from Lonely Planet and hotel information from Expedia in a map and calendar-based GUI, while Hostel WithMe lets groups of users choose and book the perfect budget accomodation using a simple but powerful GUI., companyurl: www.rucksack.com, productdesc: The WithMe gadget family harnesses the collaborative power of Google Wave to allow users to work and play together and make informed collective decisions. Travel WithMe makes innovative use of Google Maps, Street View and Google Local and allows the planned trip to be exported to Google Calendar., companylogo: columbusinternet.png, companypod: Wave, companytags: Wave, Geo, adddate: 4/25/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/dp3nl'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/df9om</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 27</title><content type='text'>companyname: Com2Us, companylocation: Seoul, South Korea, companydesc: Com2uS is a fun and creative mobile game company with various award-winning games in Korea and abroad. Founded in 1998, Com2us continues to bring innovative gameplay beyond mobile to multi-platform as a worldwide leader in mobile gaming with overseas offices in US, Japan and China., companyurl: www.com2us.com, productdesc: Android features used: multi-touch, gyro sensor, vibration, network connectivity using 3G or WiFi, and Developed by NDK(with C and C++ game code)., companylogo: com2us.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/df9om'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/dgo93</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 28</title><content type='text'>companyname: ConnectWise, companylocation: Tampa, Florida, companydesc: ConnectWise is a leading web-based professional service automation software designed exclusively for IT solutions providers by an IT solution provider. More than 37,000 IT professionals rely on us to more efficiently integrate key business operations, lower costs, increase revenue and improve customer satisfaction., companyurl: www.connectwise.com, productdesc: We’re using Google Web Toolkit to help build our community platform and working to embed Google Apps into our management software., companylogo: connectwise.png, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, GWT, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/dgo93'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/di2tg</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 29</title><content type='text'>companyname: Cordys, companylocation: Palo Alto, California, companydesc: Cordys is a global provider of software for business process innovation and offers Cordys Process Factory, a simple, effective mechanism for anyone in the world to create and deploy Mashup Applications (MashApps®). These web-based, process-centric applications are ideal for SME’s and departmental deployments to create applications and business processes on the fly, at low cost and without IT involvement., companyurl: www.cordys.com, productdesc: Cordys Process Factory has out-of-the box integration with Google Apps allowing users of Google Apps to easily enrich their offering., companylogo: cordys.jpg, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/di2tg'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/djhdx</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 30</title><content type='text'>companyname: Coupons.com, companylocation: Mountain View, California, companydesc: Coupons.com Inc. is a leader in digital coupons, including mobile, online printable, and save-to-loyalty card promotions., companyurl: www.coupons.com, productdesc: Grocery iQ for Android makes full use of the Android platform including native UI widgets, Voice Recognition to add new items to your list, dynamically resizing and re-scaling the UI and images based on hardware model, etc. In addition, Grocery iQ supports a unique intent that allows other applications to easily add items to a user's grocery list., companylogo: coupons.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/djhdx'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/dw4je</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 31</title><content type='text'>companyname: CS Odessa, companylocation: Odessa, Ukraine, companydesc: Founded in 1993, CS Odessa supplies productivity tools and graphics technologies to professional and corporate users. With headquarters in Odessa, Ukraine and an office in California, USA, CS Odessa sells products in over 120 countries., companyurl: www.csodessa.com, productdesc: We are building a mind mapping gadget for Google Wave using Google Wave's Extensions API and OpenSocial Gadgets API together to help people view real time the structure of their collaboration., companylogo: csodessa.png, companypod: Wave, companytags: Wave, Social Web, adddate: 4/22/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/dw4je'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/dxj3v</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 32</title><content type='text'>companyname: DataViz, companylocation: Milford, Connecticut, companydesc: DataViz is an industry leader in developing and marketing Office compatibility solutions across a variety of platforms including Android, BlackBerry, Java®, Linux, Palm OS®, Symbian OS™, Windows Mobile®, Windows® and Macintosh®., companyurl: www.dataviz.com, productdesc: Key Android-related features include: Open files and attachments via intents; run in the background; multi-touch and pinch-to-zoom; rotate page; and live folders., companylogo: dataviz.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/dxj3v'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/e0c8p</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 33</title><content type='text'>companyname: Digg, companylocation: San Francisco, California, companydesc: Digg is focused on building the best internet platform for news. Digg is building a platform to enable social curation of the world's content and the conversation around it.  It's Digg's belief that people across the world have a constant thirst for finding relevant news in a timely manner., companyurl: www.digg.com, productdesc: Digg develops for the Android SDK for our Android client and the Chrome extension platform., companylogo: digg.png, companypod: Chrome, companytags: Chrome, Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/e0c8p'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/drwu7</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 34</title><content type='text'>companyname: Dito, companylocation: Manassas, Virginia, companydesc: Dito provides Google Apps deployment, development, training, and supporting services to businesses and organizations of all sizes. Our mission is to provide a complete solution for our clients that are seeking to maximize the potential of Google technologies., companyurl: www.ditoweb.com, productdesc: Dito Directory for Google Apps provides external contact management for organizations and is built on Google App Engine with Google Web Toolkit. Dito Directory integrates seamlessly with Google Apps using OpenID for authentication and multiple Google Apps APIs., companylogo: dito.png, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, App Engine, GWT, Social Web, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/drwu7'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/dtbek</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 35</title><content type='text'>companyname: DotSpots, companylocation: Los Angeles, California, companydesc: DotSpots enables anyone to create dots or 'distributed objects of thought.' Dots are bigger than tweets, smaller than blogs, allow wiki-like collaboration and can be easily distributed as global annotations on text in webpages or via social media. By allowing dots on their pages, publishers enable the wisdom of crowds to interactively enrich their content., companyurl: www.dotspots.com, productdesc: DotSpots uses Google Web Toolkit to build their website, and Firefox and Chrome extensions. They're also using the YouTube and Picasa APIs to integrate video and photos into user-generated content., companylogo: dotspots.png, companypod: GWT, companytags: GWT, Chrome, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/dtbek'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/dupz1</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 36</title><content type='text'>companyname: Drawloop Technologies, companylocation: Irvine, California, companydesc: Drawloop Technologies delivers powerful on-demand document creation services to your organization. We provide a simple business process for users to merge and automate dynamic document creation using any combination of Google Docs as well as other documents like Microsoft Word, PowerPoint and Excel., companyurl: www.drawloop.com, productdesc: Drawloop uses many Google technologies. For automating document creation, we utilize the Google Docs API as well as Google's two-legged OAuth. In addition, we use Google Gadgets within Gmail and Google Sites to deploy Dynamic Document Packages (DDPs)., companylogo: drawloop.png, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, Google APIs, Social Web, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/dupz1'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/e7d2q</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 37</title><content type='text'>companyname: EA, companylocation: Redwood City, California, companydesc: EA Mobile is a division of Electronic Arts Inc. (EA), a leading publisher and developer of mobile games. Award-winning hits from EA Mobile include Tetris, Bejeweled, The Sims titles, and Spore Origins. With its strong ties to EA's overall franchises, EA Mobile continues to develop and produce innovative products across all major mobile platforms, including Android.
, companyurl: www.ea.com, productdesc: Rock Band is now on Android. Rock out on guitar, bass, drums or vocals to MP3-quality songs. Fully optimized for Android 2.0 devices. 
, companylogo: ea.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/e7d2q'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/e8rn7</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 38</title><content type='text'>companyname: eBay, companylocation: San Jose, California, companydesc: Founded in 1995, eBay Inc. connects hundreds of millions of people around the world every day by providing the Internet platforms of choice for global commerce, payments and communications. Since its inception, eBay Inc. has expanded to include some of the strongest brands in the world, including eBay, PayPal, Skype, StubHub, Shopping.com, and others., companyurl: www.ebay.com, productdesc: eBay uses OpenSocial and Gadget standard to power its Selling Manager application platform marketplace. We also developed a prototype Gadget using Google Friend Connect that distributes eBay inventory across the GFC network of publishers., companylogo: ebay.png, companypod: Social Web, companytags: Social Web, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/e8rn7'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ea67k</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 39</title><content type='text'>companyname: EchoSign, companylocation: Palo Alto, California, companydesc: EchoSign is a leading electronic signature service with over 10,000 customers and over 1 million users and is used by medium-sized businesses, enterprises, and Fortune 500 companies alike. EchoSign natively integrates with your Google Apps account, including Google docs, spreadsheets, etc. for instant on-line review, approval, and eSignatures., companyurl: www.echosign.com, productdesc: EchoSign integrates Google as an OpenID provider for easy login across both standard Google accounts as well as for Google Apps for businesses and accesses Google Docs via OAuth as a content source allowing customers to easily send any Google Doc for e-Signature., companylogo: echosign.png, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, Social Web, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ea67k'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ebks1</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 40</title><content type='text'>companyname: Eclipse, companylocation: Ottawa, Ontario Canada, companydesc: Eclipse is an open source community, whose projects are focused on building an open development platform comprised of extensible frameworks, tools and runtimes for building, deploying and managing software across the lifecycle. A large, vibrant ecosystem of major technology vendors, innovative start-ups, universities and research institutions and individuals extend, complement and support the Eclipse Platform., companyurl: www.eclipse.org, productdesc: The Eclipse community is introducing the next generation of the Eclipse platform, code name e4, that includes the ability to integrate OpenSocial gadgets into Eclipse based applications., companylogo: eclipse.png, companypod: Social Web, companytags: Social Web, GWT, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ebks1'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/e1qt2</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 41</title><content type='text'>companyname: Entrinsik, companylocation: Raleigh, North Carolina, companydesc: Entrinsik's Informer Web Reporting software delivers true real-time access to operational data simply and easily using a built-in Web-based query engine. Informer leverages a metadata model that creates consistency among data descriptions and structures to provide a single point of access to disparate data  sources for ad hoc report customization and analysis., companyurl: www.entrinsik.com, productdesc: Google Web Toolkit is the engine behind Informer’s drag-and-drop analytics, one click charting, and WYSIWYG criteria builder., companylogo: entrinsik.png, companypod: GWT, companytags: GWT, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/e1qt2'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/e35dj</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 42</title><content type='text'>companyname: Epocrates, companylocation: San Mateo, California, companydesc: Epocrates, Inc. develops clinical information and decision support tools that enable healthcare professionals to find answers more quickly and confidently at the point of care.  More than 950,000 healthcare professionals worldwide and 40% of U.S. physicians use Epocrates’ innovative mobile and web-based products to help them reduce medical errors, improve patient care and increase productivity.
, companyurl: www.epocrates.com, productdesc: You can search for a drug without launching the Epocrates application using the Quick Search box on Android devices., companylogo: epocrates.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/e35dj'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/e4jxw</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 43</title><content type='text'>companyname: ESPN EMEA, companylocation: London, United Kingdom, companydesc: ESPN EMEA is the European digital arm of ESPN international, building and running Cricinfo.com, Soccernet.com, Scrum.com, ESPNF1.com and espn.co.uk, as well as the UK’s ESPN TV channel and other digital properties., companyurl: international.espn.com, productdesc: We are currently using google's Chrome Extension support to engage with cricket fans from all over the world. We use Background Pages and Notification Badges to update our users the moment cricketing news breaks on our website. We’re doing this with Scrum.com and plan on rolling it out for our other properties too. A project is underway to localize our scorecards to Hindi. Google's Transliteration APIs are playing a key role in getting our comprehensive database of over 50,000 players localized., companylogo: espn.png, companypod: Chrome, companytags: Chrome, Google APIs, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/e4jxw'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/e5yid</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 44</title><content type='text'>companyname: Exceptional Software, companylocation: Linthicum, Maryland, companydesc: Exceptional Software Strategies, Inc. is a leading provider of information technology solutions and services to the U.S. Government, educational institutions, and private industry. Exceptional Software can meet all your information technology needs – from customized software products and solutions such as Geographic Information Systems, enterprise-level portals, and information management, to services such as network administration, security design, project management, and interactive training., companyurl: www.exceptionalsoftware.com, productdesc: EarthSpector was developed using the Google Web Toolkit (GWT), and brings GIS analysis capabilities found in heavier desktop products to the flexible platform of the Google Earth Plug-in. EarthSpector is a product of Exceptional Software Strategies, Inc., companylogo: exceptionalsoftware.png, companypod: Geo, companytags: Geo, GWT, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/e5yid'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/emtbd</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 45</title><content type='text'>companyname: eXo Platform, companylocation: San Francisco, California, companydesc: eXo provides a new way to extend, build and deploy applications, complete with rich social computing capabilities, by reusing existing services and components.  An integrated framework and user experience platform in one, the eXo Platform extends and enables rapid development of Java applications with modern APIs and tooling such as OpenSocial, gadgets, REST, Groovy, and mashups., companyurl: www.exoplatform.com, productdesc: Google Web Toolkit is an important part of the eXo Platform, as a part of our IDE and CMIS implementation. We also use the Google Gadget API in GateIn, the open source portal framework that serves as the foundation of eXo Platform. Finally, we support OpenSocial in eXo Enterprise Social, an extended service for eXo Platform., companylogo: exoplatform.png, companypod: Social Web, companytags: Social Web, GWT, Google APIs, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/emtbd'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/eczce</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 46</title><content type='text'>companyname: ExtensionFM, companylocation: New York, New York, companydesc: ExtensionFM turns the entire web into your personal music library. Discovering new music has never been easier: simply browse to your music site of choice and ExtensionFM will automatically add any music it finds into your library and keep you up to date with any new music the site publishes., companyurl: www.extension.fm, productdesc: ExtensionFM is a Google Chrome extension that makes heavy use of HTML5., companylogo: extensionfm.png, companypod: Chrome, companytags: Chrome, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/eczce'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/eedwv</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 47</title><content type='text'>companyname: Eye-Fi, companylocation: Mountain View, California, companydesc: Founded in 2005, Eye-Fi is dedicated to building products and services that help consumers navigate, nurture and share their visual memories. Eye-Fi’s patent-pending technology works with Wi-Fi networks to automatically send photos from a digital camera to online, in-home and retail destinations., companyurl: www.eye.fi, productdesc: Eye-Fi Cards upload images and videos to Picasa Web Albums and to YouTube. We use the API's to enable uploads from our servers, to Google's servers., companylogo: eyefi.png, companypod: Google APIs, companytags: Google APIs, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/eedwv'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/efsh8</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 48</title><content type='text'>companyname: EyeCon, companylocation: Palo Alto, California, companydesc: Eyecon allows you to search through all your media simultaneously and play it to any device, without cluttering the screen, without  getting up, and with zero hassle., companyurl: www.eyecontec.com, productdesc: The Eyecon application was developed using the Android SDK, companylogo: eyecon.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/efsh8'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/eh71p</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 49</title><content type='text'>companyname: EZasset, companylocation: Columbus, Ohio, companydesc: EZasset is an asset management application for home and business. EZasset is a simple and safe way to record and manage data on all your assets. EZasset provides all of the tools needed to manage assets efficiently online., companyurl: www.ezasset.com, productdesc: EZasset utilizes several Google APIs such as Google Calendar for maintenance tracking for assets and Google Docs for easy importing and exporting of information for assets. The Google Maps API is integrated to give visual representation of a physical location where assets are stored. We are running both our home and business applications on App Engine., companylogo: ezasset.png, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, Google APIs, Geo, App Engine, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/eh71p'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/etu5e</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 50</title><content type='text'>companyname: Facebook, companylocation: Palo Alto, California, companydesc: Facebook is all about connections—whether it’s to a friend, or a school, or a community of people. Connections help Facebook create a relevant and meaningful experience for users, and deliver an engaging interaction for those who want to learn more about each other, companyurl: www.facebook.com, productdesc: Facebook for Android lets other Android applications leverage the content of Facebook by allowing direct linking to relevant contact. Facebook also offers Connect to Android applications., companylogo: facebook.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/etu5e'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ev8pv</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 51</title><content type='text'>companyname: Fandango, companylocation: Los Angeles, California, companydesc: Fandango, a leading moviegoer destination, sells tickets to more than 16,000 screens. Fandango entertains and informs consumers with exclusive film clips, trailers, celebrity interviews, fan reviews and news, while offering them the ability to quickly select a film and conveniently buy tickets in advance., companyurl: www.fandango.com, productdesc: Android technologies used: widgets, intents, voice search, Quick Search integration and more., companylogo: fandango.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ev8pv'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ewna8</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 52</title><content type='text'>companyname: Farmigo, companylocation: San Rafael, California, companydesc: Our mission is to make small farming more sustainable so that many more farms can join the growing trend of farms selling direct. Farmigo CSA System is a web-based service created for small farms to promote, collaborate, sell and explain their food items online. Each farm on the Farmigo network receives farm management software for tracking harvest, processing orders, managing logistics, and servicing customers., companyurl: www.farmigo.com, productdesc: Farmigo has built a multi-tenant enterprise solution on Google App Engine enabling small organic farms to network with one another while directly selling to their local communities., companylogo: farmigo.png, companypod: App Engine, companytags: App Engine, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ewna8'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ey1up</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 53</title><content type='text'>companyname: FortiusOne, companylocation: Arlington, Virginia, companydesc: FortiusOne makes it possible to visualize and analyze massive amounts of data, make decisions and solve problems without extensive training using traditional mapping tools by delivering easy-to-use, browser-based solutions. FortiusOne's GeoIQ is a complete data management, visualization, and analysis platform that enables intuitive exploration, sharing and collaboration around geospatial information., companyurl: www.fortiusone.com, productdesc: FortiusOne has integrated with both Google Earth Fusion and the Google Maps API in order to visualize geospatial analysis with GeoIQ Enterprise, on field laptop using GeoIQ Portable, or at the community GeoCommons.com., companylogo: fortiusone.png, companypod: Geo, companytags: Geo, adddate: 4/25/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ey1up'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/eo7vq</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 54</title><content type='text'>companyname: Gameloft, companylocation: San Francisco, California, companydesc: Gameloft is an international publisher and developer of downloadable video games. Gameloft is present on all the continents with its own production studios, employing over 3,500 developers, and distributes its games in over 100 countries., companyurl: www.gameloft.com, productdesc: Asphalt is rocketing onto Android! Get behind the wheel of the best vehicles from prestigious manufacturers (Lamborghini, Kawasaki, Ford, etc) and make a name for yourself in amazing 3D surroundings.
, companylogo: gameloft.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/eo7vq'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/epmg7</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 55</title><content type='text'>companyname: GetGlue, companylocation: New York, New York, companydesc: GetGlue is an innovative social recommendation network for movies, books, and music. The GetGlue website provides a recommendation stream based on personal tastes, what friends like, and what's most popular right now. The GetGlue browser extension brings filtered friend reviews, personal recommendations, and contextual content to popular sites around the web, such as Wikipedia, Amazon, IMDB, and hundreds more., companyurl: www.getglue.com, productdesc: GetGlue makes use of the following Google APIs: Search to retrieve site and page specific information, Contacts to surface the existing social graph, and Books, YouTube, and Images to retrieve rich content. AdaptiveBlue also uses Google Web Toolkit to build their website, and Chrome and Firefox extensions.  , companylogo: getglue.png, companypod: Chrome, companytags: Chrome, Google APIs, GWT, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/epmg7'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/er10k</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 56</title><content type='text'>companyname: Glu, companylocation: San Mateo, California, companydesc: Glu is a global publisher of mobile games for feature phones and smartphones. Its portfolio of top-rated games includes original titles: Beat It!, Bonsai Blast, Brain Genius, Glyder, Stranded, and Super K.O. Boxing! Consumers can find high-quality, fresh entertainment created exclusively for their mobile phones wherever they see the 'g' character logo., companyurl: www.glu.com, productdesc: Super KO Boxing 2 takes full advantage of the Android Native Development Kit (NDK) to bring the highest quality visuals and experience to Android Market. This title features touch screen controls and uses the SD Card to store the 86MB resource file required to run., companylogo: glu.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/er10k'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/esfl1</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 57</title><content type='text'>companyname: Google Checkout, companylocation: Mountain View, California, companydesc: Google Checkout is an alternative payment flow that allows consumers to use a single account to purchase from multiple sites across the web., companyurl: code.google.com/apis/checkout, companylogo: google.png, companypod: Google APIs, companytags: Google APIs, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/esfl1'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/a6oij</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 58</title><content type='text'>companyname: Google Code Labs, companylocation: Mountain View, California, companydesc: Google Code Labs is home to developer products that are still in their formative stages., companyurl: code.google.com/labs, companylogo: google.png, companypod: App Engine, companytags: App Engine, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/a6oij'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bbf0c</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 59</title><content type='text'>companyname: Google Corporate Engineering, companylocation: Mountain View, California, companydesc: Much like Google's mission, Corporate Engineering is about solving real problems that affect a large number of Googlers.  Our goal is to provide the internal technology, infrastructure and support that allow Googlers to be the happiest and most productive workforce on the planet. , companylogo: google.png, companypod: App Engine, companytags: App Engine, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bbf0c'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/a832w</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 60</title><content type='text'>companyname: Google Customer Solutions Engineering, companylocation: Mountain View, California, companydesc: The Customer Solutions Engineering team works with select Google customers to promote consumer product and API adoption. We'll be demoing real-world examples of websites enhanced by Google's APIs., companylogo: google.png, companypod: Google APIs, companytags: Google APIs, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/a832w'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/9znoe</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 61</title><content type='text'>companyname: Google Earth, companylocation: Mountain View, California, companydesc: Google Earth takes advantage of the Android NDK and the OpenGL ES1.1 module. The main application is written in Java, and communicates to the native engine using JNI. Several open source modules in the NDK are used, including libcurl, freeimage, libjpeg, and others. , companyurl: www.google.com/mobile/earth, companylogo: google.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/9znoe'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/a128v</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 62</title><content type='text'>companyname: Google Goggles, companylocation: Mountain View, California, companydesc: Use pictures to search the web. Photograph objects or places to learn more about them. Photograph text to translate it to another language., companyurl: www.google.com/mobile/goggles, companylogo: google.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/a128v'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/a2gt8</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 63</title><content type='text'>companyname: Google Native Client, companylocation: Mountain View, California, companydesc: Native Client is an open-source technology for running native code in web applications, with the goal of maintaining the browser neutrality, portability, and safety that people expect from web apps., companyurl: code.google.com/p/nativeclient, companylogo: google.png, companypod: Chrome, companytags: Chrome, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/a2gt8'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/a3vdp</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 64</title><content type='text'>companyname: Google SkyMap, companylocation: Mountain View, California, companydesc: Google Sky Map turns your Android-powered mobile phone into a window on the night sky. It will identify objects that appear in the sky and allow users to search for various objects. By using your Android phone's orientation sensors, we can show you a star map for your location. You can search for a variety of objects and Google Sky Map direct you to the object's location in the sky., companyurl: www.google.com/sky/skymap, companylogo: google.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/a3vdp'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/agihe</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 65</title><content type='text'>companyname: Google Wave, companylocation: Mountain View, California, companydesc: Google Wave is an online tool for real-time communication and collaboration, built with GWT. A wave can be both a conversation and a document where people can discuss  and work together using richly formatted text, photos, videos, maps, and more, including developer-built extensions (robots and gadgets) with the Google Wave APIs., companyurl: code.google.com/apis/wave, companylogo: google.png, companypod: GWT, companytags: GWT, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/agihe'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ahx1v</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 66</title><content type='text'>companyname: Handmark, companylocation: Kansas City, Missouri, companydesc: Handmark is a leading developer and distributor of mobile applications, specializing in mobile solutions for publishers and media companies. Trusted by many of the world’s leading media brands, Handmark delivers a full-service mobile publishing solution including development, distribution, monetization and on-going innovation.
, companyurl: www.handmark.com, productdesc: Goal.com 3.0, developed on the Handmark Mobile Publishing Platform, provides users with live scores, tables, fixtures, and editorial content for football matches around the world. The Mobile Publishing Platform uses the embedded Media Player to present high quality video content, leverages linkify to tightly integrate content into Android’s platform services, and brings timely content to the home screen through Android App Widgets., companylogo: handmark.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ahx1v'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ajbm8</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 67</title><content type='text'>companyname: Hasbro, companylocation: Pawtucket, Rhode Island, companydesc: Hasbro, Inc. is a worldwide leader in children's and family leisure time products and services with a rich portfolio of brands and entertainment properties that provides some of the highest quality and most recognizable play and recreational experiences in the world., companyurl: www.hasbro.com/monopoly/en_US/discover/news/Monopoly-City-Streets-Has-Ended.cfm, productdesc: MONOPOLY City Streets used Google Maps API, as a way to excite consumers and demonstrate the new game play features to launch the MONOPOLY City board game. To promote the “try before you buy” experience we also worked with Google Sketch Up and ran a competition to design new buildings of which the top 3 were featured in MONOPOLY City Streets., companylogo: hasbro.png, companypod: Geo, companytags: Geo, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ajbm8'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/akq6p</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 68</title><content type='text'>companyname: HP, companylocation: Palo Alto, California, companydesc: HP creates new possibilities for technology to have a meaningful impact on people, businesses and society. HP brings together a portfolio that spans printing, personal computing, software, services and IT infrastructure to solve customer problems., companyurl: www.hp.com, productdesc: Used Google Maps API to create an HP Print App that allows users to print a map and point to point directions directly from HP printers., companylogo: hp.png, companypod: Geo, companytags: Geo, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/akq6p'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/aaw7q</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 69</title><content type='text'>companyname: HTC, companylocation: Taoyuan, Taiwan, companydesc: HTC Corporation (HTC) is one of the fastest growing companies in the mobile phone industry and continues to pioneer industry-leading mobile experiences through design, usability and innovation that are sparked by how the mobile phone can improve how people live and communicate. The company is listed on the Taiwan Stock Exchange under ticker 2498., companyurl: developer.htc.com, productdesc: As a founding member of the OHA and the first to ship Android on a phone, HTC has continued to introduce new Android phones around the world including the recently unveiled HTC Evo 4G, Droid Incredible by HTC, HTC Desire and HTC Legend., companylogo: htc.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/aaw7q'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/acas7</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 70</title><content type='text'>companyname: Hydro4GE Inc., companylocation: Scranton, Pennsylvania, companydesc: Hydro4GE (pronounced hy-dro-forge) is a Platform-as-a-Service (PaaS) that enables developers to rapidly develop complex and adaptable software systems using an online, fourth generation development environment. Hydro4GE shortens the traditional software development life cycle and accelerates time to client-ready solutions by eliminating the most time-consuming and expensive steps for a developer: low-level coding and unit testing., companyurl: www.hydro4ge.com, productdesc: The Hydro4GE user interface is built entirely using the Google Web Toolkit (GWT), relying on a single external dependency, RaphaelJS, for interactive SVG diagrams. GWT allowed us to create a highly-interactive, rich user interface (UI) with emerging features such as database schema visualization via interactive, scalable graphics., companylogo: hydro4ge.png, companypod: GWT, companytags: GWT, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/acas7'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/adpck</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 71</title><content type='text'>companyname: IBM, companylocation: Armonk, New York, companydesc: For nearly 100 years, IBM has served clients in more than 170 countries around the world. Today, IBM’s portfolio is built around networked, modularized and embedded  technologies, such as service-oriented architecture (SOA), business intelligence and analytics. IBM is working with our clients to make many aspects of our world "smarter": roadways, health care, power grids, food production for a better way of living. , companyurl: www.ibm.com, productdesc: IBM is partnering with Google and others in the industry to develop emerging open standards (i.e. OpenSocial) and open source (i.e. Apache Shindig) for the advancement of social networking technologies., companylogo: ibm.png, companypod: Social Web, companytags: Social Web, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/adpck'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/af3x1</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 72</title><content type='text'>companyname: Instantiations, Inc., companylocation: Portland, Oregon, companydesc: Instantiations develops innovative software products for the Eclipse Java open source platform with a wide range of tools for Eclipse, IBM Rational,® JBuilder® and MyEclipse. Instantiations’ AJAX offering, GWT Designer,™ is the leading GUI building tool for GWT and is based on Instantiations’ award-winning WindowBuilder product, named Best Commercial Eclipse-Based Developer Tool of 2009 by the Eclipse Foundation., companyurl: www.instantiations.com, productdesc: GWT Designer helps developers rapidly create GUIs in Eclipse and GWT/Java before deploying them as AJAX applications – using wizards, drag-and-drop visual design, bi-directional code generation, internationalization, a multitude of layout managers, and support for popular add-on widget packages such as Ext GWT (GXT) and GWT-Ext., companylogo: instantiations.png, companypod: GWT, companytags: GWT, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/af3x1'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/arr0q</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 73</title><content type='text'>companyname: Instituto Federal Electoral, companylocation: Mexico Distrito Federal, Mexico, companydesc: Instituto Federal Electoral (IFE) is the government agency in Mexico in charge of Elections., companyurl: www.ife.org.mx/portal/site/ifev2, productdesc: We are using Google Maps APIs to provide our website with the precise locations of voting sites so all of our citizens can locate the precise place where they can vote, and access data of the available candidates, also our voters roll registering offices location., companylogo: ife.png, companypod: Geo, companytags: Geo, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/arr0q'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/at5l7</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 74</title><content type='text'>companyname: InterContinental Hotels Group , companylocation: Atlanta, Georgia, companydesc: IHG is an international hotel company that welcomes over 180 million guests each year in nearly 4,400 hotels (that's over 640,000 rooms!) in 100 countries. We operate seven hotel brands – InterContinental, Crowne Plaza, Hotel Indigo, Holiday Inn, Holiday Inn Express, Staybridge Suites, Candlewood Suites and our Priority Club Loyalty Program., companyurl: www.ichotelsgroup.com, productdesc: We utilize GWT for our public facing websites and many of our internal applications. We use Google Maps on our public facing website and Wallboard application located in our hotel lobbies. InterContinetal.com will soon be launching a new Google maps interface that allows our guests to find nearby concierge suggested attractions, restaurants and services., companylogo: ihg.png, companypod: Geo, companytags: Geo, GWT, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/at5l7'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/auk5k</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 75</title><content type='text'>companyname: JetBrains, companylocation: Prague, Czech Republic, companydesc: JetBrains is a software development company that's crazy-passionate about developer productivity. Want more intelligent development tools? Consider it done. How about more efficient development processes? We've got you covered. What about shorter development cycles? Uh huh, we do that too. Simply put, our tools automate your routine tasks and help you effectively solve the challenging ones., companyurl: www.jetbrains.com, productdesc: We use Google Web Toolkit for several internal systems, and we use Google AJAX APIs on our web sites. But most importantly, we build developer tools for GWT, Google App Engine and Android SDK that allow other developers to build great apps using all these technologies., companylogo: jetbrains.png, companypod: GWT, companytags: GWT, Google APIs, App Engine, Android, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/auk5k'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/avyq1</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 76</title><content type='text'>companyname: Jive Software, companylocation: Portland, Oregon, companydesc: Jive SBS takes all the great things people love about social networking software, collaboration software, and community software and makes those work for business. Jive is a leader in Social Business Software, with an extensive solution, large implementations, and expertise in delivering value., companyurl: www.jivesoftware.com, productdesc: Jive uses OpenSocial in our Jive SBS product to host OpenSocial and Google gadgets., companylogo: jive.png, companypod: Social Web, companytags: Social Web, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/avyq1'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/am4r2</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 77</title><content type='text'>companyname: Juice Analytics, companylocation: Reston, Virginia, companydesc: Juice crafts easy-to-use web applications that engage users with your data. Unlike static dashboards and time-consuming reports, our solutions help your data tell a story., companyurl: www.juiceanalytics.com, productdesc: We use Google Analytics and Website Optimizer to improve our website. Google Analytics API and AppEngine power our analytics visualizations., companylogo: juiceanalytics.png, companypod: Google APIs, companytags: Google APIs, App Engine, adddate: 4/25/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/am4r2'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/anjbj</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 78</title><content type='text'>companyname: Kaazing, companylocation: Mountain View, California, companydesc: Kaazing is a web infrastructure software company that enables companies to quickly deliver massively scalable real-time web applications and significantly simplify their back-end server infrastructure. Its flagship product, Kaazing WebSockets Gateway, can connect hundreds of thousands of concurrent users directly to the real-time data flowing through an organization., companyurl: www.kaazing.com, productdesc: By using the HTML5 WebSockets standard and avoiding the overhead and latency inherent in HTTP, Kaazing WebSockets Gateway extends the use of any TCP-based messaging format to any browser, delivering ultra-high performance bi-directional communication over the Web without the use of browser plug-ins., companylogo: kaazing.png, companypod: Chrome, companytags: Chrome, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/anjbj'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/aoxvw</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 79</title><content type='text'>companyname: Kashoo, companylocation: Vancouver, BC, Canada, companydesc: Kashoo is online accounting for small business. Designed with simplicity and ease-of-use in mind, Kashoo allows you to take control of your finances and record keeping without having to install and learn complicated software., companyurl: www.kashoo.com, productdesc: We're using Google Web Toolkit to build our online software., companylogo: kashoo.png, companypod: GWT, companytags: GWT, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/aoxvw'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/aqcgd</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 80</title><content type='text'>companyname: Korem, companylocation: Quebec City, QC, Canada, companydesc: Korem is a North American geospatial system integrator that has been at the forefront of geospatial technology, business Intelligence and location-oriented demographic analysis since 1993. We create and implement integrated geospatial solutions based on your business needs, and we enable you to better utilize your data and improve your business decision-making capabilities., companyurl: www.korem.com, productdesc: Korem develops and implements geospatial solutions using the Google Maps API and Google Earth Enterprise., companylogo: korem.png, companypod: Geo, companytags: Geo, Enterprise, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/aqcgd'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/b2zk2</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 81</title><content type='text'>companyname: Kuali Foundation, Inc., companylocation: Bloomington, Indiana, companydesc: Kuali Student is a next-generation student system currently under development. We will offer a flexible, scalable, cost-effective system that can be configured to meet the business requirements of any higher education institution. Our student-centric design will help students, faculty, and institutions deal with the dynamic learning environment., companyurl: student.kuali.org, productdesc: Kuali Student is using GWT to building its rich user interface which will be used by faculty, students and staff., companylogo: kuali.png, companypod: GWT, companytags: GWT, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/b2zk2'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/b4e4j</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 82</title><content type='text'>companyname: Laminar Research, companylocation: Columbia, South Carolina, companydesc: Laminar Research is the brains behind X-Plane, the most realistic flight simulator available for person computers. Started in 1995 by Austin Meyer, Laminar Research is well known to be the company behind the most physically accurate games and simulations available in the consumer market., companyurl: www.x-plane.com, productdesc: Android technologies used: OpenGL ES for drawing; Accelerometers and multi-touch for input; and sound streaming interface for sound, companylogo: laminarresearch.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/b4e4j'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/b5sow</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 83</title><content type='text'>companyname: LastPass, companylocation: Vienna, Virginia, companydesc: LastPass provides a free password manager that works across all major platforms and browsers including Google Chrome, Firefox, Safari and Internet Explorer on Windows, Mac and Linux. Multi-factor authentication solutions and mobile solutions on Android, iPhone, Blackberry, Symbian, webOS and Windows Mobile are also available., companyurl: www.lastpass.com, productdesc: We are using Chrome Extension APIs to build a native chrome password manager extension, and the AndroidSDK to build the LastPass for Android mobile app., companylogo: lastpass.png, companypod: Chrome, companytags: Chrome, Android, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/b5sow'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/b779d</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 84</title><content type='text'>companyname: LGE, companylocation: Seoul, Korea, companydesc: Founded in 1958, LG Electronics has led the way in bringing advanced digital products and applied technologies to our customers. With our commitment to innovation and assertive global business policies, we aim to become a worldwide leader in advanced digital technology., companyurl: www.lge.com, productdesc: We are using Google Mobile Services on our mobile devices to enhance user value., companylogo: lge.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/b779d'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/axdae</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 85</title><content type='text'>companyname: LinkedIn, companylocation: Mountain View, CA, companydesc: LinkedIn takes your professional network online, giving you access to people, jobs and opportunities like never before. Built upon trusted connections and relationships, LinkedIn has established the world’s largest and most powerful professional network. Currently, more than 55 million professionals are on LinkedIn., companyurl: www.linkedin.com, productdesc: LinkedIn uses many Google technologies. For Java development we use Google Collections and Guice to speed development. Our OpenSocial-based InApps platform uses Apache Shindig, which powers LinkedIn Polls, Events, Company Buzz and Tweets. Shindig OAuth technology is also used in our Open API Program., companylogo: linkedin.png, companypod: Social Web, companytags: Social Web, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/axdae'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ayruv</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 86</title><content type='text'>companyname: Lombardi, An IBM Company, companylocation: Austin, Texas, companydesc: Lombardi believes that a Process-Driven approach is the best way to win. We deliver a suite of Business Process Management (BPM) software and services that enable organizations to quickly become Process-Driven., companyurl: www.lombardi.com, productdesc: Lombardi has been using GWT since 2007. We use it to develop all the user interface for Lombardi Blueprint, our software as a service process discovery and documentation product, and the web based portions of the developer interface for Lombardi Teamworks 7, our process automation, simulation and management suite., companylogo: lombardi.png, companypod: GWT, companytags: GWT, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ayruv'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/b06f8</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 87</title><content type='text'>companyname: LTech, companylocation: Bridgewater, New Jersey , companydesc: LTech is a provider of enterprise cloud computing services and broad mix of cloud enablement products for the Google Apps platform. As an early Google Enterprise Partner, LTech has successfully completed dozens of Google Apps deployments and helped develop best-practices for adopting and successfully scaling cloud computing programs., companyurl: www.ltech.com, productdesc: LTech relies heavily on the Google Apps APIs and OAuth for several products. Our LTech Power Panel for Google Apps product is built on top of Google App Engine, leverages Google Web Toolkit and uses many of the Google Apps Management and Application APIs., companylogo: ltech.png, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, Google APIs, Social Web, App Engine, GWT, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/b06f8'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/b1kzp</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 88</title><content type='text'>companyname: Manymoon, companylocation: San Francisco, California, companydesc: Manymoon is the simplest way to get work done online with your contacts. Track projects, complete tasks and share information with no training or setup. Easy enough for anyone to use, Manymoon provides the privacy required for work and the simplicity of social applications. Manymoon is a top-rated application for Google Apps and is trusted by tens of thousands of businesses., companyurl: www.manymoon.com/auth/login?v=googleIOsandbox, productdesc: Manymoon uses the Google Documents Data List API, Calendar API and Google Charts to work with tasks, projects and work activity. Google Gadgets API and OpenSocial are used to access Manymoon within Google Apps. Customers can securely login using OpenID. The Provisioning API is used for administration., companylogo: manymoon.png, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, Google APIs, Social Web, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/b1kzp'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/be856</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 89</title><content type='text'>companyname: MediaBeacon, companylocation: Minneapolis, Minnesota, companydesc: MediaBeacon is a Digital Asset Management and Enterprise Search company that provides rich media management and intelligent content discovery solutions to enterprises. , companyurl: www.mediabeacon.com, productdesc: We use Google Web Toolkit to power the entire interface layer of our enterprise digital asset management system., companylogo: mediabeacon.png, companypod: GWT, companytags: GWT, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/be856'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bfmpn</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 90</title><content type='text'>companyname: Meebo, companylocation: Mountain View, California, companydesc: Meebo enables over 100 million users to instantly connect, share, and communicate with all of their friends. Because Meebo integrates all social network and communication channels into a single, simple-to-use interface, users can easily share content and communicate in real time with the people who matter to them., companyurl: www.meebo.com, productdesc: Meebo has been developing XAuth as an open standard for simplifying access to users' online services anywhere on the web. Together with the Google Buzz APIs, we are making our products smarter and more personalized for visitors as they navigate across the social web., companylogo: meebo.png, companypod: Social Web, companytags: Social Web, Google APIs, adddate: 4/25/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bfmpn'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bh1a0</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 91</title><content type='text'>companyname: Memeo, companylocation: Aliso Viejo, California, companydesc: Memeo Inc. is a privately-held software company focused on helping consumers and businesses share, manage, and protect their digital content. The company was founded in 2003 and has shipped 45 million software licenses to over 150 countries.  , companyurl: www.memeo.com, productdesc: Memeo Connect bridges Google Docs cloud storage with desktop software. With Memeo Connect, instant access to your important documents while online or offline is now very possible. Memeo Connect is available on both Windows and Mac platforms., companylogo: memeo.png, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bh1a0'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bifuh</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 92</title><content type='text'>companyname: Mibbit, companylocation: London, United Kingdom, companydesc: Mibbit gives anyone the capability to host fast, flexible group chat on their website through the use of its customisable Javascript widget.  Mibbit currently connects to IRC networks and Twitter, YouTube and other Google services giving people the ability to collaborate around content and data in real-time., companyurl: www.mibbit.com, productdesc: We use several Google APIs: the YouTube data API lets users preview and play content inside chat; the Maps API shows maps inside chat, helping people explore locations; the Google Translate API translates chats across different languages in real-time; and the AdSense API displays contextually targeted ads that reflect users' preferences., companylogo: mibbit.png, companypod: Google APIs, companytags: Google APIs, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bifuh'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bctkt</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 93</title><content type='text'>companyname: MindMeister, companylocation: Munich, Germany, companydesc: MindMeister allows your team to be more innovative by providing a shared collaboration and brainstorming environment using the proven mind mapping technique. Plan projects, manage meetings and sketch out business plans online with partners and colleagues, all in real time!, companyurl: www.mindmeister.com, productdesc: MindMeister  uses the Google Documents Data List API and Contacts API  to  export mind maps to Google Docs and allow sharing with Google contacts. Customers can securely login using OpenID. The Provisioning API is used for administration., companylogo: mindmeister.png, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, Google APIs, Social Web, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bctkt'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bpgoi</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 94</title><content type='text'>companyname: Mint.com, companylocation: Mountain View, California, companydesc: Mint.com lets you see all of your accounts in one place, set budgets, see where you spend, and find personalized savings – all for free.
, companyurl: www.mint.com, productdesc: Mint.com for Android helps you track all of your accounts, budget, and manage your money right from your phone, updated automatically.  The app takes advantage of key Android features such as widgets, smart folders, and system searches of Mint transactions.
, companylogo: mint.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bpgoi'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bqv8z</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 95</title><content type='text'>companyname: MLB, companylocation: New York, New York, companydesc: MLB Advanced Media, the interactive media company of Major League Baseball, manages the official league site and each of the 30 individual Club sites to create the most comprehensive Major League Baseball resource on the Internet.
, companyurl: www.mlb.com, productdesc: MLB.com At Bat 2010 delivers an exclusive and reliable mobile experience for fans wherever they go with up-to-the-minute box scores and statistics, live audio with home and away broadcast feeds, in-game video highlights, MLB.com Gameday pitch speed and location tracking, and more on Android., companylogo: mlb.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bqv8z'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bs9tc</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 96</title><content type='text'>companyname: Mobiata, companylocation: Ann Arbor, Michigan, companydesc: Mobiata, founded in November 2008, is a leader in mobile travel applications through innovative and beautifully designed products., companyurl: www.mobiata.com, productdesc: Track all your flights on beautiful satellite maps or elegant flight cards that update in real-time.  An Android exclusive is a home screen widget that provides the latest information on your flight regardless of which app is running.
, companylogo: mobiata.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bs9tc'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/btodt</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 97</title><content type='text'>companyname: MobiTV, companylocation: Emeryville, California, companydesc: MobiTV, Inc. is a provider of technology solutions that deliver media over wireless and broadband networks. MobiTV’s flexible platform powers an end-to-end managed service for content ingestion, encoding and optimized delivery of media for major mobile operators., companyurl: www.mobitv.com, productdesc: MobiTV has taken advantage of Android’s open platform to create a unique media player that supports download of high quality video content with digital rights management for offline playback., companylogo: mobitv.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/btodt'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bjueu</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 98</title><content type='text'>companyname: Motorola, companylocation: Schaumburg, Illinois, companydesc: Motorola is known around the world for innovation in communications and focused on advancing the way the world connects. The Motorola MOTODEV™ Developer Program provides developers access to a wealth of services, support, and information to help design, develop and market wireless applications., companyurl: developer.motorola.com, productdesc: Motorola has chosen Android as a simple, powerful means to bring a whole new generation of phenomenal mobile experiences to Motorola users and has already announced an extensive portfolio of Android based handsets around the world. MOTODEV, Motorola's developer network, offers the one, easy-to-access, internet-enabled, open environment developers need to succeed in the future., companylogo: motorola.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bjueu'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bl8zb</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 99</title><content type='text'>companyname: mSpot, companylocation: Redwood City, California, companydesc: mSpot is free and the simplest way to get your entire music collection to your Android phone and listen from other internet-connected devices. mSpot is a mobile and PC entertainment company that delivers music, movies, and radio to more than six million mobile customers across 10 wireless carriers., companyurl: www.mspot.com, productdesc: Android technologies used: Android SDK and Eclipse Plug-in for app development; and Google Closure Tools to verify our JavaScript code used on website
, companylogo: mspot.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, GWT, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bl8zb'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bmnjo</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 100</title><content type='text'>companyname: myERP, companylocation: San Francisco, California, companydesc: myERP.com is a free online business suite that allows small businesses to manage their business in the cloud. myERP.com streamlines small businesses: sales, purchases, CRM, accounting, inventory, and logistics., companyurl: www.myerp.com, productdesc: myERP.com is developed using Google Web Toolkit on the client-side. GWT converts the Java code into a user interface of the AJAX type. While the user interfaces display in a few milliseconds, the application is just as user-friendly and intuitive as a locally installed application. myERP.com is also integrated with Google Apps, Gmail, Google Calendar and Contacts., companylogo: myerp.png, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, GWT, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bmnjo'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bo245</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 101</title><content type='text'>companyname: MySpace, companylocation: Beverly Hills, California, companydesc: MySpace is a technology company connecting people through personal expression, content, and culture. MySpace empowers its global community to experience the Internet through a social lens by integrating personal profiles, photos, videos, mobile, messaging, games, and the world's largest music community., companyurl: www.myspace.com, productdesc: MySpace supports the development of applications based on OpenSocial, allowing developers to have a standardized way to develop great social apps across platforms. As a founding partner of OpenSocial with Google, MySpace is dedicated to open standards and specifications., companylogo: myspace.png, companypod: Social Web, companytags: Social Web, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bo245'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/c0p7u</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 102</title><content type='text'>companyname: NaturalMotion , companylocation: San Francisco, California, companydesc: In addition to developing games, NaturalMotion provides advanced animation technologies for titles such as GTA IV, Red Dead Redemption and Star Wars.
, companyurl: www.naturalmotion.com, productdesc: Backbreaker is an Android game with Android-specific features including uprated graphics and effects optimised for Android devices., companylogo: naturalmotion.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/c0p7u'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/c23sb</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 103</title><content type='text'>companyname: nextstop, companylocation: San Francisco, California, companydesc: nextstop is a community effort to build a catalog of all the best things to do, places to go, and experiences to try anywhere in the world. Our long term goal is to help you find something great to get out and do — whatever you are interested in, whatever language you speak, and wherever you are., companyurl: www.nextstop.com, productdesc: nextstop's web app runs on smartphones like Android, iPhone and modern browsers by using the latest HTML5 features such as localStorage, AppCache and GeoLocation. We also extensively use the Google AJAX APIs and Google Maps APIs., companylogo: nextstop.png, companypod: Chrome, companytags: Chrome, Android, Geo, Google APIs, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/c23sb'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/c3ico</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 104</title><content type='text'>companyname: Ning, companylocation: Palo Alto, California, companydesc: Ning is a social platform for the world’s interests and passions online, offering an easy-to-use service that allows people to join and create Ning Networks. With more than 1.9 million Ning Networks created and 40 million registered users, millions of people every day are coming together across Ning to explore and express their interests, discover new passions, and meet new people around shared pursuits., companyurl: www.ning.com, productdesc: Ning Apps empower Ning Network Creators with a greater set of choices over the functionality of their Ning Network and ways they can increase engagement by their members. We support a subset of OpenSocial 0.8 APIs., companylogo: ning.png, companypod: Social Web, companytags: Social Web, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/c3ico'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/c4wx5</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 105</title><content type='text'>companyname: NordicTrack, companylocation: Logan, Utah, companydesc: NordicTrack is the premium brand more people buy for treadmills, ellipticals and other fitness products. Our consumers want to stay motivated and engaged for fitness, so we launched the interactive website iFit.com. The flagship feature is iFit Live powered by Google Maps, where you can draw a custom running route anywhere in the world there’s a map available., companyurl: www.ifit.com, productdesc: Using Wi-Fi, iFit.com sends a workout to your equipment that simulates the distance and the terrain of the route you’ve drawn. You can watch your real-time progress on Google Maps with satellite, 3D, and Street views. We’re bringing our NordicTrack X7i Incline Trainer – an extreme treadmill that inclines to 40% - so come by and experience the combination of NordicTrack, iFit, the Google Static Maps, JavaScript Maps and Earth API!, companylogo: nordictrack.png, companypod: Geo, companytags: Geo, adddate: 4/22/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/c4wx5'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bv2y6</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 106</title><content type='text'>companyname: Novell, companylocation: Waltham, Massachusetts, companydesc: Through our infrastructure software and ecosystem of partnerships, Novell harmoniously integrates mixed IT environments, allowing people and technology to work as one. Novell® Making IT Work As One™., companyurl: www.novell.com, productdesc: Novell Pulse is a new real-time collaboration environment for enterprises that's being built with Google Wave Federation Protocol so people can co-edit messages together across Novell Pulse and Google Wave in real-time. Novell Pulse also supports the Wave Gadgets API and Wave Robots API so extensions built by 3rd parties work seamlessly with a mix of users on Novell Pulse and Google Wave., companylogo: novell.png, companypod: Wave, companytags: Wave, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bv2y6'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bwhin</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 107</title><content type='text'>companyname: NPR, companylocation: Washington, D.C., companydesc: NPR is an award-winning, multimedia news organization and an influential force in American life. In collaboration with more than 800 independent public radio stations nationwide, NPR strives to create a more informed public, one challenged and invigorated by a deeper understanding and appreciation of events, ideas, and cultures. NPR content is also available on other platforms such as satellite radio, an expansive web site, and mobile devices., companyurl: www.npr.org, productdesc: NPR news and content is available as an Android app (developed using the Android SDK), a Chrome Extension, and iGoogle Gadget. Additionally, search for NPR.org and the NPR API are powered by Google Search Appliances., companylogo: npr.png, companypod: Chrome, companytags: Chrome, Android, Enterprise, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bwhin'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bxw30</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 108</title><content type='text'>companyname: NYSTROM Herff Jones Education Division, companylocation: Indianapolis, Indiana, companydesc: NYSTROM Herff Jones Education Division is the leading publisher of maps, globes, atlases, hands-on programs, and technology for the K-12 market. Introduced by NYSTROM in September 2009, StrataLogicaTM is a revolutionary, web-based product that delivers layers of age-appropriate, curriculum-based Social Studies content for K-12., companyurl: www.herffjones.com, productdesc: NYSTROM Herff Jones Education Division is using the Google Earth API to power the 3-D educational content available through StrataLogica. By using the Google Earth API, Nystrom and Roundarch have partnered to reinvent the classroom map and globe and present educational content in a groundbreaking, interactive format. , companylogo: herffjones.png, companypod: Geo, companytags: Geo, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bxw30'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bzanh</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 109</title><content type='text'>companyname: OffiSync, companylocation: Seattle, Washington, companydesc: OffiSync Supercharges Microsoft Office, enabling users to significantly improve the way they create, collaborate and share their documents by integrating Microsoft Office with Google Docs, and Google Apps., companyurl: www.offisync.com, productdesc: OffiSync uses the Google Doclist API and Google Search API to extend the core functionality of Microsoft OFfice and introduce new innovative ways of collaboration in the cloud., companylogo: offisync.png, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, Google APIs, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/bzanh'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/cbxr6</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 110</title><content type='text'>companyname: OnStar, companylocation: Detroit, Michigan, companydesc: OnStar, a leading provider of in-vehicle safety, security and communication services, has nearly 5.5 million subscribers, and is available on more than 30 MY 2010 GM models., companyurl: www.onstar.com, productdesc: The Chevrolet Volt Mobile App is powered by OnStar technology and is available on Android phones. Features include the ability to lock/unlock, remotely start your vehicle, view state of charge and remotely control when your Volt draws power from the grid., companylogo: onstar.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/4/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/cbxr6'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/cdcbn</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 111</title><content type='text'>companyname: OpenTable, companylocation: San Francisco, California, companydesc: OpenTable is a leading online provider of free, real-time online restaurant reservations for diners and reservation and guest management solutions for restaurants. OpenTable has more than 11,000 restaurant customers, and since its inception in 1998, has seated more than 120 million diners around the world., companyurl: www.opentable.com, productdesc: We use Google Maps and two versions of the Geolocation API to display real-time restaurant availability around a user’s current location on opentable.com and the Android smartphone platform., companylogo: opentable.png, companypod: Geo, companytags: Geo, Android, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/cdcbn'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ceqw0</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 112</title><content type='text'>companyname: Oracle, companylocation: Redwood Shores, California, companydesc: Oracle provides a complete, open, and integrated business software and hardware systems to more than 370,000 customers—including 100 of the Fortune 100—that represent a variety of sizes and industries in more than 145 countries around the globe., companyurl: www.oracle.com, productdesc: Demonstrating Oracle CRM OnDemand and OnPremise Collaboration with Google Wave, Google Docs, and OpenSocial gadgets.  Integration developed using Google Web Toolkit, Google App Engine and CRM OnDemand and OnPremise Web Services., companylogo: oracle.png, companypod: Wave, companytags: Wave, Social Web, App Engine, GWT, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ceqw0'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/cg5gh</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 113</title><content type='text'>companyname: Orange Honey, companylocation: Seattle, Washington, companydesc: Orange Honey has developed online photo editing and vector sketching applications that bring desktop application quality to the browser and
mobile experience., companyurl: www.orangehoney.com, productdesc: Orange Honey products utilize Google Chrome and the HTML5 Canvas standard to support cross-platform image sharing and accessibility, providing a rich image creation and sharing experience for all users., companylogo: orangehoney.png, companypod: Chrome, companytags: Chrome, adddate: 4/22/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/cg5gh'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/c6bhi</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 114</title><content type='text'>companyname: OrangeScape, companylocation: Chennai, Tamilnadu, India, companydesc: OrangeScape is a Plaform-as-a-Service for building business applications that can run across cloud platforms - Google App Engine, IBM SmartCloud, Amazon EC2 or your own data center., companyurl: www.orangescape.com, productdesc: The development environment - OrangeScape Studio - runs on App Engine and the application developed on OrangeScape Studio can be deployed on App Engine., companylogo: orangescape.png, companypod: App Engine, companytags: App Engine, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/c6bhi'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/c7q1z</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 115</title><content type='text'>companyname: Oxylabs Networks, companylocation: Gurgaon, Haryana, India, companydesc: Oxylabs develops cross-platform, cross-device social games., companyurl: www.oxylabs.com, productdesc: We use several Google technologies to develop our platform: App Engine for a scalable back end; OpenSocial for distribution; Google Charts for our API; Google Translate for our feedback management system; and Google Apps for email, collaboration and documents., companylogo: oxylabs.png, companypod: App Engine, companytags: App Engine, Social Web, Google APIs, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/c7q1z'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/c94mc</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 116</title><content type='text'>companyname: Palm, companylocation: Sunnyvale, California, companydesc: Palm creates intuitive and powerful mobile experiences that enable consumers and businesses to connect to their information in more useful and usable ways., companyurl: www.palm.com, productdesc: Palm has a long history of working closely with Google, building services like Google Search and Google Maps directly into Palm devices.  Palm and Google share the same belief in the Web and the opportunities it provides developers.  The native platform for Palm's groundbreaking webOS is the Web, allowing you to write real applications for mobile as easily as you can write them for the Web.   , companylogo: palm.png, companypod: Chrome, companytags: Chrome, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/c94mc'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/caj6t</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 117</title><content type='text'>companyname: Pandora, companylocation: Oakland, California, companydesc: Pandora is the world’s largest internet radio service available through personal computers, mobile phones, and a wide array of consumer electronic devices. More than 45 million listeners enjoy personalized radio stations based on Pandora’s Music Genome Project™, which enables Pandora to quickly and easily create relevant playlists, full of discovery., companyurl: www.pandora.com, productdesc: We use a number of Google products: the Android SDK for creating the Pandora app, Google Analytics, Google Webmaster Tools, AdSense and DoubleClick., companylogo: pandora.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/caj6t'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hmyxm</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 118</title><content type='text'>companyname: Parrot, companylocation: Paris, France, companydesc: Parrot, a global leader in wireless devices for mobile phones, stands on the cutting edge of innovation. In January 2010, Parrot introduced the Parrot AR.Drone, a flying Wi-Fi quadricopter, which allows users to play video games in Augmented Reality., companyurl: www.parrot.com, productdesc: The Parrot AR.Drone utilizes wifi connectivity, OpenGL ES for video streaming, and the accelerometer and trackball for navigation controls., companylogo: parrot.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/4/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hmyxm'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hodi3</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 119</title><content type='text'>companyname: PayPal, companylocation: San Jose, California, companydesc: PayPal is the faster, safer way to pay and get paid online. The service allows members to send money without sharing financial information, with the flexibility to pay using their account balances, bank accounts, credit cards or promotional financing., companyurl: www.paypal.com, productdesc: With the PayPal Mobile Payments Library, Android developers will be able to start accepting in-app payments for physical goods, services, donations and personal payments in a matter of minutes. Collecting financial information or requiring the consumer to fill long forms to complete a purchase is no longer needed, the PayPal library takes care of the payment flow and developers can keep focusing on building great apps.
, companylogo: paypal.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hodi3'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hps2g</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 120</title><content type='text'>companyname: PlanetInAction, companylocation: Auckland, New Zealand, companydesc: Dinther Product Design Ltd showcases their browser-based games on PlanetInAction.com, an example of what can be done with the Google Earth API. We also handle commercial projects where we develop innovative software solutions using Google Earth and other Google products., companyurl: www.planetinaction.com, productdesc: We mainly use the Google Maps and Earth API. Our solutions tend to be low tech, because we focus on results and short development times., companylogo: planetinaction.png, companypod: Geo, companytags: Geo, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hps2g'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hr6mx</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 121</title><content type='text'>companyname: Plaxo, companylocation: Mountain View, California, companydesc: Plaxo is working to deliver on the vision of a truly smart, socially-aware address book that lives securely in the cloud, while interacting with all of the applications, services, and devices in your life where contact information matters., companyurl: www.plaxo.com, productdesc: We are using Google Contacts Data APIs to build two-way contact sync between Plaxo and Google., companylogo: plaxo.png, companypod: Social Web, companytags: Social Web, Google APIs, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hr6mx'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hhcny</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 122</title><content type='text'>companyname: Playfish, companylocation: San Francisco, California, companydesc: Playfish is a leader in the social gaming industry in innovation and creativity with award-winning, category-defining games designed for friends to play together. The company has changed the way people play games by creating more social and connected experiences., companyurl: www.playfish.com, productdesc: Playfish has brought some of its most iconic social games to Open Social communities around the world, from Who Has The Biggest Brain? on iGoogle, to Pet Society on Cyworld, and Word Challenge on Netlog., companylogo: playfish.png, companypod: Social Web, companytags: Social Web, adddate: 4/25/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hhcny'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hir8f</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 123</title><content type='text'>companyname: PolarBit, companylocation: Stockholm, Sweden, companydesc: Polarbit is a leading developer of high-end 3D games and middleware for the mobile and handheld markets worldwide. Our dedication to our work and uncompromising attitude towards quality ensure customers and users that Polarbit technology is always synonymous with world class technology.
, companyurl: www.polarbit.com, productdesc: Polarbit games are built using the Android NDK, companylogo: polarbit.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hir8f'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hk5ss</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 124</title><content type='text'>companyname: Prezi, companylocation: San Francisco, CA, companydesc: Prezi is a web-based presentation application and storytelling tool that uses a single canvas instead of traditional slides. The canvas allows users to create non-linear presentations, where they can zoom in and out of a visual map., companyurl: www.prezi.com, productdesc: Prezi uses the Google Wave Gadgets API to create new features and functionality for our presentation editor., companylogo: prezi.png, companypod: Wave, companytags: Wave, adddate: 4/25/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hk5ss'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hlkd9</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 125</title><content type='text'>companyname: ProcessOne, companylocation: Paris, France, companydesc: ProcessOne provides real-time interpersonal web communications for telecommunications organisations, ISPs, social networking sites and large enterprises. Well-known businesses benefit from our expertise in real-time instant messaging., companyurl: www.process-one.net, productdesc: As an extension to its XMPP server, ProcessOne uses the Google Wave Federation Protocol in its own "WaveOne" server, federated with Google's WaveSandbox and FedOne., companylogo: processone.png, companypod: Wave, companytags: Wave, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hlkd9'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hy7gy</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 126</title><content type='text'>companyname: processWave.org, companylocation: Potsdam, Germany, companydesc: processWave.org is the project of seven students from Germany's #1 ranked software engineering school, the Hasso Plattner Institute in Potsdam, Germany. We are working on a collaborative diagram editor that supports software and business process modeling with UML, BPMN and EPC. It allows multiple people to edit the same diagram at the same time., companyurl: www.processwave.org, productdesc: Our diagram editor is realized as a gadget for Google Wave, which provides the collaborative basis for our product., companylogo: processwave.png, companypod: Wave, companytags: Wave, adddate: 4/25/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hy7gy'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hzm1f</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 127</title><content type='text'>companyname: Qik, companylocation: Redwood City, California, companydesc: Qik lets people capture and share live and recorded video with their friends, family, and the world, right from their phone., companyurl: www.qik.com, productdesc: Qik uses the Android SDK to produce video recording and broadcasting software for all Android phones, and Google Maps for website video location information, companylogo: qik.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, Geo, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hzm1f'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/i10ls</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 128</title><content type='text'>companyname: Red Hat, companylocation: Raleigh, North Carolina, companydesc: JBoss Enterprise Middleware is a broad portfolio of enterprise-class open source middleware, delivered by Red Hat, a leader in open source solutions. The portfolio includes application, portal, data integration, rules management and ESB-based SOA platforms. JBoss Enterprise Middleware is available via subscriptions that include patches, updates, support, multi-year maintenance policies, and software assurance., companyurl: www.redhat.com, productdesc: We use GWT for several of our products, including the JBoss Web Framwork Kit, the JBoss Business Rules Management System, and development frameworks like Seam, which provides GWT integration layer. GateIn, our new portal project, includes the ability for end users to easily create GWT widgets and portlet-based applications and dashboards within a secure, personalized site experience., companylogo: redhat.png, companypod: GWT, companytags: GWT, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/i10ls'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/i2f69</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 129</title><content type='text'>companyname: Remember The Milk, companylocation: Sydney, NSW, Australia, companydesc: Remember The Milk is an online task management service with more than 2 million users. With products available in 31 languages, Remember The Milk helps people all over the world be more organized and productive., companyurl: www.rememberthemilk.com, productdesc: Remember The Milk makes extensive use of Google technologies. Products include an Android app, offline web app access with Gears, a Google Maps mashup to visualize task locations, Google Talk reminders, Google Calendar sidebar and event gadgets, an iGoogle gadget, a Gmail sidebar gadget, and Firefox and Google Chrome extensions that integrate with Gmail., companylogo: rememberthemilk.png, companypod: Google APIs, companytags: Google APIs, Android, Geo, Chrome, adddate: 4/22/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/i2f69'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hsl7a</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 130</title><content type='text'>companyname: Rent.com, companylocation: Santa Monica, California, companydesc: With Rent.com, property owners and managers can create rich listings that include photos, floorplans, amenities, move-in specials, and detailed descriptions, while renters can search millions of units, filtering by number of beds/bath, city, neighborhood, price and amenities in order to find their perfect home., companyurl: www.rent.com, productdesc: We are using the Google maps API V3.0 on the Android and iPhone OS for mapping the location of, and providing driving directions to, rental properties that match a user's specific search criteria. We are also providing a search nearby feature that makes use of the Google Maps API V3.0., companylogo: rent.png, companypod: Geo, companytags: Geo, Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hsl7a'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/htzrr</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 131</title><content type='text'>companyname: Roambi, companylocation: San Diego, California, companydesc: Roambi, from MeLLmo, is the next generation mobile business application. Roambi puts the pulse of your business in the palm of your hand by transforming existing business reports and data into rich, interactive visualizations and mobile dashboards, delivered to any iPhone. Roambi lets busy professionals track the status of their project, department or company – anytime and anywhere – and make faster, smarter decisions on-the-go., companyurl: www.roambi.com, productdesc: Roambi utilizes the Google Docs and Spreadsheet APIs as well as OAuth to give users the ability to convert data from Google spreadsheets into our interactive views., companylogo: roambi.png, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, Social Web, Google APIs, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/htzrr'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hwswl</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 132</title><content type='text'>companyname: RockYou, companylocation: Redwood City, California, companydesc: RockYou is a leading innovator, creator, and distributor of content on the social web, with over 90M monthly US users, 250M users worldwide, and 15 billion global impressions., companyurl: www.rockyou.com, productdesc: We utilize Open Social to implement our applications for many of the large social networks out there including MySpace in the US, Mixi in Japan, and Cyworld in Korea. We've been big proponents for the Open Social platform and were key in pushing adoption by all of the Asian platforms., companylogo: rockyou.png, companypod: Social Web, companytags: Social Web, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/hwswl'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/i9g0a</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 133</title><content type='text'>companyname: Rosetta, companylocation: Hamilton, New Jersey, companydesc: Rosetta is the largest independent interactive agency in the country whose Personality-based segmentations uncover the drivers of brand choice and product usage. Rosetta's industry-focused marketers, world-class technology teams and creative teams translate those insights into relevant marketing solutions that attract, retain and deepen a brand's best customer relationships., companyurl: www.rosetta.com, productdesc: We use Google Web Toolkit to create the user interface for a number of our different ecommerce clients. The toolkit flexibility and ease of use enables us to create a cutting edge, brilliant, web 2.0 feel for our websites., companylogo: rosetta.png, companypod: GWT, companytags: GWT, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/i9g0a'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/iaukr</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 134</title><content type='text'>companyname: RunMyProcess, companylocation: Paris, France, companydesc: RunMyProcess is the platform as a service of choice for workflows and integration in the Cloud. It offers a complete integration with Google Apps, as well as a set of 1,000+ connectors to link it in a few clicks to most traditionnal or SaaS softwares., companyurl: www.runmyprocess.com, productdesc: We provide an abstraction layer on almost all of Google's web service API (Calendar, Sites, Spreadsheet, Docs, Analytics, etc) allowing users to use any API easily within workflows or business process designed on our platform. We use Google Web Toolkit for dynamically generating web applications and gadgets, as well as GViz for reporting dashboard on workflows embedded within gadgets. W also use Google's enablement of OAuth, OpenID and SAMLv2 for unified authentication capabilities., companylogo: runmyprocess.png, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, Google APIs, GWT, Social Web, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/iaukr'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ic954</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 135</title><content type='text'>companyname: SADA Systems, companylocation: Los Angeles, California, companydesc: One of the first 10 Google Apps for Enterprise Partners worldwide and initial contributor to the Google Apps Open Source provisioning tool kit, SADA Systems, Inc. has developed a proven track record in successful implementations of Google Apps solutions. SADA works closely with its clients to create custom, leading edge solutions that strategically meet their business and institutional objectives., companyurl: www.sadasystems.com, productdesc: At SADA, we not only resell Google Apps, but use Google Apps internally for collaboration along with the GData API to develop migration tools. We utilize App Engine to host custom applications, all of which allow us to more efficiently develop custom products for our clients such as our Single Sign On (SSO) tool, User Provisioning, On-premise and hosted Sync Tools., companylogo: sada.png, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, Google APIs, App Engine, Social Web, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ic954'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/idnpl</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 136</title><content type='text'>companyname: Safari Books Online, companylocation: Sebastopol, California, companydesc: Safari Books Online is an on-demand digital library that provides searchable, online access to the full content of thousands of books, training videos and pre-published manuscripts from the world's leading authors and publishers. For one low monthly price, Safari Books Online delivers access to the most current and critical technology, digital media and business titles, as well as time-saving tools that make it easy to organize information and personalize your learning experience., companyurl: www.safaribooksonline.com, productdesc: To deliver an improved mobile reading experience, we are implementing HTML5 features such as local storage for storing offline books and CSS transitions., companylogo: safaribooksonline.png, companypod: Chrome, companytags: Chrome, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/idnpl'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/i3tqm</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 137</title><content type='text'>companyname: Salesforce.com, companylocation: San Francisco, California, companydesc: Salesforce.com is an enterprise cloud computing company. Based on Salesforce.com's real-time, multitenant architecture, the company's platform and CRM applications have revolutionized the way companies collaborate and communicate with their customers., companyurl: www.salesforce.com, productdesc: The Force.com Toolkit for Google Data APIs provides a set of tools and services that developers can use to take advantage of Google Data APIs from within Force.com. The Force.com for Google App Engine library enables you to access the Force.com platform from Google App Engine Apps - Cloud to Cloud. Salesforce.com has done recent prototyping with Google Wave APIs, and the company also offers Google Apps and Google Adwords integration., companylogo: salesforce.png, companypod: Wave, companytags: Wave, Google APIs, App Engine, Enterprise, adddate: 4/25/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/i3tqm'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/i58b3</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 138</title><content type='text'>companyname: Samsung, companylocation: San Jose, California, companydesc: Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. is a global leader in semiconductor, telecommunication, digital media and digital convergence technologies with 2009 consolidated sales of US$116.7 billion. Recognized as one of the fastest growing global brands, Samsung Electronics is a leading producer of digital TVs, memory chips, mobile phones and TFT- LCDs., companyurl: www.samsung.com, productdesc: As a member of Open Handset Alliance, Samsung develops mobile phones based on Android for markets across the world. Including the recently announced Samsung Galaxy S., companylogo: samsung.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/i58b3'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/g2s5e</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 139</title><content type='text'>companyname: SAP, companylocation: Palo Alto, California, companydesc: As a leading provider of business software, SAP delivers products and services that help accelerate business innovation for our customers. Today, customers in more than 120 countries run SAP applications -- from distinct solutions addressing the needs of small businesses and midsize companies to suite offerings for global organizations., companyurl: www.sap.com, companylogo: sap.png, companypod: Wave, companytags: Wave</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/g2s5e'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/i81fx</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 140</title><content type='text'>companyname: Seesmic, companylocation: San Francisco, California, companydesc: Seesmic has become one of the most popular Twitter and Facebook clients that allow users to easily access their social networks in one application and successfully manage their online presence. From web to mobile or email to chat, Seesmic looks to be the gateway to all your social services on any online platform., companyurl: www.seesmic.com, productdesc: Seesmic is available on Android, taking advantage of the unique features of the mobile platform, thus making a powerful, yet nevertheless simple and easy to use application. Seesmic also relies on Google Web Toolkit as the main foundation technology for its rich and appreciated web application: Seesmic Web., companylogo: seesmic.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, GWT, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/i81fx'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ikojm</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 141</title><content type='text'>companyname: SGN, companylocation: Palo Alto, California, companydesc: SGN is a publisher of mobile social games that emphasize console-quality graphics and social engagement., companyurl: www.sgn.com, productdesc: Android Platform technologies used: NDK r3 based game engine; fully support android multi-tasking, resuming right in the middle of a multiplayer game; OpenGL ES 1.1 graphics; high detailed terrain and models, water effects; AudioPool sound system bridge from NDK to JAVA Classes; and Linux polling and sockets for multiplayer., companylogo: sgn.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ikojm'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/im343</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 142</title><content type='text'>companyname: SheepDog Inc., companylocation: Halifax, Nova Scotia, Canada, companydesc: SheepDog, like its namesake, is reliable, loyal, protective and highly trained to manage the heart of business today: information and connectivity. SheepDog facilitates migration projects to the Google Apps environment as well as showing clients how to fully leverage the most valuable and powerful aspects of the Google cloud., companyurl: www.sheepdoginc.ca, productdesc: Gtrax is an application that is built on App Engine with Google Web Toolkit. Its key advantage is that it has been designed to tightly integrate with Google Apps APIs so that it simplifies use. It's fully integrated with OpenID, MVP design pattern, command design pattern, and DI design pattern. , companylogo: sheepdog.png, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, App Engine, GWT, Google APIs, Social Web, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/im343'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/inhog</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 143</title><content type='text'>companyname: shopkick Inc., companylocation: Palo Alto, California, companydesc: shopkick turns the physical retail world into an interactive world for consumers, through the use of their cell phones. Its first app is CauseWorld - the first app that lets you do good deeds simply for walking into a store. Sponsors like Citibank and Kraft Foods provide donation money; consumers decide where it goes., companyurl: www.shopkick.com, productdesc: The CauseWorld mobile application runs on the Google Android platform., companylogo: shopkick.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/inhog'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/iow8x</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 144</title><content type='text'>companyname: ShufflePoint, companylocation: Newark, Delaware, companydesc: ShufflePoint transforms Web Analytics data into PowerPoint, Excel or Google Gadgets. We provide powerful solutions for Web Business Analysts that eliminate tedious cut-and-paste work so they can instead spend their time creating business value., companyurl: www.shufflepoint.com, productdesc: We use the Google Analytics API to retrieve data used for report generation. We also use the Google Visualization API and gadgets to create web dashboards., companylogo: shufflepoint.png, companypod: Google APIs, companytags: Google APIs, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/iow8x'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/if29y</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 145</title><content type='text'>companyname: Skytap, companylocation: Seattle, Washington, companydesc: Skytap a leading provider of self-service cloud automation solutions for dynamic workloads. Skytap enables users to run enterprise apps unchanged in the cloud, collaborate securely with global teams, and gain unparalleled business productivity. IT organizations can use Skytap for application development, testing, virtual training, ERP migration and sales demonstration projects and reduce costs by up to 70%., companyurl: www.skytap.com, productdesc: Skytap uses Google Analytics APIs and Google Apps as its OpenID identity provider., companylogo: skytap.png, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, Social Web, Google APIs, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/if29y'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/igguf</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 146</title><content type='text'>companyname: SlideRocket, companylocation: San Francisco, California, companydesc: SlideRocket is reinventing presentations with its feature rich, innovative platform that lets you create, manage, share and measure your presentations in one complete and integrated application., companyurl: www.sliderocket.com, productdesc: SlideRocket uses Google Apps API's to provide seamless integration between Google Docs and SlideRocket. We use: Google's user provisioning API for integrating accounts; the Apps licensing API and federated login (OpenID + OAuth) for enabling single sign-on; the Google Docs read/write API for importing dynamic tables, charts and presentation from Google Docs to SlideRocket; and the Contacts read/write API for integrating Google Contacts into SlideRocket., companylogo: sliderocket.png, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, Google APIs, Social Web, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/igguf'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ihves</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 147</title><content type='text'>companyname: Smartsheet, companylocation: Bellevue, Washington, companydesc: Smartsheet provides an online collaboration tool used by thousands of small businesses and teams in larger corporations for project and task management, sales pipeline management, crowdsourcing and other types of work management., companyurl: www.smartsheet.com, productdesc: Smartsheet enables single sign in for Googe Apps and Google Accounts using Google Account Authentication. Smartsheet uses the Google Documents List Data API to enable customers to attach Google Docs to any task and the Google Spreadsheets Data API for import/export between Smartsheet and Google spreadsheets. We also use the Google Gadgets API for our Smartsheet iGoogle gadgets., companylogo: smartsheet.png, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, Google APIs, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ihves'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ij9z9</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 148</title><content type='text'>companyname: SnapABug, companylocation: Huntsville, Alabama, companydesc: The SnapABug Help widget reduces companies QA and support cycle. SnapABug can easily be embedded on any website and provides all the information necessary to debug the situation quickly, including a snapshot of the remote visitor webpage. SnapABug live also lets you chat with your websites visitors while they browse, and does all this with no software install., companyurl: www.snapabug.com, productdesc: SnapABug is a 100% Google App Engine Java application. It interfaces with several Google services such as Google Talk and Google Maps API. SnapABug also relies on Google Web Toolkit as the technology behind its Widget Configurator user interface., companylogo: snapabug.png, companypod: App Engine, companytags: App Engine, Geo, GWT, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ij9z9'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ivx4q</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 149</title><content type='text'>companyname: Socialwok, companylocation: Singapore, companydesc: Voiceroute Pte Ltd is the company behind Socialwok, a feed-based, business, social networking service that help thousands of small and medium businesses to collaborate on Google Apps. Socialwok is the winner of the Techcrunch 2009 demopit award., companyurl: www.socialwok.com, productdesc: Socialwok is a Google App Engine Java application that is tightly integrated with Google Apps using Google Data APIs. Our user interface uses Google Web Toolkit., companylogo: socialwok.png, companypod: App Engine, companytags: App Engine, Enterprise, Google APIs, GWT, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ivx4q'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ixbp7</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 150</title><content type='text'>companyname: Sony Ericsson, companylocation: Lund, Sweden, companydesc: Sony Ericsson is a 50:50 joint venture by Sony and Ericsson established in October 2001, with global corporate functions located in London and operations in all major markets. Sony Ericsson vision is to become the industry leader in Communication Entertainment; where new styles of communicating through the internet and social media, become entertainment. Sony Ericsson offers exciting consumer experiences through phones, accessories, content and applications., companyurl: www.sonyericsson.com, productdesc: As one of the leading OEMs of Android phones, Sony Ericsson makes use of Android code management and review tools built around git, including Google-created gerrit and repo tools. Sony Ericsson uses the Android SDK and related tools, as well as creating new additions to Android which are in many cases contributed to the Android platform., companylogo: sonyericsson.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ixbp7'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/iyq9k</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 151</title><content type='text'>companyname: Spanning, companylocation: Austin, Texas, companydesc: Spanning extends the Google Apps collaboration and messaging suite. Spanning Sync 3 syncs both Google Calendar with Apple iCal and Google Contacts with the OS X Address Book. Spanning Backup for Google Apps is a new cloud-based application that continually backs up Google Calendar, Contacts, and Docs., companyurl: www.spanning.com, productdesc: Our products use many of the Google Data APIs, including those for Calendar, Contacts, Docs, Spreadsheets, and Provisioning. Plus, we use Google Apps, Groups, Analytics, Feedburner, YouTube, and Picasa Web Albums to run our business., companylogo: spanningsync.png, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, Google APIs, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/iyq9k'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/j04u1</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 152</title><content type='text'>companyname: Spiral Universe, companylocation: White Plains, New York, companydesc: Spiral is a powerful information management system and learning platform used by schools and colleges in 60 countries around the world. Spiral uses the power of modern technologies to improve the learning experience and provide valuable tools to school administrators, teachers, students, and parents. Our mission is to bring the best information technology to all schools regardless of their means., companyurl: www.spiraluniverse.com, productdesc: Spiral is one of the largest GWT-based applications ever built, offering hundreds of tools for school administrators, teachers, students, and parents through a cloud-based webtop user interface. We recommend Chrome to our users because of its speed and support for HTML5 features used in our system., companylogo: spiraluniverse.png, companypod: GWT, companytags: GWT, Chrome, adddate: 4/25/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/j04u1'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/iqav2</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 153</title><content type='text'>companyname: Springpad, companylocation: Charlestown, Massachusetts, companydesc: Springpad is a free web app that gives you many ways to save and access anything you want to remember. It automatically organizes and enhances the data you've stored with useful links and offers to save you time and money., companyurl: www.springpadit.com, productdesc: Springpad was built from the ground up using Google Web Toolkit. Springpad also uses Google's AJAX api's (search, maps, local, gcal), and OpenID/OAuth. An Android application is in the works., companylogo: springpad.png, companypod: GWT, companytags: GWT, Google APIs, Social Web, Android, Geo, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/iqav2'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/irpfj</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 154</title><content type='text'>companyname: Square, companylocation: San Francisco, California, companydesc: Square is focused on bringing immediacy, transparency, and approachability to the world of payments: an inherently social interaction each of us participates in daily., companyurl: www.squareup.com, productdesc: Android features used: Intent API for 3rd party developers; background processing; and notifications., companylogo: square.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/irpfj'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/iuikd</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 155</title><content type='text'>companyname: StudyBlue, companylocation: Madison, Wisconsin, companydesc: StudyBlue is a student-driven study network. Students using our services cut their study time dramatically while performing better, consistently, with less stress regardless of proficiency. We offer class and subject-specific content coupled with sophisticated tools that provide real-time adaptive feedback into the most effective methods of learning and retention., companyurl: www.studyblue.com, productdesc: Our website is built entirely with Google Web Toolkit (GWT). GWT allows for complete AJAX integration without sacrificing usability or integration capabilities. Our system architecture enables rapid evolution and adaptation to changing user expectations/needs, and delivery/consumption alternatives., companylogo: studyblue.png, companypod: GWT, companytags: GWT, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/iuikd'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/j75o2</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 156</title><content type='text'>companyname: The Huffington Post, companylocation: New York, New York, companydesc: The Huffington Post is a leading social news and opinion site, which in four and a half years has become an influential media brand -- "The Internet Newspaper." The site offers coverage of politics, media, business, entertainment, living, style, sustainable “green” living, world news, technology, and comedy, and is a top destination for news, blogs and original content., companyurl: www.huffingtonpost.com, productdesc: We use a number of Google products, including Google Apps for messaging and collaboration, Google Analytics for web trends, and the Search and Trends APIs in our CMS. Our website lets users sign in via Google Friend Connect, Google Site Search powers searches on our website, and we've built a HuffPost Google gadget and Android app. We're using the YouTube Video Uploader to help cover citizen journalism and allow our community to participate. HuffPost content is also featured on Google’s Fast Flip that is integrated within Google News pages., companylogo: huffingtonpost.png, companypod: Google APIs, companytags: Google APIs, Enterprise, Social Web, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/j75o2'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/j8k8j</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 157</title><content type='text'>companyname: The New York Times, companylocation: New York, New York, companydesc: The New York Times Company includes The New York Times, the International Herald Tribune, The Boston Globe, 15 other daily newspapers and more than 50 web sites, including NYTimes.com, Boston.com and About.com. The Company’s core purpose is to enhance society by creating, collecting and distributing high-quality news, information and entertainment., companyurl: www.nytimes.com, productdesc: The New York Times is using the latest in HTML5 to advance our online products, including video, Application Cache, DOM storage, and advanced CSS3 features. The result is exciting new Desktop-class apps that will run great on mobile phones, Chrome, and the forthcoming Chrome OS., companylogo: nytimes.png, companypod: Chrome, companytags: Chrome, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/j8k8j'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jbddd</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 158</title><content type='text'>companyname: TheDeadline, companylocation: Hamburg, Germany, companydesc: TheDeadline is an intelligent Todo-Manager. Adding and tagging todos is as easy as writing a Twitter post. TheDeadline provides a novel way to share todos fast and easy with co-workers to collaborate in small and large projects. An integrated artificial intelligence gives status updates, asks for decisions and automatically re-submits overdue todos in a smart way without annoying the user., companyurl: the-deadline.appspot.com, productdesc: We are using Google App Engine and Google Closure. Integration with Google Apps will be available by the time of Google I/O 2010., companylogo: thedeadline.png, companypod: App Engine, companytags: App Engine, Enterprise, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jbddd'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/j1jee</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 159</title><content type='text'>companyname: Thermopylae Sciences and Technology, companylocation: Arlington, Virginia, companydesc: Thermopylae Sciences + Technology is non-traditional services and software company that harnesses new and emerging concepts and technologies to rapidly deliver solutions to customers in Federal/DoD/commercial sectors. These specific solutions include products like iSpatial and iHarvest, as well as custom solution development built specifically around a customer or problem set., companyurl: www.t-sciences.com, productdesc: Thermopylae uses the Google Maps API, Earth API, Google Earth Enterprise, as well as the Android SDK in both our iSpatial &amp; UBIQUITY products and within our custom solution development efforts for customers like the Secretary of State, US State Department and US Army, SOUTHCOM for Haiti Relief effort., companylogo: tsciences.png, companypod: Geo, companytags: Geo, Android, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/j1jee'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/j2xyv</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 160</title><content type='text'>companyname: Thumbplay, companylocation: New York, New York, companydesc: Thumbplay, a leading provider of mobile entertainment in the U.S., has built an award-winning service centered on delivering millions of pieces of mobile content to 95 percent of U.S. devices among every major carrier. Thumbplay’s latest offering is Thumbplay Music, a next generation, cloud-based music service that delivers millions of songs on-demand to smartphones and PCs/Macs., companyurl: www.thumbplay.com, productdesc: Thumbplay Music is delivering cloud-based access to millions of songs via Android and soon via Chrome OS using HTML5., companylogo: thumbplay.png, companypod: Chrome, companytags: Chrome, Android, adddate: 4/25/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/j2xyv'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/j4cj8</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 161</title><content type='text'>companyname: TimeBridge Inc., companylocation: Berkeley, California, companydesc: TimeBridge is an easy-to-use web app that helps busy professionals schedule and run great meetings across companies and calendaring systems. TimeBridge helps you quickly find a time to meet, add a phone or web conference, and collaborate on the agenda, action items, meeting documents and notes., companyurl: www.timebridge.com, productdesc: TimeBridge created extensions to Calendar and Wave, using GData and OpenID/oAuth; and supports Google Apps Marketplace with Universal Navigation integration that allows for the enablement of whole domains by administrators. Our web app fully supports Calendar and Contact integration for seamless experience and Single Sign-on., companylogo: timebridge.png, companypod: Wave, companytags: Wave, Google APIs, Social Web, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/j4cj8'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jie7e</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 162</title><content type='text'>companyname: TribalDDB London, companylocation: London, United Kingdom, companydesc: We are a full service digital agency based in London. Our approach to digital communications is invention, we invent based on human insight, we build and produce never-seen-before digital experiences which enthral, excite, provoke action and emotion, thereby providing new ways for people to engage with our clients' brands., companyurl: blogs.tribalddb.co.uk, productdesc: We use the Google Maps API to produce compelling geo-aware Web applications., companylogo: tribalddb.png, companypod: Geo, companytags: Geo, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jie7e'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jjsrv</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 163</title><content type='text'>companyname: TripIt, companylocation: San Francisco, California, companydesc: TripIt helps people organize and share their travel plans no matter where they book. Travelers simply forward their travel confirmation emails from over 1,000 sites to plans@tripit.com and TripIt automatically creates a master itinerary that combines all their travel plans in one place plus weather, maps, restaurants and more, and can be accessed anytime online or through a mobile device.  , companyurl: www.tripit.com, productdesc: We use Open Social for our LinkedIn app, we use the Android Software Development Kit for our Android app, and we use Google Geo APIs for maps and directions in our trip itineraries., companylogo: tripit.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, Social Web, Geo, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jjsrv'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jl7c8</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 164</title><content type='text'>companyname: Trulia, companylocation: San Francisco, California, companydesc: Trulia is a real estate site focused on empowering you with smarter tools to help you find the right home. Whether you are an active buyer, seller or real estate enthusiast, Trulia gives you all the information you care about, from rich, property data to a personalized search experience. Trulia brings together local information, community insights, market data and national listings all in one place., companyurl: www.trulia.com, productdesc: We use the Google Maps API to enrich Trulia’s search result pages and residential real estate property pages., companylogo: trulia.png, companypod: Geo, companytags: Geo, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jl7c8'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jcrxq</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 165</title><content type='text'>companyname: TweakerSoft, companylocation: Torino, Italy, companydesc: TweakerSoft originated from more than a decade of software development in CAD/CAM, graphics and mobile applications. They specialize in the development of innovative Mac and iPhone software., companyurl: www.tweakersoft.com, productdesc: Our mobile application, AroundMe, uses the Google Maps API and Local Search API. AroundMe is also available for Android devices., companylogo: tweakersoft.png, companypod: Google APIs, companytags: Google APIs, Android, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jcrxq'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/je6i7</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 166</title><content type='text'>companyname: TweetDeck, companylocation: London, United Kingdom, companydesc: TweetDeck is a leading browser for the real-time and social web, allowing users to connect with Twitter, Facebook, LinkedIn and MySpace. Our advanced user interface gives you more power in managing your social stream across desktop and mobile platforms. , companyurl: www.tweetdeck.com, productdesc: Our upcoming product is being developed on Android and we're also using AppEngine to power various parts of our backend infrastructure. In addition, we consume a variety of APIs: Google Analytics for traffic monitoring, the Visualization API for internal statistics tracking systems, and the Social Graph API to help model the social web., companylogo: tweetdeck.png, companypod: App Engine, companytags: App Engine, Android, Google APIs, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/je6i7'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jfl2k</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 167</title><content type='text'>companyname: Twilio, companylocation: San Francisco, California, companydesc: Twilio provides a web-service API for businesses to build scalable, reliable communication apps that make and receive phone calls and and send and receive SMS messages., companyurl: www.twilio.com, productdesc: Twilio uses the Google Wave API to build a robot extension called twiliobot that enables users to make and receive phone calls from inside Google Wave. Calls are recorded, transcribed, and posted back to the wave., companylogo: twilio.png, companypod: Wave, companytags: Wave, adddate: 4/22/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jfl2k'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jgzn1</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 168</title><content type='text'>companyname: Ubisoft, companylocation: San Francisco, California, companydesc: Ubisoft is a leading producer, publisher and distributor of interactive entertainment products worldwide and has grown considerably through a strong and diversified line-up of products and partnerships. Ubisoft is present in 28 countries and has sales in more than 55 countries around the globe., companyurl: www.ubisoft.com, productdesc: Ubisoft is using Google App Engine to host TickTock and other future social games the company is developing., companylogo: ubisoft.png, companypod: App Engine, companytags: App Engine, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jgzn1'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jtmqq</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 169</title><content type='text'>companyname: UnaWave, companylocation: Los Angeles, California, companydesc: UnaWave is a simple and elegant work management application that works on top of Google Wave and fully leverages its rich real time collaboration and communications framework.  UnaWave enables managers, team leaders, and team members to easily assign, track and report on work status, reducing the complexity, cost and effort required to manage short term and long term work assignments., companyurl: www.unawave.com, productdesc: We're using Google Web Toolkit, OpenSocial Gadgets, and the Google Wave real-time communications and collaboration platform to enable customers to create, assign, share and report on tasks for team work-assignments of all types of durations., companylogo: unawave.png, companypod: Wave, companytags: GWT, Wave, Social Web, adddate: 4/25/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jtmqq'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jv1b7</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 170</title><content type='text'>companyname: Unity, companylocation: San Francisco, California, companydesc: Unity Technologies is an emerging market leader in mobile and online 3D technology. It's flagship product Unity is revolutionizing the game industry and beyond, delivering great power, workflows and platform reach.
, companyurl: www.unity3d.com, productdesc: Unity Android enables developers to create multiplatform 3D games and experiences, while also allowing them to harness the specific strengths of the individual hardware and OS platform., companylogo: unity.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jv1b7'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jxug1</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 171</title><content type='text'>companyname: Ushahidi, companylocation: Orlando, Florida, companydesc: The Ushahidi Platform allows anyone to gather distributed data via SMS, email or web and visualize it on a map or timeline. Our goal is to create the simplest way of aggregating information from the public for use in crisis response., companyurl: www.ushahidi.com, productdesc: We've built an Android-based mobile app that syncs up with our web service; we use Google Maps to display geo-tagged locations and media in our open source platform; and we use Google Geocoding web service to geo-tag text messages in our open source platform., companylogo: ushahidi.png, companypod: Geo, companytags: Geo, Android, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jxug1'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jo0h2</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 172</title><content type='text'>companyname: VendAsta, companylocation: Saskatoon, Saskatchewan, Canada, companydesc: VendAsta is sowing trust by making social context portable. With our applications StepRep (for small businesses) and MashedIn (for bloggers and website owners), the networks you've built up on Facebook, Twitter, etc. can extend to you and your social connections all over the web., companyurl: www.vendasta.com, productdesc: We use App Engine to host our core products. We leverage Open Social, Maps, and Social Graph API in our products. In addition, VendAsta uses Google Apps and Analytics extensively for running its core business. VendAsta is the developer of the open source library asynctools, which allows developers to perform App Engine API calls in parallel, most notably datastore queries., companylogo: vendasta.png, companypod: App Engine, companytags: App Engine, Social Web, Google APIs, Geo, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jo0h2'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jpf1j</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 173</title><content type='text'>companyname: Voxeo, companylocation: Orlando, Florida, companydesc: Voxeo unlocks the value of communications with open standards, disruptive innovation and a passion for problem solving. More than 100,000 developers, 45,000 companies and half of the Fortune 100 use Voxeo to deliver speech-enabled inbound and outbound IVR, call control, conferencing, and SIP-based VoIP applications, including multi-channel applications that span voice, SMS, IM, the mobile web and social networking., companyurl: www.voxeo.com/GoogleIO, productdesc: Voxeo's collaboration and communication platforms can be tightly integrated with Google technologies. Build and deploy rich multi-modal communications applications on Google App Engine. Organize a conference call within Google Wave, then call in with your phone or participate directly from your browser. Embed collaboration and web meeting spaces into any Google Friend Connect site. Or use Google Talk to interact with your users through any application., companylogo: voxeo.png, companypod: Social Web, companytags: Social Web, App Engine, Wave, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jpf1j'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jqtlw</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 174</title><content type='text'>companyname: Walk Score, companylocation: Seattle, Washington, companydesc: Walk Score measures the walkability of any address and through integrations with real estate sites helps millions of homebuyers find a walkable place to live.  We believe walkable neighborhoods are one of the simplest and most effective solutions to halt climate change, improve our health, and strengthen our communities., companyurl: www.walkscore.com, productdesc: The Walk Score API on Google App Engine serves 3 million Walk Scores a day to thousands of real estate partner sites. We also use Google Maps, Google AJAX APIs for geocoding and local search, Django on App Engine to host our site City-Go-Round.com, and we are developing a Transit API and Transit Score on App Engine using public GTFS data from transit agencies around the world., companylogo: walkscore.png, companypod: App Engine, companytags: App Engine, Geo, Google APIs, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/jqtlw'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/js86d</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 175</title><content type='text'>companyname: wave.to, companylocation: Bangor, North Wales, United Kingdom, companydesc: wave.to integrates existing products and services into the Google Wave platform. We're a small dedicated development team who have been involved in extending the platform since its announcement and have integrated Google Wave into social networking, instant messaging, CRM platforms, mobile devices and e-mail. Our e-mail platform Mr-Ray won the Judges Choice award in Mashable's Google Wave API Challenge., companyurl: www.wave.to, productdesc: We use a mixture of Google App Engine and the V8 javascript engine (node.js) to host our services that communicate with the Google Wave servers using the robots and gadget APIs. We are developing clients for our services using the Android SDK to extend them beyond desktop browsers., companylogo: waveto.png, companypod: Wave, companytags: Wave, App Engine, Android, adddate: 4/25/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/js86d'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/f52je</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 176</title><content type='text'>companyname: WebFilings, companylocation: Los Altos, California, companydesc: WebFilings delivers a revolution in collaboration software for regulatory compliance — providing the only end-to-end solution to meet SEC reporting requirements. Our intuitive user interface integrates word processing and spreadsheet editing capabilities into a single, rich internet application - streamlining the entire reporting process with features and document controls fine-tuned to the needs of SEC reporting professionals. WebFilings helps companies reduce the time, risk and costs associated with creating and filing SEC reports., companyurl: www.webfilings.com, productdesc: WebFilings uses web services built on the App Engine python SDK. Our use of App Engine and its datastore provides our customers a secure, reliable and scalable platform for their mission-critical SEC report management process., companylogo: webfilings.png, companypod: App Engine, companytags: App Engine, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/f52je'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/f7vo8</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 177</title><content type='text'>companyname: WHERE, companylocation: Boston, Massachusetts, companydesc: WHERE is a leading local search and recommendation service. WHERE puts the best local information at users’ finger tips with real-time reviews and special offers from local merchants. WHERE is available on over one hundred mobile devices and a leading application on all major smartphone platforms and carriers., companyurl: www.where.com, productdesc: We're using the Android SDK to build the WHERE mobile application for Android. , companylogo: where.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/f7vo8'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/f9a8p</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 178</title><content type='text'>companyname: WithWaves, companylocation: Seattle, Washington, companydesc: WithWaves is the exploration of Google Wave utilizing technology developed under the Streamd.in umbrella. WithWaves is a small team of developers focusing on providing simple collaborative applications and tools. We have developed http://streamd.in, amazon.withwaves.com, ebay.withwaves.com and run the withwaves.com blog, all of them with support to run standalone and as gadgets in the Google Wave ecosystem., companyurl: www.withwaves.com, productdesc: We use Google Wave to deploy our robot and gadgets and App Engine to host most of them. We also use the Google Maps API V.3 in our latest project http://streamd.in., companylogo: withwaves.png, companypod: Wave, companytags: Wave, App Engine, Geo, adddate: 4/22/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/f9a8p'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ezg9q</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 179</title><content type='text'>companyname: WorkSmart Labs, companylocation: New York, New York, companydesc: The WorkSmart Labs mission is to use technology to make fitness more motivating and effective. We make CardioTrainer mobile wellness software on the Android, as well as provide many gym entertainment solutions., companyurl: www.worksmartlabs.com, productdesc: We are using the Android SDK and a large set of other Google technologies (Protocol Buffers, Build Tools, KML, etc) to create our mobile applications and website., companylogo: worksmartlabs.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/ezg9q'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/f0uu7</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 180</title><content type='text'>companyname: WOT, companylocation: Helsinki, Finland, companydesc: Web of Trust is a community-based safe surfing tool that uses an intuitive traffic-light style rating system to help you avoid risky sites when you search, browse and shop online., companyurl: www.mywot.com, productdesc: We develop extensions for Google Chrome., companylogo: wot.png, companypod: Chrome, companytags: Chrome, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/f0uu7'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/f29ek</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 181</title><content type='text'>companyname: Yahoo! Inc., companylocation: Sunnyvale, California, companydesc: Yahoo! Inc. offers a robust set of developer tools, APIs, and resources through the Yahoo! Developer Network., companyurl: www.yahoo.com, productdesc: The Yahoo! Application Platform (YAP) provides an OpenSocial container on the Yahoo! homepage and is the largest user of the Google Caja project. Yahoo! uses iGoogle as a canvas to publish Yahoo! user updates through its Updates API and integrates numerous open Google APIs and feeds within the Yahoo! Query Language (YQL). Yahoo! is a charter member of the OpenSocial Foundation, on the Board of OpenID, and a key contributor to the OAuth spec., companylogo: yahoo.png, companypod: Social Web, companytags: Social Web, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/f29ek'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/f3nz1</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 182</title><content type='text'>companyname: Yelp, companylocation: San Francisco, California, companydesc: Yelp is a website that connects people with great local businesses in the US, Canada, UK and Ireland.  Yelpers have written more than 10 million local reviews, making Yelp a local guide for real word-of-mouth on everything from boutiques and mechanics to restaurants and dentists.
, companyurl: www.yelp.com, productdesc: Yelp for Android helps you find great businesses around you.  Using location services, Google Maps, shared Intents and a host of other features in the Android SDK, the app delivers a simple-yet-powerful Yelp experience on Android devices.
, companylogo: yelp.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, Geo, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/f3nz1'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/fgb2q</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 183</title><content type='text'>companyname: Zillow, companylocation: Seattle, Washington, companydesc: Zillow.com is an online real estate marketplace where homeowners, buyers, sellers, renters, real estate agents and mortgage professionals find and share vital information about homes and mortgages.
, companyurl: www.zillow.com, productdesc: Zillow.com uses Google Maps in our mobile applications, including our Android application. Zillow.com uses Google Street View on our main website as well as in our Android application, companylogo: zillow.png, companypod: Android, companytags: Android, Geo, adddate: 5/3/2010</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/fgb2q'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/fhpn7</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 184</title><content type='text'>companyname: Zoho, companylocation: Pleasanton, California, companydesc: Zoho offers a broad suite of Online Business, Productivity &amp; Collaboration Applications for Small and Medium Organizations. , companyurl: www.zoho.com, productdesc: We use a number of Google products, including Google Web Toolkit. We also build extensions for Chrome, solutions for Google Apps, OpenSocial gadgets, and Google OpenID/OAuth., companylogo: zoho.png, companypod: Enterprise, companytags: Enterprise, GWT, Social Web, Chrome, adddate: x</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od5/public/basic/fhpn7'/></entry></feed>