<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?><feed xmlns='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom' xmlns:openSearch='http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearchrss/1.0/' xmlns:gsx='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006/extended'><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>sessions</title><link rel='alternate' type='text/html' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/pub?key=t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw'/><link rel='http://schemas.google.com/g/2005#feed' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic'/><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic'/><author><name>christine.lee</name><email>christine.lee@gmail.com</email></author><openSearch:totalResults>82</openSearch:totalResults><openSearch:startIndex>1</openSearch:startIndex><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/cokwr</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 2</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 10:45am-11:45am, room: 6, product: Android, track: Android, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: A beginner's guide to Android, tags: Android, Mobile, Java, sessionspeakers: Reto Meier, speakers: retomeier, sessionabstract: This session will introduce some of the basic concepts involved in Android development. Starting with an overview of the SDK APIs available to developers, we will work through some simple code examples that explore some of the more common user features including using sensors, maps, and geolocation., sessionrequirements: Proficiency in Java and a basic understanding of embedded environments like mobile phones , sessionlink: beginners-guide-android, sessionhashtag: #android1, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.45, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252B-Xhdu7ZkBHw, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252B-Xhdu7ZkBHw, waveid: w+-Xhdu7ZkBHw</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/cokwr'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/ckd7g</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 3</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 12:30pm-1:30pm, room: 6, product: Android, track: Android, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Writing real-time games for Android redux, tags: Android, Mobile, Java, Games, 2D, 3D, C++, sessionspeakers: Chris Pruett, speakers: pruett, sessionabstract: This session is a crash course in Android game development: everything you need to know to get started writing 2D and 3D games, as well as tips, tricks, and benchmarks to help your code reach optimal performance.  In addition, we'll discuss hot topics related to game development, including hardware differences across devices, using C++ to write Android games, and the traits of the most popular games on Market., sessionrequirements: Proficiency in Java and a solid grasp of Android's fundamental concepts, sessionlink: writing-real-time-games-android, sessionhashtag: #android2, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.9B, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BWDgRyLZkaR, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BWDgRyLZkaR, waveid: w+WDgRyLZkaR</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/ckd7g'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/clrrx</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 4</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 1:45pm-2:45pm, room: 6, product: Android, track: Android, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: The world of ListView, tags: Android, Mobile, Java, sessionspeakers: Romain Guy, Adam Powell, speakers: romainguy, adamp, sessionabstract: ListView is one of the most widely used Android widgets but also the most complex one. Join us to learn how to master ListView and learn all about its features, optimizations, quirks and limitations.
, sessionrequirements: Proficiency in Java and a solid grasp of Android's fundamental concepts, sessionlink: world-of-listview-android, sessionhashtag: #android3, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.47, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252Bv7BXJrZkBJT, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252Bv7BXJrZkBJT, waveid: w+v7BXJrZkBJT</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/clrrx'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/d180g</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 5</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 3:00pm-4:00pm, room: 6, product: Android, track: Android, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Casting a wide net: how to target all Android devices, tags: Android, Mobile, Java, sessionspeakers: Justin Mattson, speakers: jmatt, sessionabstract: One of Android's strengths is its flexibility to run on a wide variety of devices. In this session, we will explore the facilities the Android resource system provides to developers to make supporting many devices from one application binary easier, as well as common pitfalls. In addition to hardware heterogeneity, more than one version of Android may exist in the wild at any given time. We will go over strategies for providing cross-version compatibility., sessionrequirements: Proficiency in Java and a solid grasp of Android's fundamental concepts, sessionlink: casting-wide-net-android-devices, sessionhashtag: #android4, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.48, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BfZ2urbZk7o, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BfZ2urbZk7o, waveid: w+fZ2urbZk7o</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/d180g'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/d2mkx</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 6</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 4:15pm-5:15pm, room: 6, product: Android, track: Android, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Android UI design patterns, tags: Android, Mobile, Java, sessionspeakers: Chris Nesladek, German Bauer, Richard Fulcher, Christian Robertson, Jim Palmer, speakers: cnesladek, germanb,  rfulcher, robertsonc, jimpalmer, sessionabstract: In this session, the Android User Experience team will show the types of patterns you can use to build a great Android application. We'll cover things like how to use Interactive Titlebars, Quick Contacts, and Bottom bars as well some new patterns which will get an I/O-only preview. The team will be also available for a no holds barred Q&amp;A session., sessionrequirements: Proficiency in Java and a solid grasp of Android's fundamental concepts, sessionlink: android-ui-design-patterns, sessionhashtag: #android5, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.49, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252Be6j2obZkP1, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252Be6j2obZkP1, waveid: w+e6j2obZkP1</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/d2mkx'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/cssly</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 7</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 10:15am-11:15am, room: 6, product: Android, track: Android, sessiontype: 301, sessiontitle: Developing Android REST client applications, tags: Android, Mobile, Java, sessionspeakers: Virgil Dobjanschi, speakers: virgild, sessionabstract: This session will present architectural considerations for developing RESTful applications on the Android platform. It focuses on design patterns, platform integration and performance issues specific to the Android platform.
, sessionrequirements: Advanced knowledge of Java &amp; Android concepts, sessionlink: developing-RESTful-android-apps, sessionhashtag: #android6, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.6C, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252Be6j2obZkNc, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252Be6j2obZkNc, waveid: w+e6j2obZkNc</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/cssly'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/cu76f</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 8</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 11:30am-12:30pm, room: 6, product: Android, track: Android, sessiontype: 301, sessiontitle: A JIT Compiler for Android's Dalvik VM, tags: Android, Mobile, Java, sessionspeakers: Ben Cheng, Bill Buzbee, speakers: bccheng, buzbee, sessionabstract: In this session we will outline the design of a JIT Compiler suitable for embedded Android devices. Topics will include an architectural overview, the rationale for design decisions and the special support for JIT verification, testing and tuning., sessionrequirements: Advanced knowledge of Java &amp; Android concepts, sessionlink: jit-compiler-androids-dalvik-vm, sessionhashtag: #android7, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.6D, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252Be6j2obZkRw, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252Be6j2obZkRw, waveid: w+e6j2obZkRw</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/cu76f'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/cvlqs</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 9</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 10:45am-11:45am, room: 3, product: App Engine, track: App Engine, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Appstats - RPC instrumentation and optimizations for App Engine, tags: App Engine, Python, Java, sessionspeakers: Guido van Rossum, speakers: guido, sessionabstract: Appstats is a pure userland library (for Python and Java) that inserts instrumentation hooks into the App Engine runtime at the interface between the runtime and services like the datastore. The collected statistics can be browsed in a rich UI which allows drilling down to various levels of detail. The talk will also discuss common optimizations to address typical findings., sessionrequirements: Intermediate knowledge of App Engine (Python or Java), sessionlink: appstatsrpc-appengine, sessionhashtag: #appengine1, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.4A, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BeRiTZrZkC22, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BeRiTZrZkC22, waveid: w+eRiTZrZkC22</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/cvlqs'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/dcgjs</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 10</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 4:45pm-5:45pm, room: 3, product: App Engine, track: App Engine, sessiontype: 301, sessiontitle: Next gen queries, tags: App Engine, Datastore, Query, Cursor, Zigzag Merge Join, sessionspeakers: Alfred Fuller, speakers: arfuller, sessionabstract: This session will discuss the design and implications of improvements to the Datastore query engine including support for AND, OR and NOT query operators, the solution to exploding indexes and paging backwards with Cursors. Specific technologies discussed will be an improved zigzag merge join algorithm, a new extensible multiquery framework (with geo-query support) and a smaller more versatile Cursor design., sessionrequirements: Intermediate knowledge of Google App Engine, specifically the datastore., sessionlink: next-gen-queries-appengine, sessionhashtag: #appengine10, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.71, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BY_40V7ZkB3Z, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BY_40V7ZkB3Z, waveid: w+Y_40V7ZkB3Z</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/dcgjs'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/ddv49</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 11</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 4:15pm-5:15pm, room: 3, product: App Engine, track: App Engine, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Data migration in App Engine, tags: App Engine, Data Migration, sessionspeakers: Matthew Blain, speakers: mblain, sessionabstract: Learn about the App Engine bulk loader and see an example of migrating data from an external data source into the app engine datastore--and back out. Do you have data stored in a traditional, relational DB which you'd like to upload to App Engine? This session will teach you how., sessionrequirements: Basic knowledge of Google App Engine and database concepts., sessionlink: data-migration-appengine, sessionhashtag: #appengine4, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.4D, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BeRiTZrZkC29, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BeRiTZrZkC29, waveid: w+eRiTZrZkC29</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/ddv49'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/d415a</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 12</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 11:30am-12:30pm, room: 3, product: App Engine, track: App Engine, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: What's hot in Java for App Engine, tags: App Engine, Java, sessionspeakers: Toby Reyelts, Don Schwarz, speakers: tobyr, schwardo, sessionabstract: Learn what's new with Java on App Engine. We'll take a whirlwind tour through the changes since last year, walk through a code sample for task queues and the new blobstore service, and demonstrate techniques for improving your application's performance. We'll top it off with a glimpse into some new features that we've planned for the year ahead., sessionrequirements: Intermediate knowledge of App Engine for Java, sessionlink: whats-hot-in-java-for-app-engine, sessionhashtag: #appengine6, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.6E, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BO4sGNLZkCGh, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BO4sGNLZkCGh, waveid: w+O4sGNLZkCGh</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/d415a'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/d5fpr</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 13</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 1:00pm-2:00pm, room: 3, product: App Engine, track: App Engine, sessiontype: 301, sessiontitle: Building high-throughput data pipelines with Google App Engine, tags: App Engine, Data processing, Mapping on data, sessionspeakers: Brett Slatkin, speakers: bslatkin, sessionabstract: This session will cover how to build, test, and maintain large-scale data pipelines on Google App Engine. It will cover maximizing efficiency, productionization, and how to deal with changing requirements., sessionrequirements: Advanced knowledge of Google App Engine, sessionlink: high-throughput-data-pipelines-appengine, sessionhashtag: #appengine7, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.6F, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BO4sGNLZkCHO, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BO4sGNLZkCHO, waveid: w+O4sGNLZkCHO</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/d5fpr'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/df9om</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 14</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 3:30pm-4:30pm, room: 3, product: App Engine, track: App Engine, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Testing techniques for Google App Engine, tags: App Engine, Unit Testing, sessionspeakers: Max Ross, speakers: maxr, sessionabstract: Google App Engine is designed to help developers more easily create and manage scalable web applications. But what about testing?  We typically write tests under the assumption that our development stack closely resembles our production stack, so what do we do when our target environment only lives in the cloud?  In this talk, we will highlight the key differences between typical testing techniques and Google App Engine testing techniques.  We will also present concrete strategies for testing against local and cloud-based implementations of App Engine services like the datastore and the task queue.  Finally, we will explain how to use App Engine as a highly parallel test harness that runs existing test suites without modification., sessionrequirements: Intermediate knowledge of Google App Engine and unit testing concepts., sessionlink: testing-techniques-app-engine, sessionhashtag: #appengine9, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.70, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BeRiTZrZkCzy, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BeRiTZrZkCzy, waveid: w+eRiTZrZkCzy</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/df9om'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/dgo93</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 15</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 10:45am-11:45am, room: 5, product: Chrome Dev Tools, track: Chrome, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Google Chrome's Developer Tools, tags: Chrome, sessionspeakers: Pavel Feldman, Anders Sandholm, speakers: pfeldman, sandholm, sessionabstract: In this session we'll give an overview of Developer Tools for Google Chrome that is a part of the standard Chrome distribution. Chrome Developer Tools allow inspecting, debugging and tuning the web applications and many more. In addition to this overview we would like to share some implementation details of the Developer Tools features and call for your contribution., sessionrequirements: Web developer background, sessionlink: chrome-developer-tools, sessionhashtag: #chrome1, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.4E, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252Bv_K9zbZkBY_, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252Bv_K9zbZkBY_, waveid: w+v_K9zbZkBY_</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/dgo93'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/djhdx</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 16</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 12:30pm-1:30pm, room: 5, product: Chrome, track: Chrome, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Beyond JavaScript: programming the web with native code, tags: Chrome, Native Client, sessionspeakers: Dave Springer, Ian Lewis, speakers: dspringer, ilewis, sessionabstract: Although JavaScript performance is rapidly increasing, there are still applications for which native code is a better choice. Learn about Native Client and how you can use it to build rich applications with all of the advantages and power of the web., sessionlink: native-code-chrome, sessionhashtag: #chrome2, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.4F, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252Be6j2obZkKS, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252Be6j2obZkKS, waveid: w+e6j2obZkKS</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/djhdx'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/dyxo8</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 17</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 3:00pm-4:00pm, room: 5, product: Chrome OS, track: Chrome, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Developing With HTML5, tags: HTML5, Chrome, Chrome OS, sessionspeakers: Mihai Ionescu, Arne Roomann-Kurrik, speakers: mihai, kurrik, sessionabstract: This session covers the HTML5 APIs available to Google Chrome and Google Chrome OS applications and Google Chrome extensions. Learn how to design web applications for a Google Chrome OS netbook using the latest web technologies., sessionrequirements: Familiarity with HTML and JavaScript, sessionlink: developing-with-html5, sessionhashtag: #chrome3, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.51, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BQ9WoGLZkBlw, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BQ9WoGLZkBlw, waveid: w+Q9WoGLZkBlw</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/dyxo8'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/c4wx5</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 18</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 1:00pm-2:00pm, room: 5, product: Chrome, track: Chrome, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Chrome Extensions - how-to, tags: Chrome, Chrome Extensions, sessionspeakers: Brian Kennish, speakers: bkennish, sessionabstract: Google Chrome shipped an extensions API in version 4.0. Since last year, new capabilites have been added to the extensions framework, and many people have already written powerful extensions with minimal effort. Find out how to write an extension, and what's coming next in Chrome Extensions., sessionrequirements: Familiarity with HTML and JavaScript, sessionlink: chrome-extensions, sessionhashtag: #chrome6, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.72, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BetojYbZkBGj, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BetojYbZkBGj, waveid: w+etojYbZkBGj</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/c4wx5'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/drwu7</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 19</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 2:15pm-3:15pm, room: 5, product: Google Chrome Frame, track: Chrome, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Using Google Chrome Frame, tags: HTML5, Chrome, Chrome Frame, sessionspeakers: Alex Russell, speakers: slightlyoff, sessionabstract: Google Chrome Frame brings the HTML5 platform and fast Javascript performance to IE6, 7 &amp; 8. This session will cover the latest on Google Chrome Frame, what it can do for you and your customers, how it can be used, and a sneak peak into what's planned next., sessionrequirements: Web developer backgrounds, as well as enterprise IT, sessionlink: using-chrome-frame, sessionhashtag: #chrome7, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.73, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252B9PNCdLZkBxY, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252B9PNCdLZkBxY, waveid: w+9PNCdLZkBxY</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/drwu7'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/dtbek</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 20</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 4:45pm-5:45pm, room: 5, product: Chrome, track: Chrome, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: HTML5 status update, tags: HTML5, Chrome, sessionspeakers: Ian Fette, Jeff Chang, speakers: ifette, jeffreyc, sessionabstract: Where is HTML5 today? What new features are now broadly supported, what features are on the horizon, and what features are on the chopping block? How do we decide what to implement, what to propose, and what to drop? Find out., sessionrequirements: None, sessionlink: html5-status-chrome, sessionhashtag: #chrome8, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.75, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252B9PNCdLZkBxf, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252B9PNCdLZkBxf, waveid: w+9PNCdLZkBxf</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/dtbek'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/dupz1</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 21</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 10:45am-11:45am, room: 8, product: Apps Marketplace, Enterprise, track: Enterprise, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Reach new customers fast: Learn how to sell your cloud app on the Google Apps Marketplace, tags: Enterprise, Google Apps, Customization, Apps Marketplace, ISV, SaaS, sessionspeakers: Scott McMullan, Jay Simmons (Atlassian), Chuck Dietrich (Sliderocket), Amit Kulkarni (Manymoon), speakers: scottmc, sessionabstract: In this introductory session we'll provide an overview of the Google Apps Marketplace and learn product and marketing best practices directly from 3 Marketplace ISVs., sessionrequirements: None, sessionlink: reach-new-customers-apps-marketplace, sessionhashtag: #enterprise1, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.52, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BkrgNvLZkBkL, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BkrgNvLZkBkL, waveid: w+krgNvLZkBkL</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/dupz1'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/e35dj</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 22</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 12:30pm-1:30pm
, room: 4, product: Enterprise, track: Enterprise, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Making Freemium work - converting free users to paying customers, tags: Enterprise, Monetization, Google Apps, SaaS, VC, sessionspeakers: Don Dodge (moderator), Brad Feld, Dave McClure, Jeff Clavier, Matt Holleran, Joe Kraus, speakers: dondodge, sessionabstract: A panel of prominent venture capital leaders will help you understand how to build free apps that can be upgraded to paid &amp; how to build products that can be profitable., sessionrequirements: None, sessionlink: freemium-vc-panel-enterprise, sessionhashtag: #enterprise2, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.53, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BY_40V7ZkB7J, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BY_40V7ZkB7J, waveid: w+Y_40V7ZkB7J</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/e35dj'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/e4jxw</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 23</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 1:45pm-2:45pm, room: 5, product: Apps Marketplace, Enterprise, track: Enterprise, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Integrating your app with the Google Apps Marketplace: Navigation, SSO, Data APIs and manifests, tags: Enterprise, SSO, APIs, Apps Marketplace, ISV, SaaS, sessionspeakers: Ryan Boyd, Steve Bazyl, speakers: ryanboyd, sbazyl, sessionabstract: In this fast-paced, demo-focused session, you'll learn how to build, integrate, and sell a web app on the Google Apps Marketplace.  We'll go end-to-end in 40 minutes with time left for Q&amp;A., sessionrequirements: None, sessionlink: integrating-cloud-app-with-google-apps, sessionhashtag: #enterprise3, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.54, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BTeHZ97ZkBAg, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BTeHZ97ZkBAg, waveid: w+TeHZ97ZkBAg</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/e4jxw'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/e5yid</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 24</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 3:00pm-4:00pm, room: 7, product: Enterprise, track: Enterprise, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Customizing Google Apps &amp; integrating with customer environments, tags: Enterprise, Google Apps, Customization, sessionspeakers: Mike O'Brien, Matt Pruden (Appirio), Adam Graff (Genentech), Don Dodge (moderator), sessionabstract: Learn from real life examples of customizing Google Apps to meet customer requirements. Hear from the customer (Genentech) and the System Integrator (Appirio). Explore integration issues and deployment best practices with people who have done it. Get your questions answered in this session., sessionrequirements: None, sessionlink: customizing-google-apps-partners-customers, sessionhashtag: #enterprise4, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.55, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BSVy-sLZkBYe, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BSVy-sLZkBYe, waveid: w+SVy-sLZkBYe</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/e5yid'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/cg5gh</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 25</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 11:30am-12:30pm, room: 4, product: Docs API, Sites API, Secure Data Connector, SDC, track: Enterprise, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Connecting your enterprise applications with Google Docs and Sites, tags: Enterprise, Docs API, Sites API, Apps, Google Data APIs, Secure Data Connector, SDC, sessionspeakers: Eric Bidelman, Vijay Bangaru, Matthew Tonkin (Memeo Inc), speakers: ericbidelman, vijayb
, sessionabstract: Learn how your organization can harness the power of Google Docs and Sites directly from within your existing enterprise systems using our extensive APIs. Integrate with data from behind the firewall using Secure Data Connector. Upload, share, collaborate, and sync any file to Docs. Even automate the creation of project and team workspaces in a single click in Sites from within your CRM., sessionrequirements: Knowledge of Google Data APIs and top-level understanding of Docs and Sites, sessionlink: connecting-enterprise-apps-docs-sites, sessionhashtag: #enterprise6, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.77, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252Bo01RhLZkBGa, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252Bo01RhLZkBGa, waveid: w+o01RhLZkBGa</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/cg5gh'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/eilm2</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 26</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 2:15pm-3:15pm, room: 4, product: Enterprise, track: Enterprise, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Launch your app inside of Google Apps with gadgets, tags: Gadgets, Enterprise, Google Apps, Gmail, Calendar, Sites, sessionspeakers: Dan Holevoet, speakers: danielholevoet, sessionabstract: Gadgets represent a valuable opportunity to get in front of the many Google Apps users who use Gmail, Google Calendar, and Google Sites throughout the day. This session will talk about how you can write gadgets as natural extensions of your existing products and take advantage of the unique opportunities available to gadgets in Google Apps., sessionrequirements: Basic familiarity with gadgets and/or HTML/JS., sessionlink: launch-your-app-google-apps-gadgets, sessionhashtag: #enterprise7, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.78, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BSVy-sLZkBX4, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BSVy-sLZkBX4, waveid: w+SVy-sLZkBX4</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/eilm2'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/ek06j</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 27</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 3:30pm-4:30pm, room: 4, product: Google Apps Script, track: Enterprise, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Scripting Google Apps for business process automation, tags: Apps Script, Enterprise, Google Apps, Spreadsheets, Calendar, Sites, Document List, sessionspeakers: Evin Levey, speakers: evin, sessionabstract: Learn how to use Google Apps for business process automation, and custom work-flow. We'll introduce the powerful scripting service along with several easy-to-use interfaces including Spreadsheets, Calendar, Sites and the Document List. We'll also demonstrate interoperability with third party web services and showcase exciting new developments in Google Apps Script., sessionrequirements: Basic knowledge of Google Apps, and an interest in learning how to automate processes using scripts., sessionlink: scripting-google-apps-for-business-process-automation, sessionhashtag: #enterprise8, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.79, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252Bv7BXJrZkBOq, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252Bv7BXJrZkBOq, waveid: w+v7BXJrZkBOq</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/ek06j'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/eleqw</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 28</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 4:45pm-5:45pm, room: 4, product: Enterprise, Google Apps, track: Enterprise, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Building context-aware extensions for Gmail - Deep dive on Gmail contextual gadgets, tags: Enterprise, Google Apps, Gadgets, Gmail, ISV, SaaS, sessionspeakers: Dan Holevoet, speakers: danielholevoet, sessionabstract: How much time do your users spend in email everyday? Wouldn't it be nice if you could seamlessly integrate your apps into the rich context offered by their email and allow them to avoid shifting to new applications for various tasks? Gmail contextual gadgets allow you to register regular expressions and insert gadgets into e-mail messages based on their content. In this session, you'll learn how to create and distribute these powerful gadgets., sessionrequirements: Basic familiarity with gadgets and/or HTML/JS., sessionlink: deep-dive-gmail-contextual-gadgets, sessionhashtag: #enterprise9, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.7A, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252B9PNCdLZkBt_, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252B9PNCdLZkBt_, waveid: w+9PNCdLZkBt_</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/eleqw'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/eedwv</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 29</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 12:30pm-1:30pm, room: 3, product: App Engine, track: Enterprise, App Engine, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: ​Run corporate applications on Google App Engine?  Yes we do., tags: ​Enterprise, SaaS, PaaS, Hosting, App Engine, Java, sessionspeakers: Ben Fried, Irwin Boutboul, Justin McWilliams, Matthew Simmons, speakers: bf, irwin, ogle, mpsimmon , sessionabstract: Come hear Google's CIO Ben Fried and his team of engineers describe how Google builds real-world applications on App Engine. If you're interested in building corporate applications that run on Google's cloud, this team has been doing exactly that using App Engine, SDC, GWT, Django, Closure, Google Analytics, Bulkloader, cron server, and friends. In this session, you'll hear usable recipes for uniting Google's cloud technologies with firewalls, legacy databases, proprietary servers, legacy systems, and other realities in the life of an IT developer and learn how these teams have been able to respond more quickly to business needs while reducing operational burden. , sessionrequirements: None, sessionlink: run-corp-apps-on-app-engine, sessionhashtag: #appengine2, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.4B, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252Bo01RhLZkBJ0, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252Bo01RhLZkBJ0, waveid: w+o01RhLZkBJ0</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/eedwv'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/efsh8</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 30</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 1:45pm-2:45pm, room: 3, track: Enterprise, App Engine, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: ​It’s 2010: How is your move to the cloud doing?, tags: ​Enterprise, Saas, Paas, Hosting, App Engine, Google Apps, Java, sessionspeakers: David Glazer, speakers: dglazer, sessionabstract: ​Come discover the latest innovations from Google enabling IT and ISV developers to build on Google’s cloud-based storage and computing offerings. This talk will give a complete overview of Google’s commercial developer products and provide insights and best practices so enterprise developers can take more advantage of the cloud., sessionrequirements: None, sessionlink: its-2010-move-to-the-cloud, sessionhashtag: #appengine3, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.4C, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BtaQlR7ZkBIS, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BtaQlR7ZkBIS, waveid: w+taQlR7ZkBIS</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/efsh8'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/eh71p</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 31</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 10:15am-11:15am, room: 1, product: Auth, Google Data Protocol, OpenID, SSO, track: Enterprise, Google APIs, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: OpenID-based single sign on and OAuth data access for Google Apps, tags: Authentication, Google Data APIs, OAuth, AuthSub, Enterprise, OpenID, SSO, sessionspeakers: Ryan Boyd, David Primmer, speakers: ryanboyd, primmer, sessionabstract: A discussion of all the auth tangles you've encountered so far -- OpenID, SSO, 2-Legged OAuth, 3-Legged OAuth, and Hybrid OAuth.  We'll show you when and where to use the APIs, code some example apps, and demonstrate how they all integrate with Google APIs and other developer products. We'll also talk about how these technologies relate to apps sold on the Google Apps Marketplace., sessionrequirements: None, sessionlink: untangling-auth-enterprise, sessionhashtag: #enterprise5, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.76, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BY_40V7ZkB0w, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BY_40V7ZkB0w, waveid: w+Y_40V7ZkB0w</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/eh71p'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bwhin</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 32</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 4:45pm-5:45pm, room: 6, product: Android, track: Fireside Chats, Android, sessiontype: Fireside Chat, sessiontitle: Fireside chat with the Android team, tags: Android, Mobile, Java, sessionspeakers: The Android team with Chris DiBona moderating, sessionabstract: Pull up a chair and join the Android team at Google for a fireside chat. It's your opportunity to ask us about the platform and to tell us where you'd like to see it go in the future., sessionlink: fireside-chat-android-team, sessionhashtag: #fireside-android, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.93, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252Bv7BXJrZkBPC, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252Bv7BXJrZkBPC, waveid: w+v7BXJrZkBPC</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bwhin'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bxw30</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 33</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 1:00pm-2:00pm, room: 8, product: Android, track: Fireside Chats, Android, sessiontype: Fireside Chat, sessiontitle: Fireside chat with Android handset manufacturers, tags: Android, Mobile, Java, OHA, Open Handset Alliance, sessionspeakers: Dino Brusco (Motorola), Erik Hellman (Sony Ericsson), Joon Kang (LGE), Ciaran Rochford (Samsung), Eric Chu (Google; moderator), sessionabstract: Come join us for a fireside chat with the top Android handset manufacturers. Hear about the types of devices being planned for 2010 and get your device-specific questions answered., sessionlink: fireside-chat-android-handset-manufacturers, sessionhashtag: #fireside-androidhandset, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.92, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BQhu3aLZknM, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BQhu3aLZknM, waveid: w+Qhu3aLZknM</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bxw30'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bv2y6</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 34</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 3:00pm-4:00pm, room: Fireside Chat Room, product: App Engine, track: Fireside Chats, App Engine, sessiontype: Fireside Chat, sessiontitle: Fireside chat with the App Engine team, tags: App Engine, sessionspeakers: Brett Slatkin, Guido van Rossum, Matt Blain, Max Ross, Don Schwarz, Alfred Fuller, Kevin Gibbs, Sean Lynch
, speakers: bslatkin, guido, mblain, maxr, schwardo, arfuller, kgibbs, slynch, sessionabstract: It's been an busy year for the App Engine team with lots of new features and lots of new developers.  Come tell us about what you've loved and what still bugs you. With several members of the App Engine team on deck, you'll get the answers to your questions straight from the source., sessionlink: fireside-chat-app-engine, sessionhashtag: #fireside-appengine, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.6A, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252B9PNCdLZkBuX, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252B9PNCdLZkBuX, waveid: w+9PNCdLZkBuX</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bv2y6'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/etu5e</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 35</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 1:45pm-2:45pm, room: Fireside Chat Room, product: Chrome, Chrome OS, track: Fireside Chats, Chrome, sessiontype: Fireside Chat, sessiontitle: Fireside chat with the Google Chrome and Chrome OS teams, tags: Chrome, Chrome OS, sessionspeakers: Ian Fette, Brian Rakowski, Linus Upson, Caesar Sengupta, Matt Papakipos, speakers: ifette, brakowski, linus, caesars, papakipos, sessionabstract: Curious about what's new in Google Chrome, or what makes Google Chrome OS so exciting? We'll talk briefly about the major developments over the past year, and then field questions from the audience. If you're dying to know something, this is the place to find an answer., sessionlink: fireside-chat-chrome-chrome-os, sessionhashtag: #fireside-chrome, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.69, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252B1g8YLbZkBFj, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252B1g8YLbZkBFj, waveid: w+1g8YLbZkBFj</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/etu5e'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/ceqw0</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 36</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 4:15pm-5:15pm, room: Fireside Chat Room, product: Enterprise, Apps Marketplace, track: Fireside Chats, Enterprise, sessiontype: Fireside Chat, sessiontitle: Fireside chat with the Enterprise team, tags: Enterprise, Google Apps, Apps Marketplace, sessionspeakers: Chris Vander Mey, Scott McMullan, Ryan Boyd, David Glazer, Ken Lin, speakers: cvandermey, scottmc, dglazer, ryanboyd, kenlin, sessionabstract: With the launch of the Google Apps Marketplace, we've introduced a new way to expose your software to businesses - and a new way to extend Google Apps.  If you're interested in building apps, what we're thinking about, or if you have other questions about the Marketplace, pull up a chair., sessionlink: fireside-chat-enterprise-apps, sessionhashtag: #fireside-enterprise, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.6B, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252B1g8YLbZkBBh, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252B1g8YLbZkBBh, waveid: w+1g8YLbZkBBh</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/ceqw0'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/cdcbn</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 37</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 12:30pm-1:30pm, room: Fireside Chat Room, product: Geo, track: Fireside Chats, Geo, sessiontype: Fireside Chat, sessiontitle: Fireside chat with the Geo team, tags: Geo, Earth, Maps, Maps API, Maps Data API, Earth API, sessionspeakers: Thor Mitchell, Peter Birch, Matt Holden, Ben Appleton, Bart Locanthi, Thatcher Ulrich, speakers: thor, pbirch, mholden, appleton, bnl, tulrich, sessionabstract: Here's your opportunity to pick the brains of the people behind the Maps, Earth, and Maps Data APIs! We'll take a quick walk through the milestones of the last year, and then open it up to your questions. Don't miss your opportunity to get the straight scoop on all that's new in the world of Google Geo APIs., sessionlink: fireside-chat-geo, sessionhashtag: #fireside-geo, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.67, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BY_40V7ZkB74, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BY_40V7ZkB74, waveid: w+Y_40V7ZkB74</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/cdcbn'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/ev8pv</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 38</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 11:30am-12:30pm, room: Fireside Chat Room, product: GWT, track: Fireside Chats, GWT, sessiontype: Fireside Chat, sessiontitle: Fireside chat with the GWT team, tags: GWT, Google Web Toolkit, Java, JavaScript, AJAX, sessionspeakers: Bruce Johnson, Joel Webber, Ray Ryan, Amit Manjhi, Jaime Yap, Kathrin Probst, Eric Ayers, speakers: bruce, jgw, rjrjr, amitmanjhi, jaimeyap, kprobst, zundel, sessionabstract: If you're interested in what the GWT team has been up to since 2.0, here's your chance. We'll have several of the core engineers available to discuss the new features and frameworks in GWT, as well as to answer any questions that you might have., sessionlink: fireside-chat-gwt, sessionhashtag: #fireside-gwt, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.91, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BQhu3aLZknM, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BQhu3aLZknM, waveid: w+Qhu3aLZknM</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/ev8pv'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/ewna8</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 39</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 2:15pm-3:15pm, room: Fireside Chat Room, product: Social, Open Web, Buzz, track: Fireside Chats, Social Web, sessiontype: Fireside Chat, sessiontitle: Fireside chat with the Social Web team, tags: Social, Social Web, Buzz, sessionspeakers: David Glazer, DeWitt Clinton, John Panzer, Joseph Smarr, Sami Shalabi, Todd Jackson, speakers: dglazer, dewitt, jpanzer, jsmarr, shalabi, toddj, sessionabstract: Social is quickly becoming an integral part of how we experience the web, and this is your chance to pick the brains of the people who are working on Buzz, the Buzz API and the underlying open protocols such as Activity Streams and OAuth which are an essential component of a truly open &amp; social web., sessionlink: fireside-chat-social-web, sessionhashtag: #fireside-socialweb, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.94, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BY_40V7ZkB1C, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BY_40V7ZkB1C, waveid: w+Y_40V7ZkB1C</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/ewna8'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/ey1up</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 40</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 10:45am-11:45am, room: Fireside Chat Room, product: Google Wave, track: Fireside Chats, Wave, sessiontype: Fireside Chat, sessiontitle: Fireside chat with the Google Wave team, tags: Wave, sessionspeakers: Lars Rasmussen, Douwe Osinga, Jochen Bekmann, Alan Green, Pamela Fox, Dan Peterson, Stephanie Hannon, sessionabstract: Join the Google Wave team around the campfire to chat about all things Wave: the product, the API platform, and the wave federation protocol. Come to learn about the new Wave API features, get tips on how to build the best extensions, discuss how to take advantage of the open source code available and hear more about what users are doing with the product. This is an excellent opportunity to ask the engineering team questions directly, and learn more about where Wave is heading., sessionrequirements: None, sessionlink: fireside-chat-wave, sessionhashtag: #fireside-wave, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.9F, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BsErKcbZkjh.4, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BsErKcbZkjh.4, waveid: w+sErKcbZkjh.4</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/ey1up'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/epmg7</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 41</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 10:45am-11:45am, room: 4, product: Maps API, track: Geo, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Stepping up: Porting v2 JavaScript Maps API applications to v3, tags: Maps, Maps API, JavaScript, sessionspeakers: Daniel Lee, speakers: daniellee, sessionabstract: The JavaScript Maps API v3 is the future of the Google Maps API. To take advantage of the many great features coming to the API you will need to migrate existing v2 applications to v3. This session will guide you through the process, illustrating how easy it is to start reaping the benefits in features and performance., sessionrequirements: Experience developing applications with the Maps JavaScript API v2, sessionlink: v2-javascript-maps-api-v3, sessionhashtag: #geo1, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.56, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BU2jwj7ZkBfu, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BU2jwj7ZkBfu, waveid: w+U2jwj7ZkBfu</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/epmg7'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/c6bhi</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 42</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 1:45pm-2:45pm, room: 1, product: Maps API, track: Geo, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Map once, map anywhere: Developing geospatial applications for both desktop and mobile, tags: Maps, Maps API, Mobile, JavaScript, Geospatial, sessionspeakers: Mano Marks, speakers: mmarks, sessionabstract: As the number of desktop and mobile platforms proliferates the cost of developing and maintaining multiple versions of an application continues to increase. This session illustrates how the JS Maps API can be used to simplify cross platform geospatial application development by enabling a single implementation to be shared across multiple platforms, while maintaining a native look and feel., sessionrequirements: Web application development, sessionlink: map-once-map-anywhere-geospatial-apps, sessionhashtag: #geo2, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.57, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252Be6j2obZkOR, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252Be6j2obZkOR, waveid: w+e6j2obZkOR</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/c6bhi'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/cbxr6</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 43</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 4:15pm-5:15pm, room: 4, product: Maps Data API, track: Geo, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Unleash your map data: Cloud computing for geospatial applications, tags: Maps, Maps API, Data, Cloud, Geospatial, sessionspeakers: Tom Manshreck, speakers: shreck, sessionabstract: The Google Maps API made geospatial development accessible to all but hosting your data remains complex and time consuming. This session will detail the services Google offers for storing your geospatial data in the cloud, illustrate the ways in which that data can be accessed and visualized, and walk through development of a retail store finder using these technologies., sessionrequirements: Experience developing web based applications that search over or visualise geospatial data is helpful but not essential., sessionlink: unleash-map-data-cloud-computing-geospatial-apps, sessionhashtag: #geo4, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.58, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BTeHZ97ZkBDO, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BTeHZ97ZkBDO, waveid: w+TeHZ97ZkBDO</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/cbxr6'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/a59y2</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 44</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 11:30am-12:30pm, room: 9, product: SketchUp, Building Maker, 3D Warehouse, track: Geo, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: The SketchUp 3D API: Working with 3D geospatial data, tags: SketchUp, Building Maker, 3D Warehouse, 3D, sessionspeakers: Matt Lowrie, speakers: mlowrie, sessionabstract: The world is a three dimensional space. Your geospatial applications should be showing it that way. This session will show how to create 3D data in Building Maker and then use the SketchUp API to customize that data to fit your needs., sessionrequirements: Basic understanding of 3D is helpful, but not essential, sessionlink: sketchup-3d-api, sessionhashtag: #geo5, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.7B, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252Bv_K9zbZkBY1, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252Bv_K9zbZkBY1, waveid: w+v_K9zbZkBY1</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/a59y2'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/a6oij</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 45</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 2:15pm-3:15pm, room: 9, product: KML, Earth API, Maps Data API, Geospatial, 3D, track: Geo, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Mapping in 3D: Tips and tricks for Google Earth API and KML, tags: KML, Earth API, Maps Data API, Geospatial, 3D, sessionspeakers: Josh Livni, Mano Marks, speakers: jlivni, mmarks, sessionabstract: Google Earth and the Earth API can handle a tremendous amount of data. But you always have more. We will talk about integrating large datasets efficiently, coding for optimal performance, and taking advantage of advanced features in KML and the Earth API., sessionrequirements: Attendees should have a basic knowledge of Google Earth, and KML or Javascript.
, sessionlink: mapping-in-3d-earth-api-kml, sessionhashtag: #geo6, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.7C, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BQhu3aLZkgD, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BQhu3aLZkgD, waveid: w+Qhu3aLZkgD</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/a6oij'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/a832w</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 46</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 3:30pm-4:30pm, room: 1, product: Maps API, track: Geo, sessiontype: 301, sessiontitle: Moving beyond markers: Advanced Maps API customization, tags: Maps, Maps API, sessionspeakers: Jez Fletcher, David Day, speakers: jez, davidday, sessionabstract: With such a large number of Google Maps API sites online, it can be hard to make your site stand out from the crowd. This session covers ways in which you can enhance your Maps API application to truly differentiate it, including customizing your overlays, controls, and map., sessionrequirements: Experience developing applications with the Google Maps APIs, sessionlink: moving-beyond-markers-advanced-maps-api, sessionhashtag: #geo7, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.7D, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BTeHZ97ZkBCl, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BTeHZ97ZkBCl, waveid: w+TeHZ97ZkBCl</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/a832w'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/a9hnd</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 47</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 4:45pm-5:45pm, room: 1, product: Maps API, track: Geo, Tech Talks, sessiontype: Tech Talk, sessiontitle: How Maps API v3 came to be: Tips, tricks, and lessons learned in developing a cross platform desktop and mobile API, tags: Maps, Maps API, JavaScript, Mobile, sessionspeakers: Susannah Raub, Marc Ridey, speakers: sraub, mridey, sessionabstract: The Google JavaScript Maps API v3 celebrates its one year anniversary at this year's Google I/O. In this session, we reveal the reasons for embarking on a new API, the challenges we faced in developing a truly cross platform and cross device framework, and the lessons learned on the way., sessionrequirements: Experience developing desktop web based applications, and an interest in porting such applications to new mobile platforms.
, sessionlink: maps-api-v3-api, sessionhashtag: #geo8, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.7F, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BkrgNvLZkBmC, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BkrgNvLZkBmC, waveid: w+krgNvLZkBmC</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/a9hnd'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/akq6p</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 48</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 10:45am-11:45am, room: 2, product: AJAX APIs, track: Google APIs, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Bringing Google to your site, tags: AJAX APIs, Friend Connect, Ads APIs, Web Elements, Analytics, sessionspeakers: DeWitt Clinton, Jeff Scudder, speakers: dewitt, jscudder, sessionabstract: This is an overview session about some of the many ways that a developer can enrich their site and more fully engage their visitors using Google products. We will cover a variety of products and APIs designed to quickly and easily improve and monetize your site, from AdSense and Custom Search to Feeds and Web Elements. We'll include announcements for several eye-popping new features., sessionrequirements: Basic HTML and JavaScript familiarity, sessionlink: bringing-google-to-your-site-googleapis, sessionhashtag: #googleapis1, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.98, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252Bo01RhLZkBDwC, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252Bo01RhLZkBDwC, waveid: w+o01RhLZkBDwC</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/akq6p'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/aaw7q</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 49</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 1:45pm-2:45pm, room: 2, product: PowerMeter API, track: Google APIs, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Knowledge is (less) power: Exploring the Google PowerMeter API, tags: PowerMeter API, APIs, OAuth, Java, Python, Energy, sessionspeakers: Srikanth Rajagopalan, Rus Heywood, speakers: srikanth, rheywood, sessionabstract: In this session we will discuss interesting ways to make users understand and manage their home energy use through Google PowerMeter. The Google PowerMeter API currently available allows devices to integrate with Google PowerMeter.  Come learn how you can build with the API and about exciting developments ahead. We will dig into the implementation details for integrations and open up the floor for other ideas that may be relevant., sessionrequirements: Web developer background, hardware enthusiasts, sessionlink: google-powermeter-api, sessionhashtag: #googleapis2, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.59, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BQhu3aLZkkc, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BQhu3aLZkkc, waveid: w+Qhu3aLZkkc</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/aaw7q'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/acas7</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 50</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 4:15pm-5:15pm, room: 2, product: Google Charts Toolkit, Visualization API, Chartserver
, track: Google APIs, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Google Charts Toolkit: Google's new unified approach for creating dynamic charts on the web, tags: Charts, Toolkit, Visualization API, JavaScript, Images, Data source, sessionspeakers: Michael Fink, Amit Weinstein, speakers: fink, amitw, sessionabstract: Google Charts Toolkit is Google's unified approach for creating charts on the web. It provides a rich gallery spanning from pie charts to interactive heat-maps and from organizational trees to motion charts. The toolkit lets developers choose between JavaScript based client-side rendering and image based server-side rendering. We will present the relative strengths of these two approaches, and unveil the future visual design of Google Charts. , sessionrequirements: Basic knowledge of Google Visualization API and Google Charts API, sessionlink: google-charts-toolkit-googleapis, sessionhashtag: #googleapis4, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.5A, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BSVy-sLZkBX8, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BSVy-sLZkBX8, waveid: w+SVy-sLZkBX8</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/acas7'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/adpck</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 51</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 10:15am-11:15am, room: 2, product: Google Analytics API, track: Google APIs, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Google Analytics APIs: End to end, tags: Google Analytics, JavaScript, Java, Gadgets, Mobile, ga.js, Video, sessionspeakers: Nick Mihailovski, speakers: nm, sessionabstract: Google Analytics measures performance of your website. Learn advanced techniques on how to use our tracking, processing and data export APIs as we walk you through an example of creating a most visited pages web element for your website., sessionrequirements: Intermediate Knowledge of Google Analytics, Javascript, sessionlink: google-analytics-apis-end-to-end, sessionhashtag: #googleapis5, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.7E, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BtaQlR7ZkBF9, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BtaQlR7ZkBF9, waveid: w+taQlR7ZkBF9</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/adpck'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/af3x1</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 52</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 2:15pm-3:15pm, room: 2, product: YouTube API, track: Google APIs, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: YouTube API uploads: Tools, tips, and best practices, tags: Google Data APIs, Android, iPhone, YouTube, YouTube APIs, Mobile, sessionspeakers: Jeffrey Posnick, Gareth McSorley, Kuan Yong, speakers: jeffy, gmcsorley, kuanyong, sessionabstract: Are you integrating YouTube upload functionality into your mobile, desktop, or web app? Learn about Android and iPhone upload best practices, resuming interrupted YouTube uploads, and the YouTube Direct embeddable iframe for soliciting uploads on your existing web pages., sessionrequirements: Interest in adding YouTube upload functionality to mobile, desktop, or web-based applications, sessionlink: youtube-api-uploads, sessionhashtag: #googleapis7, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.80, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252Bo01RhLZkBHy, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252Bo01RhLZkBHy, waveid: w+o01RhLZkBHy</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/af3x1'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/auk5k</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 53</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 3:30pm-4:30pm, room: 2, product: Google APIs, track: Google APIs, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: How Google builds APIs, tags: APIs, Atom, JSON, Java, Python, sessionspeakers: Zach Maier, Joseph Schorr, Mark Stahl, speakers: zpm, jschorr, mstahl, sessionabstract: Dive into the API development process at Google, and discover how we routinely take our full-featured APIs from design to testing to production in less than an hour.  We'll present Google API design goals and best practices, showcase our new API infrastructure, and demonstrate how you can take advantage of the secret "power" features hiding in every Google API., sessionrequirements: A basic understanding of web APIs is helpful but not necessarily required, sessionlink: how-google-builds-apis, sessionhashtag: #googleapis8, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.81, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252B9rTSb7ZkBm1, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252B9rTSb7ZkBm1, waveid: w+9rTSb7ZkBm1</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/auk5k'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/avyq1</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 54</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 4:45pm-5:45pm, room: 2, product: AdSense for Mobile Apps, Google Analytics, track: Google APIs, Android, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Analyzing and monetizing your Android &amp; iPhone apps, tags: AdSense for Mobile Apps, Google Analytics, Android, Mobile, Java, sessionspeakers: Chrix Finne, Jim Kelm, speakers: chrix, kelm, sessionabstract: If you've got a great mobile app, you're likely interested to know how users interact with your app and how to build a business from it. In this session you'll learn how you can drive awareness and earn revenue for your app using AdSense for Mobile Apps.  We'll also discuss how using Google Analytics can help with your app development by providing insights into where your app users are coming from and how they're engaging with your app.  We'll share tips, tricks, and examples of real-world mobile apps that have found success., sessionrequirements: Attendees should have an existing iPhone or Android app, but not necessary. Familiarity and current account setup on AdSense and Google Analytics useful but not necessary, sessionlink: analyzing-monetizing-mobile-apps, sessionhashtag: #googleapis9, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.82, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BQ9WoGLZkBoo, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BQ9WoGLZkBoo, waveid: w+Q9WoGLZkBoo</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/avyq1'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/am4r2</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 55</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 10:45am-11:45am, room: 7, product: Google Web Toolkit, track: GWT, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Measure in milliseconds redux: Meet Speed Tracer, tags: GWT, Google Web Toolkit, AJAX, Speed Tracer, Chrome, Java, JavaScript, sessionspeakers: Kelly Norton, speakers: knorton, sessionabstract: It turns out that web apps can be slow for all sorts of opaque and unintuitive reasons. Don't be fooled into thinking that bloated, slow JavaScript is the only culprit. This session introduces you to Speed Tracer, a new GWT tool that can tell you exactly where time is going within the browser., sessionrequirements: Intermediate knowledge of Javascript and DOM concepts., sessionlink: measure-in-milliseconds-speed-tracer-gwt, sessionhashtag: #gwt1, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.5B, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BeRiTZrZkC3Z, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BeRiTZrZkC3Z, waveid: w+eRiTZrZkC3Z</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/am4r2'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/anjbj</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 56</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 12:30pm-1:30pm, room: 7, product: Google Web Toolkit, track: GWT, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Faster apps faster: Optimizing apps with the GWT Compiler, tags: GWT, Google Web Toolkit, AJAX, Eclipse, IDE, Java, JavaScript, sessionspeakers: Ray Cromwell, speakers: cromwellian, sessionabstract: The GWT compiler isn't just a Java to JavaScript transliterator. It performs many optimizations along the way. In this session, we'll show you not only the optimizations performed, but how you can get more out of the compiler itself. Learn how to speed up compiles, use -draftCompile, compile for only one locale/browser permutation, and more., sessionrequirements: Intermediate knowledge of Java, Google Web Toolkit, and compiler optimization strategies., sessionlink: faster-apps-faster-gwt-compiler, sessionhashtag: #gwt2, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.5C, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252B9rTSb7ZkBlL, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252B9rTSb7ZkBlL, waveid: w+9rTSb7ZkBlL</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/anjbj'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/aoxvw</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 57</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 1:45pm-2:45pm, room: 7, product: Google Web Toolkit, track: GWT, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Architecting for performance with GWT, tags: GWT, Google Web Toolkit, AJAX, Java, JavaScript, Enterprise, sessionspeakers: Joel Webber, Adam Schuck, speakers: jgw, schuck, sessionabstract: Modern web applications are quickly evolving to an architecture that has to account for the performance characteristics of the client, the server, and the global network connecting them. Should you render HTML on the server or build DOM structures with JS in the browser, or both? This session discusses this, as well as several other key architectural considerations to keep in mind when building your Next Big Thing., sessionrequirements: Intermediate knowledge of client/server relationships, Java, and Google Web Toolkit, sessionlink: architecting-performance-gwt, sessionhashtag: #gwt3, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.5D, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BQhu3aLZker, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BQhu3aLZker, waveid: w+Qhu3aLZker</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/aoxvw'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/aqcgd</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 58</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 4:15pm-5:15pm, room: 7, product: Google Web Toolkit, track: GWT, sessiontype: 301, sessiontitle: GWT Linkers target HTML5 Web Workers, Chrome Extensions, and more, tags: GWT, Google Web Toolkit, AJAX, Java, JavaScript, HTML5, sessionspeakers: Matt Mastracci, sessionabstract: At its core GWT has a well-defined and customizable mechanism -- called Linkers -- that controls exactly how GWT's compiled JavaScript should be packaged, served, and run. This session will describe how to create linkers and explains some of the linkers we've created, including a linker that turns a GWT module into an HTML5 Web Worker and one that generates an HTML App Cache manifest automatically., sessionrequirements: Advanced knowledge of Google Web Toolkit. Intermediate knowledge of Java., sessionlink: gwt-linkers-webworkers-extensions, sessionhashtag: #gwt4, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.5E, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BetojYbZkBEt, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BetojYbZkBEt, waveid: w+etojYbZkBEt</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/aqcgd'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/b4e4j</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 59</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 10:15am-11:15am, room: 7, product: Google Web Toolkit, track: GWT, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: GWT's UI overhaul: UiBinder, ClientBundle, and Layout Panels, tags: GWT, Google Web Toolkit, AJAX, Java, JavaScript, sessionspeakers: Joel Webber, Ray Ryan, speakers: jgw, rjrjr, sessionabstract: There have been some really huge improvements in GWT's UI fundamentals over the past year. We've introduced features such as UiBinder, ClientBundle, CssResource, and uber layout panels that allow you to build fast UIs in a sane manner. Come see how fun/easy/fast it can be to use these technologies in harmony to overhaul your UI., sessionrequirements: Intermediate knowledge of Google Web Toolkit., sessionlink: gwt-ui-overhaul, sessionhashtag: #gwt5, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.83, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BQ9WoGLZkBpL, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BQ9WoGLZkBpL, waveid: w+Q9WoGLZkBpL</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/b4e4j'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/b5sow</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 60</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 1:00pm-2:00pm, room: 7, product: Google Web Toolkit, track: GWT, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: GWT + HTML5 can do what?!, tags: GWT, Google Web Toolkit, AJAX, HTML5, Java, JavaScript, Enterprise, sessionspeakers: Joel Webber, Ray Cromwell, Stefan Haustein, speakers: jgw, cromwellian, haustein, sessionabstract: How can you take advantage of new HTML5 features in your GWT applications? In this session, we answer that question in the form of demos -- lots and lots of demos. We'll cover examples of how to use Canvas for advanced graphics, CSS3 features, Web Workers, and more within your GWT applications., sessionrequirements: Baseline knowledge of HTML5 as well as intermediate knowledge of Java and Google Web Toolkit, sessionlink: gwt-html5, sessionhashtag: #gwt6, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.84, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BetojYbZkBDR, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BetojYbZkBDR, waveid: w+etojYbZkBDR</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/b5sow'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/b779d</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 61</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 2:15pm-3:15pm, room: 7, product: Google Web Toolkit, track: GWT, sessiontype: 301, sessiontitle: GWT testing best practices, tags: GWT, Google Web Toolkit, AJAX, Testing, Java, JavaScript, sessionspeakers: Daniel Danilatos, speakers: danilatos, sessionabstract: GWT has a lot of little-publicized infrastructure that can help you build apps The Right Way: test-driven development, code coverage, comprehensive unit tests, and integration testing using Selenium or WebDriver. This session will survey GWT's testing infrastructure, describe some best practices we've developed at Google, and help you avoid common pitfalls., sessionrequirements: Advanced knowledge of Java, Google Web Toolkit, and current testing frameworks., sessionlink: gwt-continuous-build-testing, sessionhashtag: #gwt7, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.85, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BeRiTZrZkC31, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BeRiTZrZkC31, waveid: w+eRiTZrZkC31</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/b779d'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/axdae</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 62</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 3:30pm-4:30pm, room: 7, product: Google Web Toolkit, track: GWT, sessiontype: 301, sessiontitle: Architecting GWT applications for production at Google, tags: GWT, Google Web Toolkit, AJAX, Java, JavaScript, Enterprise, sessionspeakers: Ray Ryan, speakers: rjrjr, sessionabstract: For large GWT applications, there's a lot you should think about early in the design of your project. GWT has a variety of technologies to help you, but putting it all together can be daunting. This session walks you through how teams at Google architect production-grade apps, from design to deployment, using GWT., sessionrequirements: Advanced knowledge of Google Web Toolkit. Intermediate knowledge of design patterns and Java., sessionlink: architecting-production-gwt, sessionhashtag: #gwt8, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.86, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BeRiTZrZkC31, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BeRiTZrZkC31, waveid: w+eRiTZrZkC31</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/axdae'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/ayruv</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 63</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 12:30pm-1:30pm, room: 1, product: Social, OpenSocial, Social Web, track: Social Web, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: The open &amp; social web, tags: ActivityStrea.ms, Salmon, WebFinger, PubSubHubbub, PortableContacts, OpenID, OAuth, OpenSocial, sessionspeakers: Chris Messina, speakers: messina, sessionabstract: This session will cover the latest and most important trends of the Social Web and dive deep into where this is all going, at both technical and conceptual levels. From the concepts of digital identity, relationships, and social objects, this session will cover emerging technologies like WebFinger, Salmon, ActivityStrea.ms, OpenID, OAuth and OpenSocial., sessionrequirements: A web developer background and an interest in the social web., sessionlink: open-and-social-web, sessionhashtag: #googlesocial, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.5F, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BfZ2urbZk6F, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BfZ2urbZk6F, waveid: w+fZ2urbZk6F</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/ayruv'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/c7q1z</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 64</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 1:45pm-2:45pm, room: 8, product: Google Buzz APIs, track: Social Web, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: What's the hubbub about Google Buzz APIs?, tags: Buzz, ActivityStrea.ms, OpenID, Salmon, PubSubHubbub, OAuth, sessionspeakers: Chris Chabot, Loic Le Meur (Seesmic), Ming Yong (Socialwok), speakers: chabotc, sessionabstract: Google Buzz is a new way to share updates, photos, videos and more, and start conversations about the things you find interesting. In this session, we'll take a deep dive into building with the Buzz APIs and the open standards it uses, such as ActivityStrea.ms, PubSubHubbub, OAuth, Salmon and WebFinger., sessionrequirements: A web developer background and an interest in the social web, sessionlink: google-buzz-apis, sessionhashtag: #buzzapi, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.99, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252Bqlswu7ZkBSc, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252Bqlswu7ZkBSc, waveid: w+qlswu7ZkBSc</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/c7q1z'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/b06f8</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 65</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 3:00pm-4:00pm, room: 9, product: Social Web, Social, track: Social Web, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Bridging the islands: Building fluid social experiences across websites, tags: OpenID, OAuth, Portable Contacts, ActivityStrea.ms, Salmon, sessionspeakers: John Panzer, Joseph Smarr, speakers: jpanzer, jsmarr, sessionabstract: As more sites add social functionality, profiles, friends, and conversations are becoming increasingly fragmented and redundant. But an emerging collection of open technologies aim to help bridge these social islands, allowing users to seamlessly move between sites, bring their friends along, and have unified conversations that span multiple web sites. Come learn how OpenID, OAuth, Portable Contacts, ActivityStrea.ms, and Salmon can help you connect your site to the rest of the Social Web, increasing your traffic, engagement, and relevance to your users., sessionlink: building-fluid-social-experiences-across-websites, sessionhashtag: #islandsio, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.60, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BQhu3aLZkgi, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BQhu3aLZkgi, waveid: w+Qhu3aLZkgi</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/b06f8'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/b1kzp</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 66</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 4:15pm-5:15pm, room: 9, product: PubSubHubbub, track: Social Web, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Make your application real-time with PubSubHubbub, tags: PubSubHubbub, real-time, Atom, RSS, sessionspeakers: Brett Slatkin, speakers: bslatkin, sessionabstract: This session will go over how to add support for the PubSubHubbub protocol to your website. You'll learn how to turn Atom and RSS feeds into real-time streams. We'll go over how to consume real-time data streams and how to make your website reactive to what's happening on the web right now., sessionrequirements: Knowledge of web technologies (Atom, RSS, HTTP, HTML) and content-mangement systems (WordPress, etc)., sessionlink: real-time-apps-pubsubhubbub, sessionhashtag: #PuSHio, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.61, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BeRiTZrZkC0N, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BeRiTZrZkC0N, waveid: w+eRiTZrZkC0N</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/b1kzp'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/be856</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 67</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 10:15am-11:15am, room: 9, product: iGoogle, OpenSocial, track: Social Web, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: iGoogle developer portal and tools, tags: iGoogle, OpenSocial, OSDE, OpenSocial Development Environment, HTML, JavaScript, sessionspeakers: Shih-chia Cheng, Albert Cheng, speakers: shihchia, albertcheng, sessionabstract: Learn how to build and maintain better OpenSocial gadgets for iGoogle. Two major applications will be introduced. The first one is iGoogle Gadget Dashboard for managing gadgets created by you. The second one is OSDE (OpenSocial Development Environment) which is an Eclipse plugin for developers to easily implement gadgets., sessionrequirements: Knowledge of web technology such as HTML and JavaScript., sessionlink: igoogle-developer-portal, sessionhashtag: #igoogleio, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.87, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BkrgNvLZkBhk, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BkrgNvLZkBhk, waveid: w+krgNvLZkBhk</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/be856'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bfmpn</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 68</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 11:30am-12:30pm, room: 1, product: Google Buzz APIs, track: Social Web, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Surf the stream: Google Buzz, location, and social gaming, tags: Buzz, Social, mobile, HTML5, App Engine, sessionspeakers: Bob Aman, Timothy Jordan, speakers: bobaman, timothyjordan, sessionabstract: Google Buzz has a feature-rich API that allows you to do all kinds of interesting things with conversations and location. In this session we'll build a Buzz-tastic mobile game using App Engine, HTML5, and the Buzz API for social awesomeness. , sessionrequirements: Knowledge of Python, the web and a good spirited nature., sessionlink: surf-the-stream-google-buzz-social-gaming, sessionhashtag: #buzzbingo, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.88, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252Bo01RhLZkBJ6, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252Bo01RhLZkBJ6, waveid: w+o01RhLZkBJ6</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bfmpn'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bh1a0</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 69</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 4:45pm-5:45pm, room: 7, product: Social Web, Social, track: Social Web, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Where is the social web going next?, tags: ActivityStrea.ms, Salmon, WebFinger, PubSubHubbub, PortableContacts, OpenID, OAuth, OpenSocial, sessionspeakers: Adam Nash, Daniel Raffel, Chris Messina, Angus Logan, Ryan Sarver, Chris Cole, Kara Swisher (moderator), speakers: messina, sessionabstract: With the advent of social protocols like OAuth, OpenID and ActivityStrea.ms, it's clear that the web has gone social and is becoming more open. Adam Nash (LinkedIn), Daniel Raffel (Yahoo), Chris Messina (Google), Angus Logan (Microsoft), Ryan Sarver (Twitter), and Chris Cole (MySpace) will discuss the importance of such emerging technologies, how they've adopted them in their products and debate what's next. Kara Swisher will moderate., sessionrequirements: An interest in the social web, sessionlink: where-is-the-social-web-going-next, sessionhashtag: #socialfuture, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.8A, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BYTqpC7ZkBXT, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BYTqpC7ZkBXT, waveid: w+YTqpC7ZkBXT</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bh1a0'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bifuh</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 70</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 1:00pm-2:00pm, room: 9, product: OpenSocial, track: Social Web, Enterprise, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Best practices for implementing OpenSocial in the Enterprise, tags: OpenSocial, Enterprise, sessionspeakers: Mark Weitzel, Matt Tucker, Mark Halvorson, Helen Chen, Chris Schalk, speakers: cschalk, sessionabstract: Enterprise deployments of OpenSocial technologies brings an additional set of considerations that may not be apparent in a traditional social network implementation. In this session, several enterprise vendors will demonstrate how they've been working together to address these issues in a collection of "Best Practices". This session will also provide a review of existing challenges for enterprise implementations of OpenSocial., sessionrequirements: General understanding of OpenSocial technologies. Some Enterprise experience is also recommended., sessionlink: opensocial-enterprise-panel, sessionhashtag: #opensocial, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.89, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BWDgRyLZkfF, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BWDgRyLZkfF, waveid: w+WDgRyLZkfF</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bifuh'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/ba0fz</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 71</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 4:15pm-5:15pm, room: 5, track: Tech Talks, sessiontype: Tech Talk, sessiontitle: Ignite Google I/O, tags: Ignite, geek culture, sessionspeakers: Brady Forrest, Annalee Newitz, Ben Huh, Matt Harding, Clay Johnson, Bradley Vickers, Aaron Koblin, Michael Van Riper, Anne Veling, James Young, sessionabstract: &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://ignite.oreilly.com"&gt;Ignite&lt;/a&gt; captures the best of geek culture in a series of five-minute speed presentations. Each speaker gets 20 slides that auto-advance after 15 seconds. Check out &lt;a href="http://code.google.com/events/io/2009/sessions/IgniteGoogleIO.html"&gt;last year's Ignite Google I/O&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Presenting this year's Ignite Google I/O speakers:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.techsploitation.com/"&gt;Annalee Newitz&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="http://io9.com"&gt;io9&lt;/a&gt;) - Weird Science
 &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.benhuh.com/"&gt;Ben Huh&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="http://icanhascheezburger.com/"&gt;I Can has Cheez Burger&lt;/a&gt;) - &lt;strong&gt;Evolution of the Meme&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Matt_Harding"&gt;Matt Harding&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="http://www.wherethehellismatt.com/"&gt;Where The Hell Is Matt?&lt;/a&gt;) - &lt;strong&gt;The Imaginary Line of Ancient Cosmic Weirdness &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://twitter.com/cjoh"&gt;Clay Johnson&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="http://sunlightfoundation.com/"&gt;Sunlight Foundation&lt;/a&gt;) - &lt;strong&gt;Tales from the District: How Washington Publishes Data&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/nwrower"&gt;Bradley Vickers&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;strong&gt;How to Row across the North Atlantic, Ration Food and Not Have Your Teammates Eat You&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.aaronkoblin.com/"&gt;Aaron Koblin&lt;/a&gt; (Google/&lt;a href="http://www.thesheepmarket.com/"&gt;Sheep Market&lt;/a&gt;) - &lt;strong&gt;Digital Art&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://van-riper.blogspot.com/"&gt;Michael Van Riper&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;strong&gt;Confessions of a Serial Community Organizer&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;a href="http://www.beyondtrees.com/weblog/"&gt;Anne Veling&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;strong&gt;Feeling Lonely on Google Wave&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://twitter.com/jamesyoung6979"&gt;James Young&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;strong&gt;You Sank My Battleship!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;, sessionrequirements: Affinity for geek culture, sessionlink: ignite-google-io, sessionhashtag: #ignitegoogleio, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BO4sGNLZkCK4, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BO4sGNLZkCK4, waveid: w+O4sGNLZkCK4</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/ba0fz'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bbf0c</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 72</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 10:45am-11:45am, room: 9, product: Closure Library, track: Tech Talks, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Opening up Closure Library, tags: Closure Tools, Closure Library, JavaScript, sessionspeakers: Nathan Naze, speakers: nnaze, sessionabstract: Closure Library is the open-source JavaScript library behind some of Google's big web apps like Gmail and Google Docs. This session will tour the broad library, its object-oriented design, and its namespaced organization.  We'll explain how it works and how to integrate it in your setup, both for development and optimized for a live application using Closure Compiler., sessionrequirements: The session assumes JavaScript and web development experience., sessionlink: closure-library, sessionhashtag: #techtalks-closure, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.64, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252Bv7BXJrZkBME, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252Bv7BXJrZkBME, waveid: w+v7BXJrZkBME</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bbf0c'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bctkt</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 73</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 10:15am-11:15am, room: 4, product: Go Programming Language, track: Tech Talks, sessiontype: Tech Talk, sessiontitle: Go programming, tags: Go, open source, language, C, C++, Java, Python, sessionspeakers: Rob Pike, Russ Cox, speakers: r, rsc, sessionabstract: The Go programming language was released as an open source project in late 2009. This session will illustrate how programming in Go differs from other languages through a set of examples demonstrating features particular to Go.  These include concurrency, embedded types, methods on any type, and program construction using interfaces. Very little time will be spent waiting for compilation., sessionrequirements: Programming experience in a language such as C, C++, Java, or Python.  Some familiarity with Go helpful but not required., sessionlink: go-programming, sessionhashtag: #techtalks-go, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.8D, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BWDgRyLZkb2, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BWDgRyLZkb2, waveid: w+WDgRyLZkb2</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bctkt'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bpgoi</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 74</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 11:30am-12:30pm, room: 2, track: Tech Talks, sessiontype: Tech Talk, sessiontitle: How to lose friends and alienate people: The joys of engineering leadership, tags: Engineering, leadership, management, storytelling, sessionspeakers: Brian W. Fitzpatrick, Ben Collins-Sussman, speakers: fitz, sussman, sessionabstract: Are you considered the 'point' person for your team? Do you have sweaty palms, headaches, and a calendar full of meetings? You may have an affliction called 'manager'. 3 out of 4 engineers aren't aware of this condition, but it is treatable through careful analysis and therapy. We'll examine how you may have arrived at this state and how you can once again regain your self-respect and the respect of your peers. Hear real-life stories of both good and bad leadership. Learn to lead by following., sessionrequirements: Sense of humor, sessionlink: lose-friends-alienate-people-engineering-leadership, sessionhashtag: #techtalks-leadership, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.8E, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252B9rTSb7ZkBlS, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252B9rTSb7ZkBlS, waveid: w+9rTSb7ZkBlS</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bpgoi'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bqv8z</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 75</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 2:15pm-3:15pm, room: 8, product: Web Search, track: Tech Talks, sessiontype: Tech Talk, sessiontitle: SEO site advice from the experts, tags: Search, SEO, site architecture, sessionspeakers: Matt Cutts, Greg Grothaus, Evan Roseman, speakers: matt, greggrothaus, eroseman, sessionabstract: A perfect opportunity to get your website reviewed by the experts in the Google Search Quality team. Attendees can get concrete search engine optimization (SEO) feedback on their own sites. We'll also answer real-life questions that affect developers when it comes to optimizing their websites for search., sessionrequirements: Perfect for web developers who want to learn more about search engine optimization (SEO), sessionlink: seo-site-review-from-experts, sessionhashtag: #techtalks-seo, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.8F, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:search,restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252B-Xhdu7ZkBLf, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:search,restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252B-Xhdu7ZkBLf, waveid: w+-Xhdu7ZkBLf</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bqv8z'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bs9tc</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 76</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 3:30pm-4:30pm, room: 9, product: Page Speed, track: Tech Talks, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Optimize every bit of your site serving and web pages with Page Speed, tags: Design, Web development, Website optimization, Page Speed, Analytics, sessionspeakers: Richard Rabbat, Bryan McQuade, speakers: rabbat, bmcquade, sessionabstract: Page Speed is an open-source Firefox/Firebug Add-on. Webmasters and web developers can use Page Speed to evaluate the performance of their web pages and to get suggestions on how to improve them. Learn about the latest rules of web development we've added, optimizations that we've updated, go over a new refreshed UI, see how to collect data through beacons to track progress over time, cut and paste fixes, and how to work with 3rd party libraries more effectively, including Google Analytics., sessionlink: optimize-site-serving-page-speed, sessionhashtag: #techtalks-speed, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.90, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BU2jwj7ZkBer, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BU2jwj7ZkBer, waveid: w+U2jwj7ZkBer</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bs9tc'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/btodt</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 77</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 1:45pm-2:45pm, room: 9, track: Tech Talks, sessiontype: Tech Talk, sessiontitle: Beyond design: Creating positive user experiences, tags: UI, UX, design, user experience, users, sessionspeakers: John Zeratsky, Matt Shobe, speakers: jazer, shobe, sessionabstract: Good user experience isn't just about good design. Learn how to create a positive user experience by being fast, open, engaged, surprising, polite, and, well... being yourself. Chock full of examples from the web and beyond, this talk is a practical introduction for developers who are passionate about user experience but may not have a background in design., sessionrequirements: Willingness to let old assumptions about their inability to solve certain design challenges get a bit banged up., sessionlink: beyond-design-user-experience, sessionhashtag: #techtalks-ux, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.97, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BtaQlR7ZkBhw, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BtaQlR7ZkBhw, waveid: w+taQlR7ZkBhw</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/btodt'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bjueu</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 78</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 3:00pm-4:00pm, room: 4, track: Tech Talks, sessiontype: Tech Talk, sessiontitle: Technology, innovation, computer science, &amp; more: VC panel, tags: VC, venture capital, technology, sessionspeakers: Albert Wenger, Chris Dixon, Dave McClure, Brad Feld, Paul Graham, Dick Costolo (moderator), sessionabstract: What do notable tech-minded VCs think about big trends happening today? In this session, you'll get to hear from and ask questions to a panel of well-respected investors, all of whom are programmers by trade. Albert Wenger, Chris Dixon, Dave McClure, Paul Graham, and Brad Feld will duke it out on a number of hot tech topics with Dick Costolo moderating.   , sessionrequirements: None, sessionlink: tech-innovation-cs-vc-panel, sessionhashtag: #techtalks-vc, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.65, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252Bv_K9zbZkBXX, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252Bv_K9zbZkBXX, waveid: w+v_K9zbZkBXX</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bjueu'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bo245</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 79</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 12:30pm-1:30pm, room: 8, product: Google Wave, track: Wave, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Google Wave API design principles: Anatomy of a great extension, tags: Wave, sessionspeakers: Pamela Fox, Michael Goderbauer (Hasso Plattner Institute), speakers: pamelafox, sessionabstract: Google Wave is all about collaboration, and the most successful extensions are user-friendly and collaborative. Wave robots should be as intuitive to communicate with as a human, and play well with other robots; Wave gadgets should extend the metaphors of the textual collaboration into the visual. In this talk, we'll discuss the design and privacy principles you should consider while building extensions, and show examples of extensions that demonstrate these principles. , sessionrequirements: Basic understanding of the Google Wave extensions APIs (gadgets and robots), sessionlink: wave-api-design-extensions, sessionhashtag: #wave1, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.62, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BkrgNvLZkBh6, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BkrgNvLZkBh6, waveid: w+krgNvLZkBh6</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bo245'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bmnjo</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 80</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 3:00pm-4:00pm, room: 8, product: Google Wave, track: Wave, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Waving across the web, tags: Wave, sessionspeakers: Dhanji Prasanna, Douwe Osinga, speakers: dhanji, douwe, sessionabstract: This talk focuses on using the Google Wave APIs outside of the Google Wave product. We'll show how to take advantage of embedded waves for commenting and discussions on your website, how to integrate with WaveThis to make your website more collaborative, and how to use the wave data APIs to get access to wave content from your website., sessionrequirements: JavaScript. Basic understanding of Google Wave is helpful., sessionlink: waving-across-the-web, sessionhashtag: #wave2, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.9C
, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BuH6OdLZkCY3.7, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BuH6OdLZkCY3.7, waveid: w+uH6OdLZkCY3.7</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bmnjo'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/c0p7u</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 81</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Wednesday May 19, sessiontime: 4:15pm-5:15pm, room: 8, product: Google Wave, track: Wave, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Open source Google Wave: Building your own wave provider, tags: Wave, Open Source, sessionspeakers: Dan Peterson, Jochen Bekmann, J.D. Zamfirescu Pereira, David LaPalomento (Novell), speakers: dpeterson, jochen, zamfi, sessionabstract: Learn how to build your own wave service. Google is open sourcing the lion's share of the code that went into creating Google Wave to help bootstrap a network of federated providers. This talk will discuss the state of the reference implementation: the software architecture, how you can plug it into your own use cases -- and how you can contribute to the code and definition of the underlying specification., sessionrequirements: XMPP knowledge is useful. Some Java proficiency is helpful, sessionlink: open-source-wave-provider, sessionhashtag: #wave3, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.63, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BTeHZ97ZkBEG, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BTeHZ97ZkBEG, waveid: w+TeHZ97ZkBEG</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/c0p7u'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bl8zb</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 82</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 11:30am-12:30pm, room: 8, product: Google Wave, track: Wave, sessiontype: 201, sessiontitle: Making smart &amp; scalable Wave robots, tags: Wave, App Engine, sessionspeakers: David Byttow, Marcel Prasetya, speakers: davidbyttow, mprasetya, sessionabstract: A smart robot must be able to store persistent data. Wave robots can store data in wave structures, like wavelets, datadocs, and annotations, instead of traditional datastores. A scalable robot must perform operations with minimal bandwidth. Wave robots can optimize by selecting the appropriate amount of context, the optimal events, and narrow filters for events. In this talk, we'll share best practices on data storage and scaling. , sessionrequirements: Understanding of Google Wave robots, and Google App Engine, the ideal attendee has already built robots in the past, sessionlink: smart-scalable-wave-robots, sessionhashtag: #wave4, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.8B, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252BSVy-sLZkBYM, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252BSVy-sLZkBYM, waveid: w+SVy-sLZkBYM</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/bl8zb'/></entry><entry><id>http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/c3ico</id><updated>2010-05-10T18:39:11.857Z</updated><category scheme='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006' term='http://schemas.google.com/spreadsheets/2006#list'/><title type='text'>Row: 83</title><content type='text'>sessiondate: Thursday May 20, sessiontime: 3:30pm-4:30pm, room: 8, product: Google Wave, track: Wave, Enterprise, sessiontype: 101, sessiontitle: Google Wave and the enterprise environment, tags: Wave, Enterprise, sessionspeakers: Greg D'alesandre, Alan Green, Kris Muller (Salesforce.com), speakers: gregd, alangreen, sessionabstract: Google Wave provides enterprises with an opportunity to streamline a variety of communications. One of the main ways this occurs is through building generalized and custom extensions. This session will cover some of the existing enterprise extensions that have been built as well as give a sneak peak as to what's in progress. If you're wondering how Wave can be used to help build your business, you'll want to attend this session. , sessionrequirements: Basic understanding of Google Wave is helpful, sessionlink: google-wave-enterprise, sessionhashtag: #wave5, moderatorlink: http://www.google.com/moderator/#15/e=68f0&amp;t=68f0.8C, wavelink: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com!w%252Bo01RhLZkBH7, _e8rn7: https://wave.google.com/wave/#restored:wave:googlewave.com, _dmair: w%252Bo01RhLZkBH7, waveid: w+o01RhLZkBH7</content><link rel='self' type='application/atom+xml' href='http://spreadsheets.google.com/feeds/list/t0bDxnEqbFO4XuYpkA070Nw/od6/public/basic/c3ico'/></entry></feed>